Happy Halloween, everyone!
Oh, that's great.
Hey. Happy Halloween.
Jan called.
Okay.
I know why she's calling.
It's the end of the month,
and I was supposed to let somebody
go by the end of the month.
And somehow I'm supposed
to put on a costume and smile.
Okay.
Jan Levinson's office.
Hey, Sherry,
Michael Scott returning.
Oh, she's in a meeting.
She just wanted the name
of the employee you let go.
Well, I'm gonna wait
until the end of the day,
because the book said it's best
to wait until the end of the day.
I just need the name of who
you're planning to let go.
I don't know yet.
I will have to call her back.
I know she wanted the name.
Okay, Sherry?
Yeah.
If you were getting fired,
how would you wanna be told
so that you could still be
friends with the person firing you?
Jan wants the name
as soon as possible, Michael.
Thanks. I'll call her back.
I wish I could fire Sherry.
Hey, I'm still here.
Okay. I'm sorry.
Yeah.
No.
Okay.
Bye.
Hanging up now.
I mean, you hear
about layoffs in the news,
but when you actually have to do it
yourself, it is heavy stuff. It's...
I mean, these are people's
lives you're talking about.
You wanted me?
Yes.
Papier-mache?
Yes. Yes.
Um...
Pam, I have to let
somebody go today.
This is the hardest thing
I've ever had to do.
Why did you put it off
until Halloween?
Because it's very scary stuff.
I think it's gonna put a
damper on the party a little.
You're worried about the party?
There's a man's life at stake here.
So it's a man?
No.
Or woman. A human life.
If you had to guess
who it would be
based on their job performance
and who you think deserves to
be fired, who would that be?
I just answer the phone.
And sometimes you just
let it go to voicemail.
Your costume is fantastic.
I know. I sent away for
it in July from a catalog.
Oh, no. Don't, don't,
don't, don't.
Okay.
Oh, man.
Okay, I have to fire somebody.
What is that? What
are you supposed to be?
I'm the three-hole
punch version of Jim,
'cause you can have me either way,
plain white Jim or three-hole punch.
That's great. I like it.
Oh? Yeah.
Yeah, well, look.
What about me?
What are...
What are you? A monk?
I'm a Sith lord.
Oh, big deal.
Three round pieces of paper
taped to a shirt.
This cost me $129.
Ass.
Hey, you guys
excited about the party?
It's gonna be fun.
Yeah.
Yes.
Oh, and look at you.
Showing your colors.
Don't you wish you wore a dress
every day. What are you implying?
All good. Happy Halloween.
What happened to all of those
spooky decorations that we had,
the cobwebs and such?
Yeah, I don't know.
We put them all up last night.
Well, you know what? Go buy some
more. I'll approve the overages.
Sound good?
Yeah.
Good.
Oh, yeah, also,
about budget stuff...
Um...
I'm gonna need you to find, like, a
full employee salary plus benefits.
Like 50 grand.
I'm gonna need you to find
50 grand in the numbers.
But we don't keep
two sets of books.
Well, that's not what I'm
saying. Just, you know, find it.
Pretend that your jobs
depend on it.
Interesting take on Dorothy.
I love it.
Hey, you know what would even be
better? A soccer ball and cleats.
Why is that?
Bend It Like Beckham.
Oh, like the movie about the
Indian girl who plays soccer?
Yeah, that would be perfect.
Yeah, I mean,
I guess I could do that.
It'd be funny. I don't really
play soccer or anything.
Well, I don't really
have two heads. So...
Wait, what are you again?
Oh, right. Three-hole punch!
Okay, greatest strength.
Okay, okay.
A dog-like obedience
to authority. Nice.
But that doesn't sound good.
Okay, okay.
How about the ultimate
team player?
Dwight is special.
But I don't believe that his talents
are being used in this office.
So Pam and I
have put his resume
on Monster. Com,
Google, Craig's List.
We're really interested most in
jobs that take Dwight out of state.
Preferably Alaska or India.
He's a gun nut.
Sticks to his guns.
Well, I looked through
all the budgets
and there is one department... Yes.
...that has three people...
Yeah.
...doing the work
that could be done by two.
This is great.
Oh.
Yeah.
Who do you think it
should be? Jim, definitely.
No, Jim brings in money.
Phyllis?
No.
Stanley, Pam,
Oscar, Meredith,
Kevin, Angela.
It's not a popularity contest.
Although it does make sense
to fire the least popular
because that has
the least effect on morale.
One of the warehouse guys.
What?
There is someone left off that
list? Who? Who is he saying?
You're right. I didn't
even think of him.
No, Michael.
Yeah, that's actually
a really good idea. No.
No. Not me.
Yeah, I could.
Not Dwight. I'm not
saying that's what he said.
I know that's what he said.
What?
Tell him not Dwight.
That is not a very nice thing
to say about him.
Tell him to stop.
Are you kidding?
Quiet, you!
I agree.
He'd land on his feet.
Make him be quiet.
Those aren't chips and dip.
No, I made brownies.
What?
I'm just trying to figure out
why you're sabotaging things.
I made brownies. And I
made cookies. Same category.
I'm guessing Angela's
the one in the neighborhood
who gives the trick-or-treaters
some toothbrushes,
pennies,
walnuts...
Dunder Mifflin, this is Pam.
Yeah.
Just one second. I will transfer
you to our manager, Michael Scott.
Wow.
Michael Scott here.
Yes, I am regional manager
of this orifice.
Hmm-hmm.
Dwight Schrute is amazing.
Yeah.
No, he is actually the single
greatest employee of his generation.
Hmm-hmm.
You know what?
I'm gonna tell you what.
You hire Dwight K. Schrute
and he does not meet,
nay, exceed every one
of your wildest expectations,
well, then, you can hold me,
Michael Gary Scott
personally and
financially responsible.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
Okay.
Stanley, could you come
with me, please? No.
As Assistant Regional Manager... To the?
Look, I've got some bad news.
You're fired. You need to
pack up your things and go.
I'm serious, Stanley.
It's over. I'm sorry.
"You're fired. "
Get your fingers off my phone.
So, how did it go with
Stanley? How did he take it?
He wouldn't listen to me.
Oh, come on.
If you wanna fire him, you're
gonna have to tell him yourself.
I don't wanna fire Stanley.
I never said that.
I'm certainly not going
to do it myself.
Get those big baleful
eyes staring at me.
Yikes. Just... Okay, just...
Cumberland Mills?
And how did you get my resume?
Oh, no, no. I'm very
flattered. Don't get me wrong.
I'm just not sure that
it's my official resume
or if it's something
that maybe
a satisfied customer
posted online.
What does it say
under martial arts training?
Oh, okay, I'm gonna
have to supplement that.
Could I have your fax number?
Would I ever leave this company?
Look, I'm all about loyalty.
In fact, I feel like part of what I'm
getting paid for here is my loyalty.
But if there were somewhere else
that valued that loyalty more highly,
I'm going wherever
they value loyalty the most.
Oh, hey.
Oh, your dress is stuck
in the back. Gotta just...
Oh.
So you got the fax.
So why didn't you add it
to the resume?
What do you mean? Of course,
martial arts training is relevant.
Oh, excuse me,
I know about a billion Asians
that would beg to differ.
Yeah, I get a little frustrated
when I'm dealing with incompetence!
Well, you know what?
You can go to hell, too,
and I will see you there
burning.
Fine. Oh, wait, so you'll let me
know when you've made a decision...
Jim is really talented.
And he should be the one who's
getting a better job offer.
Like, for real.
Don't take this the wrong way,
but you should go for that job.
Um...
It's in Maryland.
Yeah.
But, I mean,
look at the salary,
and it's definitely
a step up and a challenge.
Yeah.
Yeah. You know what, maybe...
Maybe I will.
Jim.
This is called
leveraging an offer.
Michael, can I talk to
you for a moment? Oh, God.
I just thought you should know
that I was just offered a job
with better pay,
better benefits,
and a better title
at Cumberland Mills.
Fantastic.
And I turned it down.
What? That would have
solved all my problems.
Out of loyalty to this
company. Oh, you idiot. Go.
So I was hoping to be made Assistant
Regional Manager officially.
If you left, I wouldn't
have to fire anybody.
But then you wouldn't
have me here. Big deal.
Oh, it would have worked out
so well. Can you get it back?
It's in Maryland. You could
call. Can you call them?
I can't... I suppose I... No.
They never really made me
an offer anyway.
Why are you torturing me?
God.
Honestly, I don't think Michael has the
slightest clue of who he's gonna fire.
I think he keeps hoping that
someone's gonna volunteer,
or be run over by a bus
before the deadline.
But in the end, really,
what's gonna happen is
it's gonna be the first person to
give him a dirty look in the hall.
And therein lies the true
essence of his charisma.
Can I speak to you a minute?
Yes.
Michael, I really didn't
mean to... Help me.
I'm sorry? I want you
to role-play firing me.
I want you to fire me,
and I will take it.
Oh, you want me to be you.
Yes.
Okay. I want you to be
me and I will be Creed.
Oh, are you firing Creed?
No, no, no.
That's just first thing...
Came... Can't... That head...
We should switch seats in order
to... Yes, that's a good idea.
All right?
Excuse me.
I'm really sorry,
but I have to let you go.
And it's purely budgetary.
It's not personal...
I'm gonna kill myself!
Wow.
I'm going to kill myself
and it's your fault!
That's an overreaction.
Corporate is really
breathing down my neck
and they're saying this has to
be done by the end of the month...
Is this you? Are you being
you? Or is this Creed?
Are you...
I am...
This is Creed.
Okay.
I'm improvising.
So just try to keep up.
And I'm very angry.
Hold that thought.
And I want... I'm gonna
kill you. Michael Scott here.
I'm gonna kill you for firing me. Toby.
I really have to take this,
Creed,
so it was really a pleasure
working with you, okay?
Get off. Get off.
No, no. Just get up.
Just, just... Yeah.
What happened?
It wasn't me.
Oh, that was, like, crazy,
because I was... Yeah, I know.
Hey, Creed?
Could I talk to you
for a second?
You are great
and very ambitious,
and I feel like you want more than
this little office has to offer.
And I understand that you'd
want to just spread your wings
and fly the coop.
What are you telling me?
We're gonna have to...
You want something better.
No, I don't.
I wanna stay right here.
No, you wanna leave.
No, I wanna stay here.
Now, why are you
making this so hard?
I think there's a
misunderstanding about this.
I think you're right.
Can I go?
No, of course you can't go!
We haven't even started
this horrible process of...
Okay, Creed.
I need to let
somebody go today.
They told me I need to
let somebody go.
And as much as I think you're
a great guy, and I like you,
you're... Goodbye.
Let's fight it.
Let's call Jan and fight this
thing together like the old days.
What old days?
What are you talking about?
Did you start
the paperwork yet?
It's right here
on the desk, yeah.
You don't have to do this,
Michael. I can't, though.
Undo it!
I can't change anything.
This is the way it... No.
You have the power to undo it.
I don't. Okay, just let's
not... You can undo it.
Michael, undo it!
Yeah, I went hunting once.
Shot the deer in the leg.
Had to kill it with a shovel,
took about an hour.
Why do you ask?
I have to fire someone
today. Okay?
Fine. Fire someone else.
Fire Devon. He's terrible.
I am so much better
at my job than Devon.
Okay, well, I already
picked you and you know that,
so, unless I just
go through with this,
you're always gonna look at me
as the guy who almost fired you.
No, no, no, no, no, no. I will
forget so fast. You will be my savior.
You're the guy
who gave me my life back.
Thank you. I knew
you'd see it my way, Michael.
God bless you.
You're a fine man.
Don't...
Listen, you will not
regret this, either.
Devon is terrible.
No one's gonna miss him.
Good, good, good, good.
Devon, could I
talk to you for a second?
Creed's an idiot. You
know that. Well, he...
No, no, no, no, no, no. You
had it right the first time!
Well, maybe I did. Exactly,
you gotta go with your gut, man.
No, I can't...
No, I can't go back.
I would look like an idiot.
That's why I'm being fired?
No.
So you might not look
like an idiot?
No, it was all the stuff
that I said.
It was the business downturn
and cutbacks, and...
You...
God, this is unbelievable!
I just hope that you
and I can remain friends.
Devon, wait. Please.
What?
Look, look.
In addition to severance
and everything,
I want to give you
this gift certificate
to Chili's from me.
Okay? No hard feelings.
Kevin, Jim, Pam, Kelly,
Toby, Oscar, Meredith,
Phyllis, Stanley, or the temp.
If any of you wanna meet me for a
drink, I'm gonna be at Poor Richard's.
And the rest of you
can go to hell.
What about
the Halloween party?
Oh, hey, Jim. Wait, stop.
I'm sorry for pushing you
toward Cumberland.
Seriously, if you left here,
I would blow my brains out.
Come on.
That's just
a figure of speech, you know.
Blow your brains out? Come on.
All it really means is
that we're friends.
And who else is she gonna
talk to if I'm gone? Right?
I mean, if she left,
I wouldn't blow my brains out.
Of course, I would take that job in
Maryland because it's double the pay
and soft-shell crab just
happens to be my favorite food.
I love Halloween.
You know, it's just... But it's
just fun. Every year, it's just fun.
Last Halloween, I came
as Janet Jackson's boob.
It was topical. People
got a big kick out of it.
The year before that
I came as Monica Lewinsky,
and I wore a stained dress.
The year before that, I
also came as Monica Lewinsky,
and before that I was O. J.
It was pretty funny.
Oh, I wish you were
here last year.
Trick-or-treat!
Hey. How you doing?
Wow, you guys look great!
I'm a bumble bee.
You look great.
And you're a princess?
A fairy princess.
A fairy princess. You're
very... I'm a lion!
You're a lion. Wow.
I wanna hear your...
Oh! Okay, that's all yours.
That's all yours. Okay!
Grab it. Grab it.
You know what? You guys
are getting all of these.