JOSH: The Stamford branch is closing,
and everybody's just packing up their stuff.
Andy Bernard made these tasteful hats.
That's the other thing
you have to watch out... Yo, Tuna.
I wanna talk to you about this new boss,
Michael Scott.
Yeah?
So what's he like?
Likes, dislikes, favorite sports,
favorite movies, favorite men's magazines.
You know what?
I think you just need to meet him.
Playing your cards close to the vest. I get it.
Good luck over there, Tuna.
Cross me and I will destroy you.
Sounds good, Andy.
This is gonna be an adventure.
Yes, this is going to be very interesting.
All right, I'm out of here.
See you later?
Bro.
Hey, is that Josh's computer?
What?
PAM: Hey!
Hey!
How'd the run go?
Pretty good. I finished.
That's great.
Yes.
Why is that great?
Because he accomplished something.
What was your mile time?
About seven.
I could beat that on a skateboard.
Well, that has wheels.
Yeah, well, my feet don't,
and I can still crush that time.
Really, Dwight? How fast are you?
Let's just put it this way.
Last weekend,
I outran a black pepper snake.
Really?
I am fast.
To give you a reference point,
I'm somewhere between
a snake and a mongoose.
And a panther.
Man, what is taking Toby so long?
Oh, I'll just time him later.
And you'll compare the times?
Yeah.
Are you ready? Set, go!
No, my groin's really tight, I can't...
Am I being mean to Dwight?
I don't know.
I did just make him run around the building,
and I have no intention of timing him.
This isn't even a stopwatch.
It's a digital thermometer.
He does make my life harder sometimes,
and on purpose.
Like, he tried to put meters
on the bathroom stalls
as a way of bringing in
more money for the company.
Hey, three more laps to go!
You gotta pick it up
if you're gonna beat Toby!
(GRUNTING)
I should probably get back to work.
Here. Who's here?
Nametag?
Yes, please.
Karen Filippelli.
Karen...
Karen a-Filippelli!
Probably Italian.
Possibly Filipina.
Okay...
My branch is absorbing
the Stamford branch.
Or as I like to put it,
my family is doubling in size.
And that's all
I'm gonna say about it,
because I have a gigantic performance
ahead of me,
and I have to get into my head and focus.
Who's next?
That's Andy Bernard.
Andy Bernard.
If I were you...
St. Bernard.
...I would fire Anthony Gardner...
What?
...before noon...
I'm not...
...to consolidate power.
I'm not firing somebody on the first day.
No, no, not somebody. Gardner!
The Japanese camp guards of World War II
always chose one man to kill
whenever a batch of new prisoners arrived.
I always wondered how they chose
the man who was to die.
I think I would have been good
at choosing the person.
Good morning!
Got the food, good!
Looky, looky, looky. What I want you to do...
Set it up in the conference room, please.
Make it look nice,
as if you were trying to impress
a much older man
who's way out of your league.
Okay.
Yes, I'm in a good mood today.
I'm excited to meet all of the new people
and to see my old friend again, definitely.
That's always a thing
that makes people happy,
to have an old friend back.
HANNAH: Hello?
Ding, ding, ding, ding, ding.
Our first arrival.
Welcome to Scranton.
This is Hannah Smoterich-Barr!
Hannah Smoterich-Barr!
Welcome to our humble abode.
Follow me to your desk.
Your ball-and-chain is right over here.
You know, a lot of these people,
this is the only family they have.
So, as far as I'm concerned,
this says, "World's Best Dad."
There he is!
Tony... What's your last name?
Gardner.
Gardner! I knew that.
There you go, gift bag for you. Okay!
Thanks.
Michael, I didn't get a gift bag.
Well, they're just for guests.
If there are any left over,
you can buy one later.
My bag's mostly pencils.
Well, and coupons to various hot spots
around Scranton. All right!
Let me show you to your area, sir.
MICHAEL: Come on, big guy.
Can I have your pencils?
No.
Hi!
Hi.
I'm Pam.
Karen. I love your sweater.
Oh, thanks. My mom made it for me.
Really? That's so cool.
I've always wanted to learn
how to knit.
Welcome, welcome, welcome!
Take me to your leader.
Oh, wait, I am your leader.
Wait, are you a robot or a Martian?
I am actually your boss, Michael Scott.
Hi.
Welcome.
Wow, you are very exotic-Iooking.
Was your dad a GI, or...
I'll be the number-two guy here in Scranton
in six weeks.
How?
Name repetition, personality mirroring,
and never breaking off a handshake.
I'm always thinking one step ahead,
like a carpenter that makes stairs.
ANDY: Hello.
You must be Andy Bernard.
Aloha and welcome!
And you must be Michael Scott.
Aloha and hello.
Very good. Welcome to our little kingdom.
We have a bag of nifty gifties for you.
Well, Michael, thank you for welcoming me
to your little kingdom. Mike.
Nifty!
They are nifty!
They're nifty gifties.
You know who I really like
is this guy Andy Bernard.
He has got this very likeable way about him.
...which is why they need a passing game.
Right?
No way! Get him out of here.
We don't want any of this kind in here.
Good to see you, man!
Wow, okay!
How are you? Martin Nash, I presume?
This is a little gift bag for you
free of charge.
Follow me,
I will show you where all the slaves work.
Not... So your desk is...
Hi, I'm Jim. I'm new here.
Oh, my God, it's really you!
I was just doing a little joke there
about how we'd never met.
I know, I don't care.
Awesome! Good to be back.
The place looks really good.
It's really good to see you.
You, too.
Where do I stand with Pam?
No idea. I mean, we're friends.
Always have been friends.
That is where we stand.
DWIGHT: Well, well, well.
Look what the cat dragged in
from Stamford.
Hey, Dwight.
Fact.
I am older. I am wiser. Do not mess with me.
Okay, sounds good.
What are you doing?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Do I have a smudge on my forehead?
No, you look good.
Why are you looking at my forehead?
I'm not.
Meet my eye line, Jim!
I am.
Stop acting like an idiot!
Okay.
Hey, buddy. Welcome back.
Hey.
How are you, man? Good to see you.
I'm good. How are you?
So...
Oh, I'm sorry, are you sitting here now?
Yeah.
Unless you really, really want it back.
You know, man, it's really your call.
Cool, thank you.
Let me get that for you.
Got it?
This one taken? No? Good.
Yeah, Jim is a nice guy.
That's why I got the desk.
Michael Scott, thank you.
I appreciate it, Mike.
MICHAEL: All right.
Hello. I don't believe we've been introduced.
Dwight Schrute,
Assistant Regional Manager.
Andy Bernard,
Regional Director in Charge of Sales.
So you'll be reporting to me, then.
On the contrary.
My title has "manager" in it.
And I'm a director.
Which, on a film set,
is the highest title there is.
Do you know anything about film?
I know everything about film.
I've seen over 240 of them.
Congratulations.
Hey, Toby.
Hey, Jim.
How are you, man?
Oh, really good!
I just wanted to say hi.
How are you? Hey, welcome back.
Oh, is that, like, your new thing, or...
No, I'm sorry, that's...
No, that's cool.
No, it's nothing, we'll just...
All right. Good to be back.
So...
Okay.
All right.
All right. Sorry about that.
No problem.
It was...
What?
Nothing.
"I present the orientation video."
We need to talk.
Not now.
Which is higher,
Assistant Regional Manager,
or Regional Director in Charge of Sales?
I told you the titles are irrelevant.
They just relate to pay scale.
Okay, so who gets paid more, me or Andy?
It is not a matter of more or less.
Your pay is just different, okay?
All right! Showtime, part one.
Okay, who reports to who?
I don't care, Dwight!
You all report to me. That's all that matters!
The rest of it just work out
amongst yourselves, okay?
And then if I want...
Work it out amongst yourselves, please!
I have a company to run.
Will you let me run the company?
I... One...
Will you? Please?
KELLY: Jim!
Kelly!
Oh, my God, I have so much to tell you!
Really?
Yes. Tom Cruise and Katie Holmes,
they had a baby and they named it Suri,
and then Brad Pitt and Angelina Jolie,
they had a baby, too,
and they named it Shiloh.
And both babies are amazing!
Great. What's new with you?
I just told you.
Okay, everybody settled in? Good.
Why don't we all proceed
into the conference room,
or should I say the banquet hall?
For... Drum roll, please.
(IMITATING DRUM ROLL)
The official
Merger Day All-Family Welcome Breakfast.
Come on in!
MICHAEL: Don't be shy.
Hey, champagne.
No, no, guests only.
Smoked salmon!
No, for the guests it is,
for you, consider it cow meat.
Strictly taboo.
I eat beef.
Well, then, consider it poisoned beef.
It's no touchee.
The beef is poisoned?
No, it's not beef! Just...
Sit down, please. Welcome, help yourself.
You might want these orientation materials.
Wrong, Toby, this is an orientation,
not a bore-ientation.
Okay, do not worry. All of your questions
are about to be answered.
Cell phones and pagers off, please.
Oh, this looks promising.
You won't be disappointed.
MICHAEL: Let's face it, moving to a new job
can be very stressful,
so I have made an orientation video
especially for you newcomers.
But it's not like any orientation video
that any of you have ever seen.
It's funny.
It's got a little bit of a zing to it.
And I hope that it gives you a flavor
of what we're all about
here at Dunder Mifflin,
and what we're all about here in Scranton.
So let's just all laugh together.
And watch...
(MICHAEL READING)
Sittin' in my office
With a plate of grilled bacon
Call my man Dwight
Just to see what was shakin'!
Yo, Mike, our town is dope and pretty
So check out how we live
In the Electric City!
They call it Scranton!
What?
The Electric City! Scranton!
The Electric City!
Call Poison Control if you're bit by a spider!
But check that it's covered
By your healthcare provider!
It reminds me of the orientation video
Michael showed on my first day,
The Scranton Witch Project.
I am so scared
when people don't label their personal food.
You like coalmines and you wanna see 'em?
Well, check it out, yo
the Anthracite Museum
Plenty of space in the parkin' lot!
But the little cars go in the compact spot!
Spot! Spot! Spot!
Well, so far, I think it is killing.
I thought it would either be
an A or an A-plus,
but I completely forgot
that there is an A-plus-plus.
DWIGHT: What?
This is Karen Filippelli,
please leave a message.
Terrible. Totally unconvincing.
This is Karen Filippelli,
please leave a message.
Not bad.
But you are Italian, so try it more Italian.
This is Karen a-Filippelli,
please leave-a me the message.
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
You feel good? All right.
Karen Filippelli.
Hey, buddy.
Anything new to report?
Do you mean, to me from you?
'Cause that's how it works.
Sure thing, buddy.
AND Y: Am I trying to get
under his skin? Yes.
Because the angrier he gets,
the more marginalized he becomes.
Meanwhile, Andy Bernard is out there
laying on the charm.
Hey, Angela. Check this out.
It's my new screensaver.
Do you like it?
I do like it, actually.
Thank you.
You have such a pretty smile, by the way.
You're welcome.
Hey.
What happened to grape soda?
Oh, yeah, I'm trying to move away from that.
Getting into more of a bottled water phase.
You've changed so much.
Well, I'm evolving, Pam.
So when do I get to hear everything?
Are you still getting unpacked, or...
You wanna grab a coffee
or something after work?
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Tonight, actually?
No, I'm just still getting settled, so...
Oh, yeah, no, you know, whenever.
Okay.
Sorry to interrupt, I...
Nope, you're not interrupting anything.
Nope, I'm... Don't.
All right.
Okay.
I should probably get back to work.
Crack the whip. All right.
Yeah, I know, me, too.
The day's going fine.
It's been a little chaotic, but it's fine.
It's great. A lot of distractions, but it's good.
Take a picture, it'll last longer.
I'm sorry, it's just... It's a little distracting.
Ditto that, my brother.
Look what's on his computer!
What is that, a squid's eye, or...
It's my left breast.
How did you...
Right place at the right time.
Oh, what's that smell?
What smell?
There must be an air freshener
plugged in somewhere.
It smells like a funeral home.
Oh, I'll help you find it.
You know what, never mind.
What is it?
I think I'm just allergic to your perfume.
My perfume?
It's just my crazy nose.
I'm used to different smells.
Bob Vance bought this perfume for me
in metropolitan Orlando.
It's made from real pine.
Who's Bob Vance?
You've a lot to learn
about this town, sweetie.
I don't know who these new people
think they are.
I've sat downwind of Phyllis'
stinky perfumes for years.
Never said a word.
People hate people
that are different from them. That's natural.
But you know what makes people
forget their differences?
A great show.
That is why I created
the integration celebration.
This is the moment
when Scranton and Stamford
come together as one,
united in applause.
I know a lot of you must be thinking,
"Wow, what a day.
"It feels more like a night at a party
than a day at work."
Well, in my opinion,
business should feel like a night out,
a night at
the Roxbury.
Okay, there's supposed to be music,
and it's...
I got it, I got it, Dwight! Just...
Do you have batteries in there?
Stupid...
(SCATTING)
What is love?
That's it! Yes, yes! Okay. Here we go.
Baby don't hurt me
Don't hurt me no more
Let it rock, baby!
What is love? Baby don't hurt me
Here we go, here we go!
Don't hurt me no more
(EXCLAIMING)
Excuse me, excuse me, excuse me.
(BOTH SCATTING)
You and me! You and me!
Me and you! You and me!
You and me! You! You!
You! You! You and me! You! You!
Oh, my nose is so itchy.
Why is my nose so itchy?
Probably because of all the nose candy.
Okay.
I told you these guys had a sense of humor.
Very funny, Michael!
Okay.
Really funny, Michael!
All right, all right, all right, I'm on a roll.
Why are the new people on the table?
To show them that we are not above them.
Shouldn't we be equals?
Not today, no.
Tony! Please join your cohorts
on the table, if you would.
This is difficult for me.
Hey, I understand, we're all friends.
No, I mean, I can't physically.
I can't get on the table.
Oh, well...
Just use the momentum of your lower half
to hoist yourself up.
Okay?
You know what? I'll help. I will help.
No, please.
Don't...
Don't be shy. Dwight, let's do this.
Come on, we're doing this thing.
Ready? On three. One...
Let's get up.
Bend at the knees. Okay.
Here we go! Here we go!
I'm under this. I'm under this hock here.
I don't know what I'm grabbing here!
All right, all right! Stop!
Put me down!
But it feels good. Push it, push it!
I'm right in your crack!
No, put me down right now!
Don't give up! You got it, man!
Put me down right now!
I've had enough! Put me down right now!
You got it, you got it!
Wait, wait, wait, okay, okay, okay. Easy.
Hey, easy.
I'm sorry!
Don't...
It's just not going to work for me.
I have to go.
I don't understand.
I was on the fence about this,
and it's just not a good fit.
Well, we'll squeeze you in!
I can't work here.
I have to quit.
You can't quit on the first day!
That's heresy, my friend!
Okay, let's talk about this. What happened?
I mean, what...
Was it Toby? Did he say something?
'Cause he's...
No, Toby was helpful. He was very kind.
It's just your management style.
My management style? So...
Didn't you think Lazy Scranton was funny?
No.
Was it supposed to be funny?
Okay, well...
Don't bother quitting, because you're fired.
Excuse me?
You are fired!
I'm sorry,
but we don't have quitters on this team!
Just clean out your desk!
But there's nothing
in my desk except coupons.
Don't try to apologize to me, man.
It's too late! Just get out!
Take your bad vibes with you!
That was my advice.
Remember, I'm the one who suggested
that you fire him!
Probably the best advice
you ever gave me, Dwight.
And what advice has Andy given
to you today that you have acted on?
Would none be an accurate estimate?
None advice?
Fire Andy.
Dwight may have won the battle,
but I will win the next battle.
Tony was right.
This environment is dysfunctional.
Well, maybe that's because
some people treat it
like their own private Hooters strip club.
Whoa, Angela, hold on.
Hooters is a restaurant
with over 400 locations worldwide.
Back to work. We don't have to get along.
We just have to work together.
No, we do have to get along.
Can't we all just get along?
Or have we forgotten the words
of the Reverend King?
The word "merger" comes
from the word "marriage"
and that was what today was
supposed to be.
The loving union between people.
Instead, it has become like
when my mom moved in with Jeff.
And once again, it becomes my job to fix it.
Hey, hey, everybody! Something happened!
Those guys from Vance Refrigeration,
they let the air out of our tires!
What?
Yeah, they punk'd us, they punk'd us good!
Come on! Come on!
Does Bob Vance
work for Vance Refrigeration?
Does he ever.
Man, they got us so bad.
We cannot let them get away with this!
We have got to pull together as one
and steal their refrigerators!
Yeah!
Yeah?
I don't think we can do that.
Go home, Toby. Just...
Hey. Why doesn't your car have a flat tire?
Why? I will tell you why.
Because they saved the worst for me!
They put a hate note
under my windshield wiper.
Check this out, it's so hateful.
"You guys suck!
"You can never pull together as one
and revenge us!
"That is why you suck!"
For crying out loud.
No. No, no, no, no! No, you are falling for it!
You are playing right into their hands.
This is just what they want you to do!
Don't, okay.
What is with this guy?
Got an hour? I'll try to explain.
MICHAEL: This is egregious!
This is egregious!
Trust me, it only gets worse.
Is he always like this?
Sometimes he brings more costumes.
When do people work?
We find little times during the day.
How are we gonna get home?
Bob Vance has an air pump.
He said he'd fill all our tires up.
Bob Vance of Vance Refrigeration.
See that? Mission accomplished.
They're like a bunch of fourth graders.
Sometimes what brings the kids together
is hating the lunch lady.
Although, that'll change!
Because by the end of the fourth grade,
the lunch lady
was actually the person
I hung out with the most.
(MOBILE PHONE RINGING)
Jell-O. Hi, Jan.
JAN: Michael!
Did you fire Tony Gardner
when he was trying to quit?
I did. Major personnel crisis averted.
Compliment accepted.
Do you realize, Michael,
that we now have to pay him severance?
Yes.
You do?
But do you realize that
that was actually Dwight's idea?
Bad advice from my number two.
What? No, no, no, Jim is your number two.
What?
He is the only one
who has worked with both groups.
I sent you a memo about this.
Yes, I know that, for I do read the memos.
So, after a great deal of thought
and introspectivtion,
I have decided to make
Jim my new number two.
If he even wants it.
It doesn't come with a pay raise.
No, it does, actually.
So who will be your new number three?
That I have not decided yet.
Michael, I would just like to say
that you have handled
this entire situation with great aplomb.
Thank you, Andy, that's very kind, thanks.
And I have to say
that your leadership has brought...
Shut it. Shut it. That's...
Suck-up.
(MOBILE PHONE RINGING)
Hey, where you at, Filippelli?
KAREN: I'm at the grocery store buying
a corkscrew to give myself a lobotomy.
What's wrong,
you didn't have a good first day?
Oh, my God!
Hey, you wanna meet
at Cooper's in an hour? I need a drink.
Yeah, sure. Sounds good. I...
Hey, you know what?
Can I give you a call right back?
Yeah. Bye.
Okay, thanks.
Hey.
Hey!
I thought you had already left.
No, I just had some other stuff I had to do.
Good.
What's up?
Oh, nothing, I just feel bad.
I feel like things were a little weird today,
or something.
What do you mean?
I just think I should tell you
that I've sort of started seeing someone.
And...
That's totally cool.
You can do whatever you want.
Okay, good.
We're friends. We'll always be friends.
Right.
It's good to have you back.
Yeah, good to be back.
Saw your dork-mobile in the parking lot.
What does it get, like,
four miles to the gallon?
Try double that.
Classic Trans Am, vintage American muscle.
Please.
Yeah, my Xterra is pretty sweet.
Luxurious yet rugged.
Leave it to the Japanese.
Xterra's not even a real word.
Actually, it is, it's Latin for "earth."
Oh, so you drive an X-earth?
Yeah, that makes sense.
I'd rather drive a classic Trans Am
than an X-earth.
Yeah, I bet you would.
Oh, by the way, 1985 called.
It wants its car back.
Well, I hope 1985 has a time machine,
'cause I drive an '87.
Speaking of time machines?
I just got back from the future,
and I went to your funeral, and guess what?
Nobody came.
Speaking of funerals,
why don't you go ahead and go die?
That was a really well-constructed sentence.
You should be an English professor
at Cor-Not University.
Idiot!
If I were an idiot, I'd be driving a Trans Am.
If you were driving a Trans Am,
you'd be the smartest idiot
in the whole world.
(COUGHING) Idiot!
(COUGHING) You're the idiot.
(COUGHING) Nice comeback.
(COUGHING) I was making fun
of your comeback. That's why it worked.
I totally got the best of that interchange.
(COUGHING)