Oh, she's absolutely adorable.
He.
Oh, sorry. He's... He's dressed all in pink.
That's his favorite color.
Oh, that's fun for him.
Fantastic.
Oh, wow, look at that. How cute.
Thank you.
Oh, may I?
Oh, sure.
Hey, look at me! I'm a baby.
I'm one of those babies
from Look Who's Talking.
What am I thinking?
(MICHAEL LAUGHING)
Look at all those staplers. What's a stapler?
I don't even know. I'm a baby.
Hey, Mom! I'm thirsty! I'm thirsty, Mama!
I want some milk!
And you know where milk comes from?
Breasts.
(LAUGHING)
Hey.
Almost done?
Just about. Yeah.
Now.
Yes, I have started to see Karen.
It's very new and... Not really ready
to talk about it openly yet
just because I think,
once the word gets out there,
it might affect the way people behave
around us or...
I don't know. Just not yet.
Yeah, Jan, it looks like a check,
a piece of paper of some sort. Receipt.
I don't know.
Jan, this is Angela Martin from Accounting.
We have a rebate
from the Federal Work Opportunity Program
and no one knows what that means.
JAN: We get that money
for hiring an ex-convict.
I didn't hire an ex-convict,
unless they mean Toby. Convicted rapist.
I'm just kidding.
When did the check come?
Last week.
Okay, that's when the branches merged.
So Josh must have been taking
advantage of this program. Smart move.
One of the Stamford people is a criminal?
Hey, Jan, speaking of Stamford,
Hannah brought in her baby.
Jan, which one of the new employees
is a criminal?
A reformed convict, and I'm not sure
so hang on, let me e-mail our H.R.
Stay on the line.
Who is it?
Hannah?
Andy?
ANGELA: Andy?
Martin?
Oh, you are such a racist.
Wait, why am I a racist?
Because you think he's black.
He is black, right, and...
He was the last one...
Stop it, stop it right...
Just stop it right now!
Okay, it's someone named Martin Nash.
Yeah!
Michael?
Why did the convict have to be a black guy?
It is such a stereotype.
I just wish that Josh had made
a more progressive choice,
like a white guy
who went to prison
for polluting a black guy's lake.
I wonder what he did.
In our society a black man can be arrested
for almost anything.
He was probably at a sporting event
and saw some people pushing each other
and he intervened.
Why would anyone go to jail for that?
So what we need to do is to forget
about this whole Martin-in-prison thing.
People will draw unfair conclusions
about Martin andlor black people.
Cool.
Okay.
Angela?
Sure.
Let's protect the convicts
at the expense of the general feeling
of safety in the workplace.
As a 90-pound female that sits in an ill-lit,
rarely-visited corner of the office,
naturally, I agree with that.
Good.
All right.
(PHONE RINGING)
Jim Halpert.
I am so horny.
Okay, I can't help you with that.
Oh, I think you can, Big Tuna.
Tell me about that Indian chick, Kelly.
She seems pretty slutty,
good for a romp in the sack.
She is dating Ryan, I think.
Oh, and I care, why?
She's high-maintenance.
Next. How about...
(WHISPERS) Angela?
Blondes are more fun.
Come on, trust me on that.
Yeah, trust me.
That would be fun for no one.
Okay, fine.
Okay.
Pam, the receptionist.
Pam, should I go for it?
Absolutely, you should.
Jackpot.
Just try to be cool.
I am cool.
Okay. Are you cool, really?
I'm cool. I'm cool. I'm so cool.
Tell me what is going on.
(SIGHS)
Martin from Stamford
was at one time in prison.
No! Be cool, be cool!
I am greatly concerned
about having a convict in the office.
And I do not care if that convict is white,
black, Asian, German
or some kind of halfsy.
I do not like criminals.
(WHISTLING)
Oh, God!
All righty, let's get started.
What is she into?
I know Pam pretty well.
I know the things that she likes,
and just as important,
I know the things that she hates.
So one of the things that she likes
is pranks and the things that she hates...
Frisbee-based competitions.
Are you kidding?
She...
I started the main Frisbee Golf Club
at Cornell where I went to college.
I live to frolf.
Lead off with that.
Okay...
She loves hunting.
She also loves those ads for Six Flags
with the old guy.
(SINGING)
Got it.
Also, do you speak pig Latin?
Hey, Martin. How's it going?
Good.
Getting settled.
Ah, good, good. Good.
Just a second.
Hey, everybody,
may I have your attention, please?
I realize that a lot of you
have already heard that Martin, here,
has had some trouble with the law.
But I just want to declare publicly
that I trust him completely
and that anybody who doesn't
is an ignorant, dumb person, okay?
As a matter of fact, you show me
a white man you trust
and I will show you a black man
that I trust even more.
Pam, tell me a white person you trust.
My dad.
Danny Glover.
Yeah.
Jonas Salk.
Who?
Justin Timberlake?
Oh, please. Colin Powell.
Hey, I've got one.
Yeah.
Jesus.
Apollo Creed.
Close your eyes. Picture a convict.
What's he wearing?
Nothing special.
Baseball cap on backward, baggy pants.
He says something ordinary like,
"Yo, that's shizzle."
Okay, now slowly open your eyes again.
Who are you picturing? A black man?
Wrong. That was a white woman.
Surprised? Well, shame on you.
So, you all wanna know
what I was in for?
No, that's not cool.
You don't have to tell them.
I really don't mind.
It was stupid mistake.
I was working in finance
and I got involved in some insider trading.
So, I spent a little time in the clink.
That is awesome.
I had Martin explain to me three times
what he got arrested for because
it sounds an awful lot like
what I do here every day.
What was prison like?
Not terrible. Boring.
We do the same thing every day.
But at least we get outdoors time.
You got outdoors time?
Two hours, every day.
Sometimes we'd play
pick-up football games...
Michael, why don't we get outdoors time?
Yeah, some days I never go outside.
Well, we are running a business.
What was your cell like?
Not good.
It's a little bit bigger than Michael's office,
but, you know, I really only slept there,
you know?
During the day our time's our own.
They had classes.
I took some watercolor classes.
They have art classes?
Yeah.
Did they have business classes there?
They did, taught by some
Harvard Business School guys.
A lot of the guys also that were in the class,
the inmates, a lot of them have gone on
to do extraordinary things in business.
Terrible things...
It kinda sounds like prison's better
than Dunder Mifflin.
Well, that's not true.
I would so rather be in prison.
PAM: Yeah.
RYAN: Prison sounds great.
No, you would not.
This place is not prison. This place...
It's way better than prison.
Baby. Hello, baby.
Here, you want to play with this?
You can't give paper clips to a baby.
He could swallow them.
It's okay. I've got tons of them.
You like that?
(BABBLING)
Pam-a-lama-ding-dong.
Listen, you're cute.
There is no getting around it.
So, I don't know if you like country music,
but I was thinking maybe one of these days
we could drive out to a field,
crank up some tunes,
smoke a few Macanudos,
maybe even toss a disc around.
(SPEAKING PIG LATIN)
Ut-way ooh-day ooh-yay ink-thay, am-Pay?
Wow. I...
Shh.
Think about it.
I'll hit you back.
Wow. That was... Wow.
Okay! Listen up, everybody!
You guys said that prison was better
than this place.
And I heard you loud and clear.
So, I am instituting some changes
to make this more like prison.
We are going to start
with an hour of outdoor time. So let's go!
Michael, it's freezing out.
I can't feel my toes.
Why don't we pump some iron?
Anybody wanna pump up?
What is that, like,
five pounds?
It's two-and-a-half.
I'm not going for bulk, I'm going for tone.
I'm going back inside.
Yeah, it is freaking cold
out here.
Anybody wants to stay out,
you've got about 27 minutes of rec time.
Oh, hey, man.
Hey.
Did you have TV in the joint?
Yeah, in the rec room.
Like a 10-inch black and white?
Actually, our TV was bigger than that one.
(SNIGGERING)
MICHAEL: These people don't realize
how lucky they are.
This office is the American dream
and they would rather be in the hole.
Oh, Andy.
I thought of one last tack
you could take with Pam.
Yeah? What?
Quick question. Do you play the guitar?
I play the banjo.
Hold on, let me think about that.
Yes, that'll work.
But can you sing
in a sexy, high falsetto voice?
(SINGING)
You know I can, my man!
Yep, that's perfect.
Hey.
Maybe I'll get my banjo out of my car.
Perfect.
What is going on?
I'm messing with Andy.
I'm sending him to all the women
in the office with just terrible information
on how to get them to go out with him.
I love it. I want in.
Who's the target?
Oh, you know what? It was gonna be Pam...
Perfect.
But...
But what do I do?
Just give me an assignment.
Oh, you know what, though?
I feel like I
already sicced him on Pam.
We'll give her a break.
Let's think of someone else.
All right, everybody, there has been a lot
of name-calling against our office today,
corporate maligning, slurring,
much of it coming from one of you,
who claims that prison is better than here.
And none of us can say, "Boo," because
none of us have ever been to prison.
Well, there's somebody I'd like you to meet.
Somebody else who has been to prison,
who can tell you what it is really like.
I'm Prison Mike!
You know why they call me Prison Mike?
Do you really expect us to believe
you're somebody else?
Do you really expect me to not push you
up against the wall, biatch?
ALL: Whoa, whoa, whoa...
Hey, pass...
All right. Yay, yay, yay, yay.
That's just the way we talk in the clink.
Been a lot of fun talk about prison today,
but I am here to scare you straight.
I am here to scare you straight!
In prison you are somebody's bitch.
Oh, and you. You, my friend,
would be the belle of the ball.
Don't drop the soap. Don't drop the soap.
Michael, please.
Where did you learn all of this?
Internet.
So, not prison.
And prison. It's 50-50. Both.
Look, prison stinks, is what I'm saying.
It's not like you can go home
and recharge your batteries
and come back in the morning
and be with your friends,
having fun in the office.
What did you do, Prison Mike?
I stole and I robbed
and I kidnapped the President's son
and held him for ransom.
That is quite the rap sheet, Prison Mike.
And I never got caught, neither.
Well, you were in prison, but...
Prison Mike,
what was the food like in prison?
Gruel sandwiches. Gruel omelets.
Nothing but gruel.
Plus, you can eat your own hair.
Wow. Prison sounds horrible.
Yeah, yeah. Well, thank you, Andy. Thanks.
Prison Mike,
what's the very, very worst thing
about prison?
(SOFTLY) Don't encourage him, Dwight.
(SCREAMING) The worst thing about prison
was the Dementors.
They were flying all over the place
and they were scary
and then they'd come down and they'd suck
the soul out of your body and it hurt!
Dementors like in Harry Potter?
No, not Harry Potter.
There are no movies in prison.
This is my point.
You guys got it soft and cushy.
This place is freaking awesome!
The people are awesome.
Your boss is nice.
Everybody seems to get along.
People are tolerant.
People who would jump to conclusions
can redeem themselves.
Nobody is nobody's bitch.
I hope that this scared you,
and from me, Prison Mike to you,
I just wanna thank you for listening to me
and letting me be a part of your life today.
'Cause you got a good life!
You got a good life, a good life.
So what do you think?
It doesn't sound so great, does it?
Wow. Thank you.
That must have been hard for you
to relive that. Both of you.
Yeah, that wasn't really at all my experience.
There's certain elements
of what you performed
I've seen on television,
but it didn't remind me of my time in prison.
Okay. Okay, fine.
You guys think prison is so great. All right.
Well, here you go.
KEVIN: Okay, Michael,
come on, let us out.
No! If you think prison is so wonderful,
then enjoy prison.
Are we gonna...
They are such babies.
I am going to leave them in there
until they can appreciate
what it's like to have freedom.
And if this doesn't bother them,
then I am out of ideas.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
KEVIN: Hey, let us out of here.
(HUMMING A LULLABY)
Hey! I have...
Shh.
(PHONE RINGING)
This is Toby.
Hey, Pam.
Where're you calling from?
Michael, why is everyone locked
in the conference room?
They were very disrespectful to me
and to the office
and Martin has had a bad influence.
To think that I gave him
the benefit of the doubt. It's...
Well, you're gonna have to let them out,
or I will, okay?
You know what, Toby?
I am teaching them a lesson, so...
You know they're teasing you.
I mean, obviously this is a much nicer place
than an actual prison.
We get paid to be here.
We go home afterwards
and have social lives.
And we have parties here.
They're teasing you to be funny.
Okay, nutcases, get out of there.
Good work. Long day. Really long.
Why don't you guys head home early.
Time off for good behavior!
Good job. Enjoy your freedoms.
Martin went from being a new guy
from Stamford
to the convict, to my friend,
back to a convict,
then to kind of a nuisance, actually,
if we could be completely honest,
and finally, to a quitter.
And I will not miss him.
And that is not because he is black.
(SINGING IN FALSETTO) So we've been told
and some choose to believe it
But I know they're wrong
wait and see
'Cause one day we'll find it
The ainbow-ray anection-cay
The lovers, the dreamers and me!