W.B. Jones is renovating
their offices,
And their construction crews
are taking up
Some of the parking spaces
we used to get.
So we had to park At a
satellite parking lot over there.
Which just means we get
to see more Of our lovely street.
Tell them what we saw today,
jim.
Oh, today we saw
a junkyard dog
Attacking the bones
of a rotisserie chicken.
Nature.
I've been here nine years,
and now all of a sudden I'm
supposed to park half a mile away.
I lost a penny
out of my loafers, oscar.
I will quit.
As god is my witness,
i will quit If this is not fixed.
Some of us like the walk
more than others.
hurts like hell.
www.1000fr.com presents
Capture:FRM@ÓÅÑÅµÄ±ù
Sync:FRS@¹âÏË
Resync:
nadielostzilla.
the office S04 ep10
did you pick a new chair?
It's been a while.
Pam, when i first opened
this catalog,
I thought i was just going
to be picking out a chair.
But instead you found something
to distract you
from ever picking out a chair.
Michael started the process of selecting
a new chair About three weeks ago.
And normally i wouldn't care,
But he promised me his old one.
It's way better.
It's one of these:
I really want it.
Have you ever seen
this woman?
Her?
The one in the really great
mesh, black, Hi-back swivel chair?
Look at her smile.
it's eyes.
look at her eyes.
She's got--
i don't know what it is exactly.
She dresses like
a professional,
And yet you know there is a side of
her That could just curl up on a couch.
Or in a great chair.
Uh, yeah, maybe, but...
Remember after my dinner party
When i said that
i was swearing off women?
I definitely remember
your dinner party.
i think what i meant Was that i am
completely swearing off one woman:
Jan.
I think that fate
put this catalog in my hands.
Actually, i put the catalog
in your hand
'Cause you have
to pick out a new chair.
What is it like being single?
I...like it.
I like starting each day
With a sense of possibility.
And i'm optimistic
Because every day
i get a little more desperate.
And desperate situations
yield the quickest results.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Would you please open your supply
catalogs And kindly turn to page 85?
yo,
Is this his new chair?
No, he hasn't picked one yet.
When pam gets michael's old chair,
I get pam's old chair.
Then i'll have two chairs.
Only one to go.
I am ready to start dating
again.
getting back on the market.
So fyi for those of you
Who were thinking about fixing me up
with any of your friends,
Use the woman on page 85
as a template.
That will be all.
I left my cell phone
in my car.
Call us when you get there
So we know you're okay.
Listen, man,
I am completely over jan.
So...would you set me up?
If i had somebody
to set you up with, michael,
Then i'd take her
for myself.
- I thought you were engaged.
- Nope.
stacy broke up with me.
What?
God, that's terrible, man.
Augh, she's crazy.
Um, are you still on good terms
With any of her friends?
Not anymore.
It's a bigger situation.
Yeah--ugh!
She's--
you don't deserve her.
all right.
Oh, hello, oscar meyer
weiner lover.
I bet that you have A bunch of
very liberal girl-type friends
Who trust you implicitly
Because they know
you'd never touch 'em
Because of your condition.
- michael.
- What?
- I have a friend who's single.
- oh.
Sandy.
She's gorgeous and she's got
a feisty personality too.
Hmm, feisty.
So she's not jolly or sassy?
Not like a jolly,
sassy opera singer?
No, she's a professional
softball player.
catcher or infield?
I don't know,
michael.
Is she a dress-wearer
Or a pants-wearer?
Could we share a rowboat?
Could a rowboat support her?
What are you asking?
I think i'm being very clear
what i'm asking.
Would an average-sized rowboat
support her Without capsizing?
It bothers me that you're
not answering the question.
No, all right?
No, she can't fit in a rowboat.
Damn it! i knew it!
I knew it, phyllis. okay.
What is wrong
with these people?
I would do anything for them,
And they're just hanging me out to dry.
Dating shouldn't be hard
for somebody like me
But it is,
and you know why?
Because nobody here
is willing to help me.
nothing would ever get done
In this office
without a formal request, would it?
Well fine, here goes.
- i don't think that this is--
- now okay,
I know that this
is probably not appropriate.
But i need help.
Because i want to play ball
with my kids Before i get too old.
and before that happens,
I need to get laid.
And before that happens,
i need to be in love.
and i don't want to hear
"i don't know, i can't help, na na na."
No, no, i am a catch,
And i am not going to be
the one who got away.
So this is what
we're going to do.
Dwight is going to hand out
index cards,
And i want you all to write
down the name Of an eligible woman
for me to date
By the end of the day.
No, by the end of the hour,
Or you are fired.
Write legibly, people.
Because of the construction
at W.B. Jones,
Half of us have to park
in the satellite lot.
it's, like,
a 10 minute walk.
No, 30.
Well, look, i have an assigned
parking place in front, So...
all right, all right,
all right.
Um, let me try to think about
what it would be like To not have one.
Okay, yes.
that would be bad.
Yes. yes.
Okay, so...
- help us out.
- Wish i could, but i can't.
well can,
But won't.
Should, maybe, but shorn't.
Michael, please--
What part of shorn't
don't you understand, kevin?
Look, i could probably
handle it, yes.
But i think it would be a good exercise
For you guys to do it yourselves.
- We won't let you down.
- Oh, you can't because i don't care.
listen, don't forget
to fill out those cards.
My love cards.
There's nobody i hate enough
To write her name on this card.
Well, i'm setting michael up
with my fat friend anyway.
He can just deal with it.
- Who are you putting down?
- Oh, you don't know her.
- Who is it?
- Your mom.
Yeah, whatever.
Give that to me!
give that to--
"Hot and juicy redhead."
Let's give this a try.
wendy's.
Hello, wendy.
This is kevin's friend
michael.
this isn't wendy.
Oh, i'm sorry.
could you put her on, please?
dude, this is a wendy's
restaurant.
??God, kevin. Okay, um...
Could i just have a frosty
and a baked potato, please?
you have to come to
the restaurant to order food.
Well, i'll send somebody
to pick it up. Just have it ready.
it's ready now.
Well, put it aside.
All right, um...
Okay, i collected the rest
of the ladies.
Good, good,
Because this batch was awful.
This one says "chair model."
I wrote that.
Michael, you shouldn't have
to settle.
This is my pledge to you.
I will find her,
And i will bring her
to you.
And as god is my witness,
She shall bear your fruit.
That sounds good.
Go get her.
W--w--wait, wait.
First go to wendy's, get my food,
Come back, and then go.
That is fantastic. thank you.
Thank you very much.
This is just what i needed.
The furniture company gave me
the name Of the advertising agency.
They gave me the name
of the photographer.
The photographer, a spaniard,
Used a wilkes-barre modeling agency.
The agency gave me
the following information:
Deborah shoshlefski,
142 south windsor lane.
Dead, car accident.
Case closed.
She's dead?
- She's so young.
- she was so young
And now she is dead.
As dead as every dead animal
who has ever died.
God.
why don't you
sit down, michael?
come on.
There we go.
Michael, you didn't even
know her.
Try not to be so hurtful,
jim.
- jim, how dare you?
- not at time like this.
okay, michael,
You know what?
I might have someone
for you.
Oh, really?
what's her name?
- Burger king?
- no, i mean it.
She's really nice
and sweet and...
You guys might actually
get along.
I don't--
i don't think i'm ready.
Is she hot?
I'm setting michael up
with my landlady.
She's really sweet and...
Whatever, i just can't take
michael like this.
No question about it.
I am ready to get hurt again.
We need to assemble
the five families.
No, not the five families.
We have to!
The five families are the five
companies Of scranton business park.
The bosses rarely meet.
There's michael scott,
Regional manager, dunder mifflin.
Bob vance,
vance refrigeration.
Paul faust
of disasterkits limited.
They call him cool guy paul.
W.b. jones
of w.b. jones heating and air.
Grade a badass.
And bill cress
of cress tool and die.
Bill cress is super old
and really mean.
Kevin, i don't have time
for this right now.
I'm trying to get a date
with pam's hot friend.
And she needs to meet me
right now.
I'm calling the meeting
anyway.
Thank you very much.
Our suspect
has straight brown hair.
She is wearing blue jeans
and a black top.
So...
behold our bachelorette.
give her a 10
for looks
And a 3 for her ability
to describe herself.
Hello, m'lady.
Michael?
Are you michael scott?
Is who a michael what?
Oh, i'm sorry.
I'm supposed to be meeting
someone named michael.
Oh, that's not--
yeah, i'm not--
michael?
Michael.
large hot chocolate with caramel
and a shot of peppermint.
So you...
get the rent checks
every month...
And...
What happens next? What--
You're asking me what i...
Do with the checks
that people write to me?
Just making conversation?
Why is it so hard
to meet people?
I--you know, it's, uh...
All i want Is somebody nice,
and sweet,
And someone i can talk to
And share an experience with, You know?
Why is it so hard
for people like us?
I don't know.
You want to see
what i walked out on?
This is going to blow
your mind. Look at that.
- She's beautiful.
- yeah.
Yeah. And you can't
see her whole body.
Down here,
she has a boob job.
Just--
she was just crazy smart
And really manipulative.
And i don't know.
michael? Hello. Michael.
Well, i'm gonna head out.
Okay.
Well, um, i enjoyed
this conversation.
It was very nice.
It was like talking to
the sweet, old lady On the bus.
That's incredibly rude.
Now you ruined it.
Where's scott?
michael scott Could not make it today
Due to an unforeseen prior engagement.
Let's just meet back
in an hour.
Gentlemen, please.
We called this meeting.
Andrew bernard
is the name of me.
And this is my associate,
mr. Kevin malone.
I have things.
All right,
what do you want?
Well, first of all,
i'd just like to say
What an honor it is to be sitting
here With you gentlemen.
- you have about ten seconds--
- We want our parking spaces back.
Whose parking spaces?
W.b. jones's construction guys Park
in our parking spaces Every morning.
And some people
have to park really far away
And walk all the way
to the office.
And some people
sweat too much for comfort.
By god.
I don't have time
for this, guys.
Just give them back
their spaces.
Okay.
We good? Okay.
Could've done this
over email.
After stacey left,
things...
Did not go well
for a while.
And it was hard to see...
It's just nice to win one.
Margaret the landlady?
Really, pam?
is that what you think of me?
She's sweet and cute.
I thought you would get along.
Oh, okay.
Well, i'm looking
for a passionate affair.
Not companionship.
I'm a man of intensity.
Of--of cool, and youth,
And--and passionately.
God, just...
- Margaret?
- i know.
You just got yourself
kicked out of your apartment.
Oh, i don't care. I don't really
like that place that much anyway.
I'll just move.
oh, really?
Who's gonna take you in?
You're messy.
you're a klutz.
You spill everything.
And you leave the volume
on the tv Way too loud.
Yeah. Maybe i'll just
move in with my boyfriend
'Cause he's kind
of a slob too.
Okay. Sure.
let's do it.
No, i, um, well,
i'm not gonna--i'm--
I'm not gonna move in
with anyone unless i'm engaged.
Have i not proposed
to you yet?
i don't...no.
no.
Well, that's comi n'.
Oh, right now?
No. I'm not gonna do it
right here.
That would be rather lame.
Okay.
so then when?
Pam, i'm not gonna tell you.
I hate to break it to you,
But that's not how that works.
Oh, right. Yeah.
Wait, i'm serious.
- It's happening.
- okay.
And when it happens, It's
going to kick your ass, beesly.
So...
Stay sharp.
I've been warned.
I am not kidding.
Got it a week
after we started dating.
I don't know, man.
I was with jan
for so long.
I was excited
about meeting somebody new.
Put my heart out there.
You know what you need?
Closure.
You're right.
What do you mean though?
There was a woman in your life
Who affected you very deeply,
And she left
before you could say good-bye.
I think you need
to say good-bye.
Come on.
i'll drive.
- We did it!
- i did it.
We got our spaces back.
Nice job.
- Nice.
- yeah, there it is.
You're welcome.
Did i do this for me? No.
I did this
for the little guy.
For joe six-pack.
The guy who wakes up every morning
In his $400 a month apartment,
Wonders how he's gonna pay
his mortgage that month.
Wonders how he's gonna fill
his car up with oil.
Wonders how am i going to pay
my kids' orphanage bills?
That guy...
Shouldn't have to wonder
where he's gonna park.
How did she die?
I guess you could say she died Of...
blunt force trauma and blood loss.
She got in a car accident
And ploughed into the side
of an airplane hangar.
- God.
- yeah.
She was so innocent.
She was stoned,
apparently.
You know,
i used to think That
i had this perfect person
out there waiting for me.
But now i know that that's
just silly.
Because she's dead.
What do you do?
You wait till next year's
chair catalogue comes out
And find someone
who's still alive.
- We move on.
- yeah.
Where do you want to go
for dinner?
I don't know. I kinda hate all
our regular places right now.
you know what,
that one...
Hey, pam.
Will you wait for me
one second While i tie my shoe?
- I hate you.
- what?
My shoe is untied.
what is your problem?
Oh, my god.
you thought i--
- No, no, no.
- how could i have thought that?
How could i
have thought that?
* bye-bye *
* ms. Chair model lady *
* i dreamt that we were married *
* and you treated me nice *
* we had lots of kids *
* drinkin' whiskey and rye *
* but why'd you have to *
* go off and die? *
* why'd you have to *
* oh, you believe in rock and roll? *
* can music save your mortal soul? *
* and can you have to dance *
* real slow? *
* well, i know that *
* you're in love with him *
* 'cause i saw you *
* dancin' in the gym *
* kicked off both her shoes *
* turned off her shoes *
* no more rhythm and blues! *
* no verdict was returned! *
* rhythm and blues *
* this'll be the day that i die *