Ready?
Come on, show me excited!
- Yes!
-Yeah, I'm pretty excited too.
Today I'm heading over to the job fair
at Valley View High School,
to find some new interns.
Want to get some fresh blood.
Euthanize this place.
Hey, are we doing this thing?
- Yeah.
Oh my God, Darryl,
you look like Barack Obama.
Everybody,
I'm dating Barack Obama!
- Why are you dressed like that?
- Like what?
Like you're applying for a loan.
Maybe he's going to church.
Or court.
Figured I look presentable.
You... went a different way.
I think you look nice.
- Thank you.
Here's what we're going to do:
I'm going to instruct the kids
about management and sales.
Oscar will be in charge of accounting.
Pam will be eye candy.
No... uh, also,
because that is your alma mater.
Darryl will hire some kids
for the warehouse.
We don't have to worry
about internships with them,
because they definitely
ain't going to college.
What college did you go to, Mike?
Let's go!
Subtitles by Aimee
www.tusseries.com
Resync:
nadielostzilla.
4x13 'Job Fair'
Today, I am meeting a
potential client on the golf course,
because Ryan put me on probation.
You remember Ryan,
he was the temp here.
Yeah. And it is not a good time
for me to lose my job,
since I have some...
pretty big long term plans
in my personal life with Pam,
that I'd like her parents
to be psyched about.
So I am about to do something
very bold at this job
that I've never done before:
Try.
Mister Maguire,
it's been a couple of years.
Jim, how are you?
Nice to see you, man.
My grandfather would be
spinning in his urn
if he knew that I was out here
with a Dartmouth boy.
You take that shirt off right now
or I will take it off for you, sir.
I am totally and completely kidding!
- Andy Bernard, Cornell, 95.
- McGuire, Darmuth, 74.
- Got some blisties.
- Yeah, you do.
Hit about 1,200 balls last night
in preparation for today,
so hands are a little tender.
It's actually not funny at all.
It's incredibly painful.
Let's make it interesting.
Say, ten bucks a hole?
Okay. What are we talking?
Skins? Acey Deucy?
Bingo bango bongo?
Sandies, Barkies? Arnies?
Wolf? What?
I'm gonna take this petty cash
that I got from Oscar,
and turn it into next month's rent.
So many memories in this old gym.
Pretending I have PMS so
I didn't have to play volleyball,
pretending I have PMS so
I didn't have to play basketball.
Those were the days!
A little over the top,
don't you think?
Show them
what you brought, Mike.
- That's all we brought.
- This is all we need.
- We'll see.
- Yes we will see, Oscar.
We will see,
because a blank sheet of paper
equals endless possibilities.
Conceptual.
All right!
We are open for business!
Hello!
- Andy, you're up, let's go!
- Giddy up, let's do this.
People assume I'm great at golf.
But like everybody,
I hated golf lessons
when I was a kid. So,
I used to hang out
at the sailing club instead.
Got my "knot" on.
Dammit!
Guys, do we have to stay all day?
I mean, Michael's gone,
can't we just go?
Yeah, and I finished my work
months ago!
Excuse me, people.
It has come to my attention,
some of you have forgotten...
who is in charge here.
When Michael is gone...
Jim is in charge.
When Jim is gone,
Andy and I are in charge.
When Andy is gone
you answer to me. Okay?
Excuse me, where do you think
you're going?
You're not leaving.
No! Stanley,
do not walk out that door!
If you walk out that door,
so help me, I will...
He left.
Last time I checked,
the American workday
ends at 5 PM.
You will all stay at your desks
until that time.
Or you will suffer
the consequences.
What consequences?
I will tell on you.
There's some filing,
restocking the supply shelves.
Replacing the water jug,
which nobody likes to do.
We...
eat a lot of cake!
Yeah, and you basically learn
how an office runs.
Hello. Hi.
Can I talk to you for a sec?
- Excuse me.
- This is Michael, my boss.
- Justin.
- Hey, remember what we talked about,
in the car on the way up,
"only the best and the brightest"?
He's nice and he seems interested.
He's totally wrong, Pam.
How you doing? Listen,
I don't think that a handsome,
funny, smart, funny-looking
kid like you,
should limit himself. You could do
whatever you want to do.
You could be a classy janitor,
or...
a cashier with dignity, or a...
migraine worker.
Maybe for you,
paper should be more of a hobby.
- Sorry for wasting your time.
- Oh, no problem.
And he signed!
He put his name on the piece of...
That was supposed to be
a blank canvas
on which to put
their hopes and dreams.
And he just made it
into a stupid piece of paper.
We need another one
immediately.
Yeah, the booth is lame without it.
- I only brought the one.
- Are you mental?
Michael, do you remember,
you specifically told me
to only bring one sheet of paper?
You said it only takes
one sheet to make a difference.
And I said, "Are you sure, Michael?"
And you said "Pam! Pam! Pam!"
And then you sneezed in my tea,
and then you said,
"Don't worry, it's just allergies."
- Do you remember that?
- I don't.
Okay. I'll go look for another one.
And that is why
I need a smart intern.
Hey, so how is
the direct mail business going?
I can't complain,
people love their junk mail.
Are you getting
all your paper from PPC or...?
You know what, Jim?
I'm not really looking
to change things up right now,
I just came out here to get out
of the office for a little bit,
so why don't we just play, okay?
- Absolutely, will do.
So I guess I'll just...
work on my short game.
Hello there.
What is this company?
Well, it's funny that you should ask,
because...
it's really more than a company...
- Dunder Mifflin paper.
- Thanks.
Dammit, Oscar!
Yeah, I'm trying to lure
these kids into my booth,
but kids are very wary
about being "lured" these days.
Thank you, Dateline!
Thank you.
- Extension 128.
- Hiya, Pumpkin, it's Creed.
Say, we're gonna ditch this bitch.
You in?
Are you out?
Pumpkin's out, let's go, gang!
My old art room.
Oh, maybe it's still here!
No, no. They must have
taken it down. Never mind.
- What do you want?
- Michael, I know you're swamped.
I just thought you should know that
everyone in the office has left,
except for Angela and I.
Do not worry though,
I have taken down their names,
and I have docked them a personal day.
Who cares? I'm not there, Jim's not
there, why should they have to be there?
So... what else is up?
Thank you!
What, what is this?
- A piece of paper.
- This isn't Dunder Mifflin paper.
Some sort of Pendleton crap.
Well I think they'll get
the spirit of it.
We're dying here.
I want you to go back to the office
and I want you to get the real stuff. I
want you to get ultra white card stock.
- Are you serious?
- Yes. And don't call me Shirley.
Dammit!
You know, you can just pick it up,
take the triple bogey.
Yeah, I'll get it out. Thank you.
Come on, Tuna!
Hey, can't really talk now,
what's up?
Just checking in, how's it going?
You know, we'll see, we'll see.
I just drove 20 miles round-trip
back to the office
to get Michael a
single sheet of white paper.
So, I could have just
had them fax it to me, I guess.
- I like you.
- Talk to you later?
Yeah. All right. Bye.
All right.
Sorry, I got to annoy you
one more time.
What if I bring down shipping costs?
You can try.
But I've looked at your prices.
Even with free shipping?
Doesn't work.
It's just- it's not in the stars, Jim.
Six.
All right, race to the next hole!
Winner gets ten bucks!
- Wait for me! Andy!
- Shortcut! Shortcut!
I fell in the sandtrap!
All of these jobs suck.
I would rather live jobless,
on a beach somewhere,
off the money
from a large inheritance...
than to have to work in any one
of these crap-holes.
They suck.
Game over.
- Just-in time.
- Hi.
Just-in case. What's your last name?
- Polznik.
- This just in. Justin Polznik!
Justin is the ugly girl in the movie,
who takes off her glasses
and she's hot!
And you realize she was always hot,
she was just wearing glasses.
And that you were the blind one.
He's the most
important thing in my life right now.
I want you to meet my family.
Come on.
Oscar Martinez. Accountant
extraordinaire. This is Justin.
This is Darryl Philbin.
Isn't he big?
And you already met her,
Pam Beesly, office hottie.
She will do you.
No, no. But she has already dated
two guys in the office that we know of,
so this could be number three,
you never know.
Come here.
I would never
say this to her face,
but she is a wonderful person
and a gifted artist.
Why wouldn't you
say that to her face?
What do you think?
Think these guys are nice?
The guys I didn't bring are even better.
Justin,
I'm willing to commit right now.
Would you do me the honor...
of spending the summer
with us, at Dunder Mifflin?
- I think you are very special.
- You didn't want me before.
- That's what you said.
- No, I didn't.
- You were kind of a jerk to me.
- You misconstrued me.
- And I'm, I'm gonna go now.
- Why don't...?
Bless you.
Thank you.
Okay, Jim, you owe me one-twenty,
and Phil, you owe me two-thirty.
Let's open a tab, because you and me
are gonna be playing more often.
- Count me in!
- No.
All right!
You had some fun,
and I think I paid for it.
So let me get my last shot in there.
Is there anything
you can do for me?
I'll tell you what.
My fiscal year ends in two months.
Let's talk then.
Sound good?
- Absolutely.
- Good playing with you guys.
You know? It's a tough thing,
seeing a grown man take six shots
to get out of a sand trap but, I had
to give Phil credit for not quitting.
Which is what I told him.
I also told him I don't quit either,
and I'd call him every single day
until he gave me his business.
Which he then did, after...
15 minutes of me blocking his car.
So I am now his paper supplier!
And I shot a 102 today,
so I'm feeling pretty good.
The job fair will be closing
in five minutes.
Eighth period will commence
as scheduled.
Hold down the fort,
I have to do something.
Excuse me.
If you can hear me, I'd like you to
look around at all these companies
and know that none of them
are good enough for you.
H and R Block? Come on,
I mean I don't even know what they do.
Frank Regan Funeral Home?
Too much formaldehyde!
The Air Force?
Air Force is cool.
The refreshments?
Bush league!
You know, that's not what you want.
Okay I see security is coming
so I just want to say,
come to Dunder Mifflin.
Dunder Mifflin, a great place to work!
Anybody? Show of hands, anybody
want to intern at Dunder Mifflin?
We do not offer college credit,
we cannot give you any sort of pay,
but it is a really
fun work environment.
Anybody? Show of hands?
Damn... it. Okay,
I'm gonna wrap it up here.
Thank you for your time,
and drive safe.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Beers?
You closed it?
- I closed it.
- Yes!
- Congratulations to you, sir.
- Thank you very much.
- Well done.
- Thank you.
You know what, screw this!
Today I did something stupid:
I questioned myself.
And I will never do that again.
Because I look at somebody
like Jim Halpert
and I think, that guy could do
anything he wants to do.
He could do anything,
and he chooses to work here,
selling paper.
Just like me.
Yeah, kiss her.
Kiss her good.
- Hi.
- Hello.
I was just wondering...
what kind of jobs do you guys have?
- Are you interested in graphic design?
Yeah.
-  Can I fill out an application?
- Oh absolutely, here, take a seat.
I should let you know right away,
this is just an entry-level job.
It's really basic.
We're looking for like, a self starter,
someone who can meet deadlines and...
pretty much just go
the extra mile, I guess.
- I can do that.
- Great. And uh,
obviously we're looking for someone
who knows Photoshop,
and Dreamweaver.
Corel Painter, Illustrator,
AfterEffects, all the basics.
I don't know any of those.
It's actually not super-complicated.
I'm sure there's some sort of like,
adult education classes in the area.
But if you're really serious
about graphic design,
one thing about
New York or Philadelphia,
they've got amazing programs
out there for design.
New York or Philadelphia.
All right. Cool, well, thanks.
- And I'll look into those.
- You should.
- New York or Philadelphia.
- Absolutely.
Thanks.