Did you know that in Morocco
it is common to
exchange a small gift
when meeting somebody
for the first time?
In Japan, you must
always commit suicide
to avoid embarrassment.
In Italy, you must
always wash your hands
after going to the bathroom.
This is considered
to be polite.
Why are you telling us this?
I am jetting off
on an international
business trip.
Where are you going?
To Canada.
Where is it?
Canada.
Okay.
My boss is
sending me abroad
to do a presentation to
an international client,
and I have always
been intrigued by
all things international,
the women, the pancakes,
the man of mystery.
Meredith,
I would like you to pretend
that you are from Abu Dhabi.
Hello.
I am ashamed
at your naked face.
I must cover it
with my jacket.
You are now sexy
in your culture.
(WHISTLING)
T-minus...
6.5 days.
(WHISPERING)
One more week.
Pam comes back from
New York next week,
and everyone here
has just been
so excited for me
and involved
and intrusive and weird.
One more week.
(CHUCKLES)
DAVID ON PHONE:
Do you have your passport?
I have my passport.
Got your per diem?
I have my per diem.
I already know
what I am going
to spend this on.
I'm going to buy a sweater.
Michael,
that's for your food.
Well, I'll just...
I'll use different
money for that.
I was happy to send
Michael on this trip.
He's been feeling
pretty down since we
had to transfer Holly
up to New Hampshire, and...
But this little perk
really seemed
to turn him around,
and it's pretty tough
to find somebody
who wants to go up
to Winnipeg mid-November.
And business-class air,
like a five-star hotel
in the sky.
Nothing but the best.
Actually better
than a five-star hotel
'cause you get a big,
cushy seat
and you sit in
a row of people
and to eat whatever
the mind can imagine.
I think I am going to have
a fillet with mushroom sauce.
Well, I'm just glad
you're happy
because, you know,
I felt bad.
Well, that is all in the past.
And in terms of nightlife,
when you get there,
just ask the concierge.
They have one of those?
Let's do this!
Wait, why do you
need three suitcases?
Two are empty.
For souvenirs.
You have your money belt?
I do.
It is right here.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
You wanna wear that puppy
right up on the breastbone
like a bra.
No, I don't wanna
wear a bra.
Here, let me help you.
Stop it! Stop it!
Do you want to get robbed
in a foreign country?
I wash my hands of this.
Okay, where's
my translator?
Ici, monsieur.
MICHAEL: There he is.
I'm just bidding
a bon voyage a la
mon petite fiancee.
Translation,
goodbye my petite fiancee.
Be good.
I will try.
Meaning what?
Meaning I will try to
get other dudes laid.
Yeah, baby.
That's what I'm
talking about.
That could be you
if you hadrt
forgotten French.
Where is my numbers man?
Here.
MICHAEL: There we go!
Our town car awaits.
It's just a van.
It's not just a van.
Look, I know
my way around a van.
That is just a van.
Dwight, can you
get those, please?
Welcome to Cribs,
the business-class
edition.
Check this out. Mimosa.
Sweet.
Handed it to me
as I sat down.
This was my hot towel.
It is still wet.
Michael G. Scott
rolling like a pimp.
Take a sip of that.
Mmm-hmm.
Is that good?
Mmm!
Don't drink all of it.
Give some to Oscar.
That's really good.
I'm good.
You want one of your own?
I can hook you up.
I'm sorry,
you'll need to
keep moving.
Yes, this is Beth.
This is my personal
valetlflight attendant,
and she will be
helping me this morning.
We need to keep
the aisle clear.
Yes. Get back.
Get back.
Oh. All right.
Come on.
Get back to the slums.
Here we go.
ANDY: Oh, boy.
(WHISPERING)
You guys, check it out.
My own personal
DVD player
and 20 movies.
(WHISPERING)
Andy brought one, too.
Harry and the Hendersons.
(SHUSHES)
Keep it down.
I made egg-salad sandwiches.
Do you want one?
Could you have
picked something stinkier
to bring on a plane?
(SCOFFS)
My God, Oscar, really.
Do you have a bag
of baby poop in there, too,
to share with everybody?
No, I'll be ordering
my own food.
Thank you very much. Hi.
STEWARDESS: Hi.
I'd like to see a menu,
please.
Oh, I'm sorry, there are
no meals on flights
less than two hours.
Okay.
Doesrt matter because I'm
going to take a nap.
I think I'm going to use
my complimentary blindfold.
I will don it and... Oh.
Look at that,
I can't see
because I am in...
(CRASHING)
God!
And what would
you like to drink?
Just checking out
where I'm gonna be
pretty soon
when Pam gets back.
It's gonna be
close quarters.
Gonna be a lot of tension.
For you. I'm with Darryl.
This looks like where
I'll probably do
my pushups every day.
Is that supposed
to impress me?
No, not gonna happen.
He has hurt me
too much and too often,
and I am in
a healthy relationship now,
so I'm not
going to flaunt it,
I'm not going to hurt him,
but that door is closed.
What are we doing?
This is so wrong!
Yeah.
This is nice.
Move in here.
Very sweet.
(EXCLAIMS IN DELIGHT)
I'll check us in.
MICHAEL: All right.
Very cool.
We are going to find out
where the action is,
my friend.
Okay.
Where's the concierge?
Yes, Wallace said
there would be
one of those.
Bingo.
Follow moi, bro-sieur.
Wow.
What about
a nice sushi place?
Maybe a place
with a view?
Oh. Matsuki.
It's a good one.
You may walk there
if you wish,
or you may take
the number 17 bus
until 9:00.
Other than that,
you can take the taxi,
and the number
is right there.
Wow. Wow,
I'm blown away
by this.
I...
This is great.
Thank you.
One final question.
Where might you find
yourself on a Winnipeg
night like tonight?
Oh. The Huntsman is good.
The Huntsman?
Down here,
the financial district.
A concierge is
the Winnipeg equivalent
of a geisha.
This is a woman
who has been
trained in the fine art
of fanciness and pleasure,
and when you meet one,
it is intoxicating.
Just what
the doctor ordered.
I can't believe this.
(SIGHS)
Are you sure?
PAM: I just talked
to my advisor. Failing.
Wow. I thought you
were good at Flash.
I was. And then they
switched to Acrobat
just as I was learning Quark.
I hate computers.
Okay, okay,
it's no big deal.
So you're not
a computer geek.
I have to stay and retake it.
Wow. Um...
Well, okay.
That means
another 12 weeks.
Can you do another
three months of this?
It's not...
It's not about me.
I mean, this is your dream.
And you went to
New York to do this.
So when you come back,
you come back
the right way, right?
Right.
You okay?
My cell battery's low,
so I have to let you go.
Okay. All right.
All right.
Love you. Bye.
Love you, too.
(SNIFFLES)
Guys. She's in there.
Engaging wings.
(IMITATING MECHANICAL NOISE)
I'm probably going to
leave after one drink.
Let's do this.
Yeah, with a hot slab
of Canadian bacon
in your hand.
Excuse me. Hello.
Concierge Marie.
Michael Scott.
Good to see you again.
Hello. Good to see you.
This is my associate
from Dunder Mifflin,
Oscar Martinez.
Nice to meet you.
Oscar.
Works in accounting.
This is Concierge Marie,
who works at our hotel.
You look,
how you say,
radiant tonight.
Thank you.
And it is, how you say,
a beautiful night.
Michael, why?
She's foreign. I...
For madame et monsieur.
Thank you.
You're very welcome.
Thank you, Andy.
Thank you.
Let me get
a picture of you guys.
MICHAEL: Everybody's
going to end up
dying some day,
and I think
it's better to die
with some people
that you like,
like Oscar and Andy
and Concierge Marie,
than to know that
there's somebody
out there
that you love
that you're not with.
All right,
I've scoped out
the joint.
Those two dudes
are as good as naked.
How do you even
know they're gay?
Come on, it's Dandy Dale
and Foppy McGee over there.
Mademoiselle, beer me deux
Long Island Iced Teas,
s'il vous plait.
Bad decision in a glass.
I don't care
if you're gay,
straight, engaged,
whatever,
a guy needs intercourse.
You will thank me
when they spank thee.
(WHISPERING)
Don't do this.
You guys like apples?
What?
Do you like apples?
Sorry, what?
How do you like
these apples?
All right,
on a scale of one to 10,
how hot is that dude?
Is he your boyfriend
or something?
No, but he could be yours
if you play your cards right.
Dude, leave us alone,
all right?
Gentlemen.
What are you doing?
Dude, you struck out.
They're totally stuck up.
Here. Drink up.
How about this one.
It's Christmas Eve...
Mmm-hmm.
...and everything is closed
and you need to get
some dry-cleaning done.
12:00, midnight,
where do you go?
What do you do?
Come on, what do you do?
Uh... Astro Cleaners
on St. James Place
is the only place
that is open
on that day.
Unbelievable. Unbelievable.
If you don't
mind me asking...
Anything.
You can ask me anything.
Okay.
I'm your wingman.
It's just that I've
sat next to Angela
for a very long,
very long time.
Right-oh.
How could anyone
stand that woman?
What?
What do you see in her?
What do you see in Angela?
What do I see in Angela?
I wanna know.
I see through a hard exterior
to a little jelly
in the middle.
She is teaching me
to be a better person.
She's working
really hard on that.
AND Y: And she has
the softest skin
I've ever seen,
and I can't wait to
have sex with her.
OSCAR: You haven't had sex?
No.
Are you guys waiting
to get married? Or...
Honestly, I don't know
what we're waiting for.
Andy, something is
wrong with that woman.
What is wrong with her?
I'd like to know.
You should call
her and ask her.
I'd like to know
what's wrong with her.
I should call
her and ask her.
What is wrong with her?
Do it. It's a...
Call her.
Oh, my God,
don't call her.
Don't call her, Andy.
Andy! Oh, my God!
It's too late.
It's dialing.
Now it's ringing.
(GIGGLING)
ANGELA: Hello? Hello?
What is wrong with you?
Why won't you do Andy?
What?
That's Oscar,
and he wants to know
why you won't do me,
and I think it's
a valid question.
Are you drunk?
This is Andy Bernard!
I know who this is.
I want to take
you to sex school.
What?
DWIGHT: (WHISPERING)
Who is that, monkey?
Is somebody there?
ANGELA: Are you drunk?
I have needs.
We'll discuss this later.
Naked!
What?
We'll discuss it later naked.
I wanna see you naked.
Do you want to
get some breakfast
or something?
MARIE: I'm so tired.
Okay.
How does
everyone know already?
Know what?
Pam failed art school.
Wow. Doesrt surprise me.
Excuse me?
Have you seen
her painting, Jim?
The building?
There are shadows coming
from two different directions.
PHYLLIS: Dwight, stop it.
What? Are there two suns?
STANLEY: My God.
PHYLLIS: Come on.
Last I checked,
that's not an office building
in the Andromeda Galaxy.
All right. I'm gonna
grab a cup of coffee.
It's totally unrealistic.
There are no lines
in the parking lot.
Oscar!
Hey.
That was fun last night.
Yeah, it was.
You know,
it's true what they say.
Long Island Iced Teas
are way stronger in Canada.
Hey, thanks for
trying to hook me up.
Are you kidding me?
That's what I do.
Get the whole nine nards.
I can't believe
we called her up.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Totally.
It's crazy.
Wait.
Who?
I'm talking about Angela.
I can't believe
we called her up
last night.
We called Angela?
You... You called her.
That was real?
I thought I dreamed that.
Oh, God. Oh, God!
All right.
Okay.
This is so bad.
Good morning, Michael.
Are you ready
for the meeting?
Slept like a baby.
This can't happen again.
This has to happen again.
Darryl can't
happen again.
Look at me.
Do you want me to
do more pushups?
Yeah.
Okay. You have to
break up with Darryl.
I already typed out
a text message for you.
All you have to do
is press send.
I don't know.
I mean, it's well-written
and all, I just...
Has to be done.
We'll press send
together.
(BEEPS)
Oh, my God,
he's gonna kill us.
I'd like to see him try.
(CELL PHONE BEEPS)
Oh.
He says it's cool.
He said it's cool!
That's all he wrote?
That's all he wrote.
Can I see it?
Mmm-hmm.
Didrt you two date for,
like, a long time?
Mmm-hmm.
This is like a fairytale.
(ALARM DEACTIVATES)
I'll be honest with you.
We've been talking
with Catalyst Paper.
Their prices are
better than yours.
Look, people continue
to come back to us
time and time again
because they feel
cared for here.
They feel respected,
and they feel that
their needs matter.
They are treated
like human beings.
MAN: Everything okay?
Yes.
Oh, man,
she is so pissed.
She's taking us
back to first base.
What's first base
with Angela?
I get to kiss
her forehead.
I had a good time
hanging out this weekend.
I had a good time, too.
Wingman for life. W-M-F-L.
Thank you.
You up for a chest bump?
No.
Bro hug?
Back to basics. I like it.
I had to go
all the way to Canada
to get to know
a guy who sits
20 feet away from me.
And he's delightful.
DAVID ON PHONE:
Hey, I just heard
you guys made the sale.
MICHAEL: Yeah, we locked
him up for two years.
Good. Very good!
See? I told you.
Sounds like somebody
had a good trip.
No, actually,
the trip sucked.
Excuse me?
The trip sucked, David.
It blew chunks.
It was terrible.
It was a bad trip.
I did not like the trip.
What are you talking about?
Well, starting with
the airport shuttle,
which was
basically just a van,
and business class...
Okay.
...which was
basically just coach,
and the hotel,
which sucked big time.
The hotel. What...
It was not...
It sucked.
Okay.
I'm sorry to hear
the hotel was bad.
The Crestmore...
And thanks for
the tip on the concierge.
That was great.
That was a...
Okay.
...that was
a really good choice.
Hey, hey, hey. Michael.
Please listen for a second.
No, David, you listen to me.
Why'd you send her away?
That...
God. You knew I liked her
and you just sent
her away, and that...
That was a sucky
thing to do, man.
Michael.
That was a really
sucky thing to do.
Sometimes... Sometimes...
MICHAEL: Why have I stayed
at Dunder Mifflin for so long?
Certainly not
because of the paycheck
'cause I could be
making more money
as a doctor
or a professional athlete.
I think it's
because they respect me.
A boss that will not fire you
even though you
just tell him off
right to his face
over the phone,
that's respect.
You did it, man.
Day one.
Congrats.
Thanks, man.
I'm coming back
the wrong way.
It's not because of you.
I don't like graphic design.
That's it.
Stop smiling.
I really didn't like it.
It's just designing
logos and stuff,
and I miss Scranton,
but it is not
because I missed you.
I just really
wanted to come home.
And I know you said
to come home the right way,
but you can't tell me
what to do. Got it?
I missed you.
I missed you, too.
You're back.
Yeah.
Good.
I need you to make
five copies of these.
I'm not going inside.
All right. First thing
in the morning, then.
Welcome back.
We're back
together again, baby.
We're back.
They tried
to keep us apart,
but they couldn't.
It was like destiny.
I realized that,
for whatever reason,
I just couldn't do
better than Kelly.
Aw!
Yeah.