Are you
swallowing them whole?
You're eating them so fast,
are they even
touching your tongue?
Yes.
Why aren't you
having any, Angela?
Oh, I ate so many already
when no one was looking.
(LAUGHING)
Yeah, right.
My baby's dieting.
She wants to fit into
a special child-size
wedding gown for our big day.
Why do those exist?
It's from
my pageant days.
I was
Miss Tiny Mid-Atlantic Bride
when I was 10.
Probably heard of it.
Brownies, is it?
Pastry cubes
made of sugar and fat?
No, thank you.
I'll stick with my jerky.
So why'd you
come in here?
To socialize.
And inform.
Brownies!
I'm taking two,
so I can parcel them up
and eat them
at my leisure later on.
Much healthier.
You taking two?
Yeah, but one of them
is for Toby.
Yeah. Why don't you
send that to him
in Costa Rica?
I'm just gonna hand
it to him right now.
Okay, weirdo.
Why's that?
Why's that weird?
She said she was going to
give it to him right now.
She's probably going to
because they
sit next to each other.
Yeah, they used to.
Toby works here again.
Oh, can you imagine?
Oh, no.
You don't know.
I don't know. What?
You should probably
just meander back there,
take a look,
see if he's back.
Dare I?
(LAUGHS)
You know what?
I'm going to,
for old time's sake.
Great practical joke, Jim.
Got me to go to the annex.
Hi, Michael.
(SCREAMING) No! God!
No, God, please, no!
No! No!
No!
I blame the two of you.
This is your fault.
Michael, Dwight and I
were talking about this,
and we both don't understand
how you didn't realize
Toby was back.
I'm concerned
you may have brain damage.
You cannot expect me
to keep track
of all of my personnel.
There are a lot of people
here and a lot of different
shapes and sizes.
And there is nothing that
is even vaguely interesting
about the way that he looks.
So, I'm off the hook.
Maybe you cleaned your ears
too vigorously with Q-tips.
I know where this is going.
You hurt the temporal lobe...
I'm not going to stop
putting Q-tips
in my ears.
I don't care
how much it hurts!
Maybe I just block Toby
from my mind.
Oh, interesting.
Continue.
Like someone
who's molested.
Doesrt remember it
for years.
Toxic Shock Syndrome.
Maybe it's
Stockholm Syndrome.
China syndrome.
Could be any one of them.
It's a messed up world.
It is a messed up world.
But it's our messed up world.
Oh, come on!
Do you see this?
Disgusting.
MICHAEL: Look at him.
With his stupid face.
Stupid tan.
Yeah.
He looks great.
Well-rested.
No. He looks worse.
(PHONE RINGING)
Yeah.
WOMAN: David Wallace
is on the line for you.
Thank God. David, hello.
We need your help.
DAVID: Michael,
is everyone okay?
Oh, well,
I'm afraid not.
Toby Flenderson
of HR has made
a sudden reappearance.
I don't understand.
Is anyone hurt?
Not on the surface, no.
But I can tell
people are disturbed, David.
Michael, you texted me,
"911, call me."
Yes.
All in caps.
Do you know
what "911" means?
I learned a while back
that if I don't text "911,"
people will not
return my calls.
But now people
always return my calls,
because they think
that something horrible
has happened.
DAVID: Toby was hired back
because
he knows the branch,
he was available,
and I like him. Okay?
And that's that.
With all due respect, David,
this hardly seems
like a dialog.
That's because
it isn't, Michael.
Now, what I'm curious
about is how you were able
to go an entire week
without knowing
a member of your staff
was there.
I did not want to
go back to the annex
because that is where
Holly worked,
whom I loved.
Also, it's icky back there.
That's true.
People say it's icky.
Okay. I have to go.
David, wait.
No.
Is there no way
we can get rid of him?
Not without cause, Michael.
I have cause.
It is because I hate him.
You have to get
along with Toby.
No.
Yep.
I don't.
Goodbye, Michael.
Don't do that.
So, Tunes,
you still going to buy
your old mars place?
Yeah, I am. Wait.
How do you know that?
I didn't tell you that.
No, I was just
walking by your desk.
I saw some e-mails.
I got peepers
of an eagle.
That's really not cool.
So, Jim,
you're going to live
in the same house
that you used to
pee the bed in?
Yeah. I guess,
technically, Kev,
you're right.
Today's a big day.
Today's the day
that I show Pam
the house
that I bought for us.
Without telling her.
But it's my parents' house,
the house I grew up in.
And, yeah, I bought
it kind of impulsively.
I mean, the price was good,
and I was helping out my mom.
It's got shag carpets.
I mean,
you can't blame my parents.
It was the '70s.
And why would you want to buy
ugly wood from trees
when you can have paneling
and a painting
of some creepy clowns
that is apparently crucial
to the structural integrity
of the building?
She's gonna love it.
Right?
Could you guys
all do me a favor
and just not talk about
this until I tell Pam?
That'd be great.
You haven't told
the missus
about the castle?
You're in
for a spanking,
my friend.
Myself and my lady,
no secrets.
PHYLLIS:
Jim, don't listen to Andy.
I think it's so romantic.
JIM: Oh, thanks, Phyllis.
Bob bought our house without
consulting me and I loved it.
Yeah? You didn't mind
not choosing?
Oh, no. Not at all.
But Bob's so extravagant,
I knew
it would be spectacular.
There's a maze
in the back
like The Shining.
Where's your place?
It's on Linden Ave.,
by the quarry.
Cool beans, man.
I live by the quarry.
We should hang out
by the quarry and
throw things down there.
Definitely, we should.
OSCAR: "To whoever made
the microwave mess.
"The microwave is
a shared kitchen appliance.
"By not cleaning it up,
you are basically
telling whoever follows
"that their time
is less valuable,
"as they will have to
scrub out
your disgusting splatter.
"Sincerely,
Disappointed."
That is just obnoxious.
OSCAR: No kidding.
Yeah.
Wait, what?
The mess or the note?
The note.
So "holier than thou."
I liked it.
Don't you think
the person
who left the mess
is the obnoxious one?
No.
The note is way more
obnoxious than the mess.
"Sincerely, Disappointed."
Get off
your high horse, richie.
Just because
someone likes things clean
doesn't mean they're rich.
Nah. They're rich.
Yeah, I wrote the note.
Not ashamed of it.
I'm not proud of it.
It is what it is.
Everyone keeps asking me
if I wrote the note
on the microwave.
It was rude and condescending
and a little snotty.
I wish I had written it.
(READING)
The nerve!
You want to see some
real high-caliber acting?
Well, Mr. Kurt Russell,
you are about to be served.
Hey, Toby.
Great to have you back, man.
Seriously. Just...
Just a real pleasure
to see you again.
Thanks, Michael.
You're welcome.
Missed you.
Missed you
as part of our family.
Well, that's sweet.
I missed you guys, too.
So Costa Rica, that was...
Did you have fun?
That must have been fun.
Well, it was amazing,
really was.
Thanks for asking.
Beaches were pristine.
Nice beaches,
pristine beaches?
Yeah.
The whole thing was
incredibly cathartic.
Why'd you come back?
Why didn't you stay?
Well, it's actually
kind of hard
to meet people, I found.
I bet. For you.
And, yeah...
Plus, it was hot.
Hot. Why didn't
you get an air...
Should've gotten
an air conditioner
for yourself.
Are you
all right, Michael?
Yeah, I am. I am.
I tried. I tried.
I tried to talk to Toby
and be his friend,
but that is like
trying to be friends
with an evil snail.
I feel like
I'm dying inside.
Neve Campbell
in Scream 2.
She thinks she can
go off to college
and be happy.
And then,
the murderer comes back
and starts killing off
all of her friends.
Learned a lot of lessons
from that movie.
This is just one of them.
Okay, just summarize.
Okay,
fireable offenses include
workplace violence
and sexual harassment.
That's it.
That's it, perfect.
We will get him
to hit on somebody,
and then we'll
catch him in the act.
I love catching
people in the act.
That's why I always
whip open doors.
Me, too.
Okay,
let's get this started.
Okay.
What are you doing?
I am the bait.
For what?
Men find me desirable.
No, no, no.
It's a good day, too.
I'm wearing my mustard shirt.
You're the bait for Toby?
No. For one thing,
he's not gay.
And if somebody
were to be bait,
it would be Jim
or Ryan or me.
Men find me desirable.
Yes.
Sure they do, Dwight.
When it comes down to it,
it's a health issue.
I should've written that.
Yeah.
Why aren't you as mad
or interested in this
as me?
Oh, totally.
Sorry, are we talking about
the microwave still?
Are you inching away
from me?
No.
Reach your arms out.
I'm always this close.
(SINGING) Pamtown ladies
sing this song
doo-dah doo-dah
Hello, Pam.
Jim, may I have
a moment with Pam,
please?
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
Yes. I just have to
take this call anyway,
so...
His mistress!
No, I'm kidding.
No one would
ever cheat on you.
You are
the complete package, Pam.
What do you need, Michael?
Okay, what I would
like you to do
is take this folded note
and deliver it to
Toby Flenderson.
I want you to just react
to whatever
this note elicits.
Do not read it
beforehand.
Can you do that for me?
Sure.
Good.
No, no, no, no, don't...
"Please hug and kiss me,
no matter how hard I struggle.
"I am too shy to tell you
that I love you."
Damn it, Pam.
You gave me your word.
You have a good day?
Hey. Hey, guys,
that's really
inappropriate.
What's up?
I got some photos
from Costa Rica
if you want to see them.
Yeah, yeah, I'll see them.
Cool.
Toby, can I see those?
What's the matter?
You scared?
Okay, those are
fighting words.
You mad?
You mad at me?
I hope he doesn't
haul off
and just hit you.
Do you want to do that?
Do you want to hit me?
You want to punch me?
MICHAEL: He might do it.
I dare you to.
Punch him, Toby.
Come on.
Come on...
What's the matter?
Hit him.
Hit him, chicken!
Yeah, punch him.
Hey, hey.
Come on, Ryan.
Whose side are you on?
DWIGHT: Ryan, come on, man.
No, do it. Do it.
I dare you.
Punch him as hard
as you possibly can
in the face.
I dare you, Flenderson.
Not...
Not as hard
as you can.
Just a good,
solid punch.
Come on, come on.
I'm not going to
punch you, Michael.
Are you really not
going to punch him?
No, why would I punch you?
Son of a bitch.
Should have hit him, man.
The guy was asking for it.
Once in a lifetime, man.
"Hey, whoever
was bashing the first note,
grow up.
"The microwave is filthy
and no one here is a maid."
See? Someone
around here is sane.
"You are all a bunch of idiots
and privileged ass-wipes
who werert raised right.
"If I find you,
I'm gonna
knock your teeth out."
Yikes.
That's a little
over the top.
Their heart's
in the right place.
I thought you were
going to
parcel those out
through the day.
Would you stop it?
You haven't done
anything helpful all day.
There's still
one thing we can do
to get Toby fired.
What's that?
Frame him for using drugs.
Frame him?
Yeah.
It's illegal,
but everything they do
on The Shield is illegal.
I've never
framed a man before.
Have you?
No, I've framed
animals before.
I framed a raccoon
for opening
a Christmas present.
And I framed a bear
for eating
out of the garbage.
It just seems
awfully mean.
But sometimes,
the ends justify
the mean.
Punch you, Michael.
Hello.
I've seen you guys around.
I'm Michael Scott,
Dunder Mifflin.
How you doing?
So I guess you
know why I'm here.
I need to
purchase something.
Like a fridge?
No.
I wanted...
I wanted to buy
some weed from someone.
What?
Grass, weed.
What makes you think
we'd have weed?
I heard you were drug...
I heard you dealt.
Hey, just hold on
one second.
I'm not wearing
a wire, so...
Why would you
even say that?
Hey, it's going
to be $500.
How much?
$500.
It's a good price.
It's a steal.
How many pounds
is that?
LEO: It's two pounds.
I'm losing money
on this, man,
just give me the money.
Okay.
All right. Walk away,
walk away, walk away.
Hey, Pam? I just
wanted to let you know,
I'm totally on your side
with the whole
microwave situation.
Thank you.
I was just back there
to make some Cup-a-Soup,
the thing
is still a huge mess.
I know.
Can you believe it?
Yeah, it's crazy.
But I guess the thing is,
at some point,
notes or no notes,
someone's going to
have to just get in there
and clean it up.
I guess that's why
we have a temp, huh?
Oh, no, trust me,
I would just
make it worse.
How would wiping it
with a paper towel
make it worse?
I would find a way.
You've seen things
clean before though,
right?
I... Pam,
I am hopeless
at that stuff.
Hi, Michael.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
I forgot...
DWIGHT: (WHISPERING)
Yes. I repeat,
a drug dealer
is on the premises
of Dunder Mifflin.
His name is
Toby Flenderson.
And he recently returned
from a mysterious vacation
in Central America.
I have risked a great deal
to tell you this information.
My name is Andy Bernard.
Andrew Bernard,
that's my name.
See you soon.
Pervert!
Angela, I didn't
do that.
So is this what
they taught you
at your fancy art school?
Why would I draw
a penis on my own note?
Why do you wear bright colors?
For attention, Pam.
Everyone, I have
an announcement to make.
I'm the person
who put the first note
on the microwave.
But I did it because
it needed to be said.
Why did you hide
behind anonymity?
Because I was scared.
But if that's my only crime,
is it a worse crime
than leaving
a filthy microwave?
Amen.
Don't.
This is for real.
Just clean it up yourself
if it bothers you so much.
It's not my mess.
It would've taken less time
to clean it up
than to write all those notes.
That's not the point.
Listen, New York,
that might fly...
Why? Because
I went to New York
for three months?
That and the black sweater,
Manattan.
Okay, yes.
I went to New York,
everybody.
I'm not gonna apologize
for it.
I experienced more there
in one week than I experience
here in three months.
I love New York.
You know, I especially love
that people there
cleaned up after themselves.
Well, I work too hard
all day to be
maid here, too.
I got a mess to clean up
at home, plus
I'm a part-time maid.
And what about
the penises?
I thought those were funny.
I didn't do them, Phyllis.
OSCAR: It's the anonymity
that I find so cowardly, Pam.
Really? Can you just
get over that part?
Why should I?
You couldn't get over
the messy microwave.
What?
I can't do this.
Can't do what?
It's not fair to you
and it's really
not fair to me.
Wait, what are you saying?
I broke up with Darryl
so I could be with you.
That was your choice.
Don't put that on me.
I'm just going
on a little trip.
Can I come?
It's not
that kind of trip.
I'm going to Thailand
with some friends
from high school.
Well, a high school.
And if I don't do it now,
I'll never get to go.
And I'll always
resent you for it.
You don't want me
to resent you, do you?
So you're dumping me?
Let's be adults about this.
Let's have sex
one more time,
and if you have
any extra cash,
that would be amazing.
Okay.
Hi. We received a call.
I don't know
anything about that.
We were tipped off
about a possible
narcotics situation.
Here?
Hey, Pam, hey,
I got this, okay?
Hello, officers.
Dwight Schrute,
former volunteer
sheriff's deputy.
Listen, I may have
inside information
that someone
is hiding drugs
in this very office.
Just pretend
like we're talking
until the cops leave.
Those are real cops.
Real guns.
Wonder what's going on.
Officers, I reveal to you
the perpetrator.
Hey, what is this?
Search his things.
Sir, could you
step away from
your desk, please?
Why?
Sir, please step away
from your desk.
Hey, what's going on?
You don't have
my permission
to do this.
They don't need
your permission,
Flenderson.
They've got
the company's
permission.
Hey, hey,
what are you...
Why are you doing this?
You know what?
I think this...
This is probably
a misunderstanding.
Don't search my stuff.
POLICEMAN: Sir.
I have a reasonable
right to privacy.
Save your whining
for the jury there,
Flenderson.
Yeah, let's just
cancel this, okay?
TOBY: Michael?
Sir, did you recently
return from a trip
to Central America?
Oh, my God.
I went to Costa Rica
for a few months.
MICHAEL: No, no, no.
That was legitimate.
What is going on?
MICHAEL:
That was totally legitimate.
Hey, check this out.
MICHAEL: Oh, God!
That is not mine.
Turn around please.
I have never
seen this before.
No, no, no, no, God!
What is going on here?
No, that's...
I don't know
what that is.
Do you have any weapons?
Of course not!
I bet he has nothing
to do with that.
That's mine.
No, Michael, no!
Yes, it's mine.
Some basil.
And salad dressing,
I think.
Salad dressing?
Yeah, it's a Caprese salad.
There's a little bit of
mozzarella right there.
Are you kidding me?
That's my salad.
So wait a minute.
There's no drugs?
POLICEMAN: No.
Oh, damn it. Come on!
We got a fake tip.
Wait, officers,
are you sure you
don't want to
interrogate him?
POLICEMAN: No.
You have laws
that protect you
in any kind
of interrogation.
Why don't you use them?
You must feel pretty good
about yourself right now.
I didn't put Caprese salad
in my drawer, Michael.
Did you?
Since when is it illegal
to put Caprese salad
anywhere?
You know, the police
could have been out there,
catching real criminals,
instead of here,
searching my stuff.
Are you kidding me?
That's what
you're worried about?
You're worried
about the cops' time.
You think I framed you
and you're worried
about the taxpayer?
God!
Welcome back,
jerky jerk-face.
You said you were leaving,
and you made liars
out of all of us.
I did leave.
Yes, you did.
And then you came back.
Which makes you
the biggest liar
of history.
I don't see it
that way.
Do you want to
hear a lie?
What?
I think you're great.
You're my best friend.
Hey, do you mind
if we make a stop
on the way home?
Sure.
Cool.
What are we doing at
your parents' house?
I have a surprise for you.
All right. Ready?
Close your eyes.
And now, open your eyes.
Ta-da!
I don't get it.
I bought it.
It's ours.
Let's go inside.
I'll show you inside.
So if you can believe it,
I did it without a realtor.
Saving on
closing costs
is good.
And we can put
all the money
to de-shag the carpet.
Which I think will
help the color situation.
Yeah,
I am really sorry
about this.
I tried to move it,
but he is really
nailed in there.
Worried about
art theft, I guess.
A lot of art thieves
in this neighborhood.
This is the master bedroom,
but I'm actually
not allowed in here.
So, I'm still in the process
of converting the garage.
It's got great light
in here.
And I was thinking
it could be perfect
for an art studio.
Look, I know.
I bought this
without asking you.
And it doesn't look great.
I know that.
And if you really hate it,
I totally understand.
It's just...
I love it.
You do?
Yeah, I love it.
Really?
I mean,
you bought me a house.
Oh, my God.
You bought me a house!
Yeah, I did.
Do we have to sleep
in your parents' bedroom?
No. No, we'll just
board that up.
It'll be that
weird spare room
that people ask us about.
And the clown?
Yeah, I really
can't move him.
What is my perfect crime?
I break into Tiffany's
at midnight.
Do I go for the vault?
No, I go for the chandelier.
It's priceless.
As I'm taking it down,
a woman catches me.
She tells me to stop.
It's her father's business.
She's Tiffany.
I say no.
We make love all night.
In the morning, the cops come
and I escape
in one of their uniforms.
I tell her to
meet me in Mexico,
but I go to Canada.
I don't trust her.
Besides, I like the cold.
30 years later,
I get a postcard.
I have a son and
he's the chief of police.
This is where
the story gets interesting.
I tell Tiffany
to meet me in Paris
by the Trocadero.
She's been waiting
for me all these years.
She's never
taken another lover.
I don't care.
I don't show up.
I go to Berlin.
That's where
I stashed the chandelier.