DWIGHT: Last week,
I gave a fire safety talk,
(CLEARS THROAT LOUDLY)
And nobody paid
any attention.
It's my own fault
for using PowerPoint.
PowerPoint is boring.
People learn in
lots of different ways,
but experience is
the best teacher.
Today, smoking is
going to save lives.
Does anyone
smell anything smoky?
Did you bring
your jerky in again?
(CLEARS THROAT)
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Fire!
Oh, fire! Oh, my goodness.
What's the procedure?
DWIGHT: What do we do, people?
The phones are dead.
Oh. How did that happen?
It's out in the hall.
No. We don't know that.
The smoke could be
coming through
an air duct.
Oh, my God!
Okay, it's happening.
Everybody stay calm.
Everybody stay calm!
DWIGHT: What's the
procedure, everyone?
What's the procedure?
Stay... calm!
Everybody just... calm down!
No, no, Michael, no!
Touch the handle.
If it's hot there could
be a fire in the hallway!
What does warm mean?
Oh, my gosh.
Try a different door.
(ALL CLAMORING)
Not a viable option.
What next?
MICHAEL: Don't run!
JIM: Try the other door.
DWIGHT: Here's a door.
Check that one out.
How's the handle?
It's warm.
JIM: Okay,
go to the back door.
Well, another option.
Another option.
Jeez! Okay,
settle down, everyone!
PHYLLIS: I forgot my purse!
Leave it, woman!
MICHAEL: Get out of the way!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Things can be replaced,
Phyllis!
People, human lives,
however...
(EXCLAIMS)
My hand! That's hot!
This one's hot, too.
Okay, we're trapped.
Everyone for himself!
Let's go! Let's go!
Get out of my way!
DWIGHT: Okay. Okay. Okay!
KEVIN: Get out of the way!
DWIGHT: Have you ever
seen a burn victim?
Move it!
DWIGHT: Okay!
Procedure! Procedure!
Exit options!
Where do we go, folks?
DWIGHT: Use a what to
cover the mouth?
(SHUSHING) It's okay.
A what? A rag,
a damp rag perhaps.
Let's remember
those procedures.
What are the options?
Okay! That's the wrong way.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
We've already tried that.
Remember your exit points.
DWIGHT: Exit points, people.
Oscar?
DWIGHT: What's next, huh?
Oscar!
Stay alive, I'm getting help!
Pull me up!
You're too heavy.
I only weigh 82 pounds.
(CAT MEOWS)
Save Bandit!
(CAT YOWLS)
How about 911? Anyone? 911?
What do we do?
Use the surge of
fear and adrenaline
to sharpen
your decision making.
Okay, I am
not dying here.
Come on.
(FIRECRACKERS BURSTING)
ANGELA: What is that?
What is that?
The fire's shooting at us!
What in the name of God
is going on?
(ALARM RINGING)
I'm trying to...
(PHYLLIS SCREAMS)
(SCREAMS)
Help! Help!
Oh, my God!
(AIR HORN BLARING)
Attention!
Employees of Dunder Mifflin!
This has been
a test of our
emergency preparedness.
There's no fire.
It was only a simulation.
What?
Fire not real.
This was merely
a training exercise.
So what have we learned?
Oh, come on.
It's not real, Stanley.
KEVIN: Oh, my God.
DWIGHT: Don't have
a heart attack.
No, no, no, no,
you will not die!
Stanley! Stanley!
You will not die! Stanley!
Stanley! Barack is President!
You are black, Stanley!
I'm gonna give
him mouth-to-mouth.
No, no, no.
Don't give him
mouth-to-mouth for this.
He just swallowed
his tongue.
Michael! Michael!
Open your mouth.
Don't swallow it!
I'm fine!
Leave me...
I'm saving him!
How could you
possibly think
this is a good idea?
A lot of ideas
were not appreciated
in their time.
Electricity.
Shampoo.
You could have burned down
the whole building.
I just want to say,
for the record,
I did not kill anyone.
Stanley was attacked
by his own heart.
And he should be
released from the hospital
and back in the office
in a couple days.
Did you shout "fire,"
causing a panic?
Yes, I shouted "fire."
I shouted many things.
I also shouted instructions
on how to get out
of the building.
So you can
imagine my frustration,
as safety officer,
when nobody would heed of...
Heeded... Heeded of...
"Head." "Head."
When no one headed...
"Take headed of."
No one would
take headed of
my instructions.
So you...
"Heed." "Heed."
"Take heed of."
And I don't see my co-workers
heeding this right now.
Wait, what?
Okay.
(SIGHS)
(EXHALES) The city.
Dwight.
We are not mad,
we are just disappointed.
No, we are mad.
Yes, we are.
We are livid.
But we are going to
let this one slide.
DWIGHT: Thank you.
No, we're not.
I am not
a mind reader, David.
Look, this is
a very serious offense.
We have cause to fire you.
MICHAEL: (WHISPERING)
Can you shove down?
Instead...
Shove down, please.
Instead what I think
we should do is
strip you of your
title as safety officer.
No.
And we should take
a part of his pay
and donate it
to the charity
of your choice.
Something that
Dwight doesn't like.
PETA.
Michael, you have to
take responsibility here.
One of your employees
had a heart attack.
He could have died
because of the way
you're allowing
your office to run.
Do you want that
on your conscience?
Do you?
DAVID: Michael?
Are you talking to me?
DAVID: Yeah.
What?
Well, I guess
we papered over that
pretty nicely.
(CHUCKLES SMUGLY)
Always amuses me
when corporate thinks
they can make some big change
with a 20-minute meeting
in some fancy high rise.
What's the matter?
Are you hungry?
No, Dwight,
I am worried.
A mars life is
in my hands.
Now don't you
worry about that.
I got it covered. Okay?
I am planning a bomb scare
that should really
get the blood pumping.
That's not going to happen.
I'm taking over
as safety man.
What? You?
Yes.
Come on.
I'm a smart guy.
That's preposterous.
I'll figure it out.
No. I will.
Nobody should have to
go to work thinking,
"Oh, this is the place
that I might die today."
That's what a hospital's for.
An office is for not dying.
An office is a place to
live life to the fullest,
to the max. To...
An office is a place
where dreams come true.
(SHUSHING)
Don't excite him.
Don't make him excitable.
Welcome back, Stanley.
Thank you, Michael.
It's true,
around this office
in the past
I have been a little
abrupt with people.
Not maybe, yes or no.
No way. Uh-uh.
Are you from another planet?
Boy, have you
lost your mind?
Because I'll
help you find it!
Did I stutter?
I'm done. Goodbye.
But the doctor said
if I can't find a new way
to relate more positively
to my surroundings,
I'm going to die.
Andy.
(IN BRITISH ACCENT)
A throne for your highness.
I'm not sitting
in a wheelchair.
No, no, no.
No debate.
You are going to
sit in that wheelchair
until you are
back on your feet.
I'm going to die.
ABC, okay?
And that stands for
"Airway, Breathing
and Circulation."
Okay. You know what?
That could be
a little confusing,
because in sales ABC
means "Always Be Closing."
This is a farce.
I should be
teaching this course.
Shut it. Shut it.
We found ourselves
on the less prepared
side of things
when Stanley had his...
When his heart went berserk.
And I knew
exactly what to do.
But in a much more real sense,
I had no idea what to do.
So I thought we should have
a CPR training class.
And of course you can't
get the practice dummy
unless the instructor
comes along with it.
Red Cross and their racket.
I can't keep
doing this forever.
It's been 20 seconds.
Call it.
Would you like to try next?
Absolutely I would not.
You know who
I really think
should go?
Stanley.
Oh, I don't know.
It's not
a good idea, Michael.
He needs to rest.
No rest for the sick.
We are not always
going to be there
to coddle
your heart back when it
disappears to be working.
What are you going to do
if you're by yourself
and your heart stops?
I would die.
And you're
okay with that?
I'm okay with
the logic of it.
Uh-uh. No, no, no.
Come on. Get up.
Let's do this.
STANLEY: Yes,
I had a heart attack.
I would quit,
but I'm too old
to find another job.
And I don't have
enough saved to retire.
I feel like I'm
working in my own casket.
Come on, Stanley!
You're losing you!
You're losing you! Do it!
Michael.
MICHAEL: This is you
we're talking about.
Michael.
Okay, okay,
I'll show them.
Here we go.
All right.
ROSE:
So assessing the situation.
Are they breathing?
No, Rose.
They are not breathing.
And they have no arms or legs.
No, that's not part of it.
Where are they?
You know what?
If we come across somebody
with no arms or legs,
do we bother
resuscitating them?
I mean, what kind of
quality of life
do we have there?
I would want to
live with no legs.
How about no arms?
No arms or legs is
basically how you exist
right now, Kevin.
You don't do anything.
ROSE: All right.
Well, let's get back to it,
because you're losing him.
Okay, too fast.
Everyone, we need to
pump at a pace of 100
beats per minute.
Okay. That's hard
to keep track.
How many is that per hour?
How is that
going to help you?
I will divide
and then count to it.
Right.
Okay, well, a good trick
is to pump to
the tune of Staying Alive
by the Bee Gees.
Do you know that song?
Yes, yes. I do.
I love that song.
(SINGING)
First I was afraid,
I was petrified
No, it's...
(VOCALIZING)
(SINGING)
Stayir alive,
stayir alive
Okay. That's enough.
You were in
the parking lot earlier.
That's how I know you.
(VOCALIZING)
(SINGING)
Stayir alive,
stayir alive
(BOTH VOCALIZING)
Stayir alive, stayir alive
Well, you can tell by
the way I use my walk
I'm a womars man,
no time to talk
Music loud, women warm
Been kicked around
since I was born
Well, it's all right
It's okay
You can look the other way
ROSE: Okay! Okay!
(VOCALIZING)
ALL: Stayir alive,
stayir alive
Yeah. Okay,
you didn't maintain
a hundred beats per minute.
And the ambulance
didn't arrive
because nobody called 911.
So you lost him.
Okay, he's dead.
Anyone know what we do next?
Anybody? Rose?
I have no idea.
Anyone else?
We bury him.
Wrong! Check for
an organ donor card.
If he has one,
we only have
minutes to harvest.
He has no wallet,
I checked.
He is an organ donor.
He is?
Get me some ice
and Styrofoam bucket.
Here we go.
ANGELA: Oh, my God!
KELLY: Dwight!
Dwight!
(DWIGHT SCREAMING)
KELLY: Dwight, what are you...
What are you doing?
We search for the organs.
Where's the heart?
The precious heart.
I'm not feeling well.
I need to sit down.
Stanley.
Hey, Stanley.
Are you okay?
(DWIGHT MAKING LICKING SOUNDS)
Oh, my God!
STANLEY: Oh, my God!
Dwight!
Clarice.
STANLEY: Oh, my God.
Can you tell me
why you had to cut
the face off the dummy?
I didn't think it
was very realistic
in the movie,
and it turns out
it's pretty realistic.
We had to pay for it.
It cost us $3,500.
$5,300 for a dummy?
Wow.
Well, okay, look.
David, this is
why we have training.
We start with the dummy
and we learn
from our mistakes.
And now Dwight knows
not to cut the face
off of a real person.
Hope you
brought your apetitos,
my lady, my Tuna.
A little movie popcorn.
Damn it.
This movie,
a lot of buzz.
Not coming out
for another six months.
Mrs. Albert Hanaday.
So the friendship
with the Nard-Dog
has its privileges.
We don't normally
download films illegally
because we're honest,
hard-working people.
And we don't know how.
But Andy does,
so we have to
watch it with him.
Punishment fits
the crime.
I want you to meet my nana.
Nana, this is Sam.
Hi. Nice to meet you,
Mrs. Hanaday.
Please, call me Lily.
Let's play bridge.
You can be my partner.
All right, Lily.
(CELL PHONE BEEPS)
(SIGHS)
What's going on?
No one really knows,
but Pam's parents
are going through
a little bit of a rough
patch in their marriage.
My dad spent the night
at our place last night.
My parents have been
fighting for weeks
and it kind of sucks.
Jim's been great.
But I'm going to need
to buy my dad a robe.
He's not saying
what he needs to say.
Hmm?
Who? Jack Black?
Yeah.
I mean, they just
need to communicate,
you know.
If they said to each other
what they're saying to
everyone else, then...
Hmm.
Jim and Pam are
like movie geniuses.
They're catching things
that are totally
going over my head.
Hi, everyone.
Corporate has given
Dwight two strikes.
They are very,
very upset with him.
So, as a
disciplinary measure,
he is going to
have to issue
a formal apology.
Dwight, have you prepared
your statement of regret?
I have.
Let's hear it.
(CLEARS THROAT)
I state my regret.
You couldn't have
memorized that?
I could not
because I do not feel it.
Okay, everyone,
I'm going to need you
to sign
this statement of regret
as an acknowledgment
that you heard it.
Okay?
Everyone come on up here.
It's not a big deal.
It is a big deal.
You almost killed Stanley.
Yeah, right.
I filled him full of butter
and sugar for 50 years
and forced him
not to exercise.
Now take a lesson
from Stanley
and jog on up here
and sign this. Okay?
Make a line.
Just form a line
right here.
Sign it! Sign it now!
(TELEPHONE RINGS)
Hi, Dad.
Yeah, Jim has shaving cream.
Check our bathroom.
SAM: Lily?
I'm in here.
I... I'm sorry.
I didn't
realize you were
in the bath.
Do you want me to go?
I want you to stay.
Oh, boy.
Oh, man.
You know,
Lily was supposed
to be Nicole Kidman.
And it was going
to be Sophie's mom,
not grandmother.
But then Nicole Kidman
dropped out,
so they went with
Cloris Leachman,
with a small rewrite.
SAM: Just give me your hand
and get that in there.
Help me pull it around.
Oh, yeah.
You did
that one already.
I know,
but if I get it deeper...
What is...
He was pretty
talkative at breakfast.
What?
Breakfast?
You mean when they
were eating soup?
I don't think
that was breakfast.
Unless soup...
Does soup
symbolize breakfast?
So he doesn't share
with his daughter,
but he shares with
his daughter's fiance?
You guys, they're making out.
Hey.
Did my dad say
anything about my mom?
No. We mostly just
talked about cereal.
What?
I don't know.
I mean,
maybe he'll talk to you
about some of the stuff
'cause he can't
really talk to me about it.
Mmm...
You're good to talk to.
I'm okay.
I'm not great.
And...
(CHANTING IN SANSKRIT)
Everybody sit on the floor,
Indian-style like me.
My God,
if you're wearing a dress,
please keep your
knees together,
nobody wants to see that.
My goal is to make
this office as peaceful
a place for Stanley Hudson
as I can.
And I think
sounds have a lot
to do with that.
Here are some downloaded
peaceful sounds.
(SERENE INSTRUMENTAL
MUSIC PLAYING)
(SAD INSTRUMENTAL
That one makes me think
of death.
It's kind of nice.
MICHAEL: It is
a beautiful, sunny day
as we walk
through the meadow.
That is very
spiritual and relaxing.
And there are flowers
and it is sunny
and beautiful.
(WHISPERING) Now, up ahead,
a castle in the distance.
Don't open your eyes.
What? Oh.
And you walk up
toward the castle.
And inside the castle
are four men,
and each of them...
None of them have shoes.
And they give you
a funny cigarette
and you feel
even more relaxed,
and then you want ice cream.
You want a big bowl
of ice cream.
So what kind of ice
cream do you want?
Yell it out.
Chunky Monkey.
Too expensive.
Chocolate.
Racism is dead, Stanley.
You can have any kind
of ice cream you want.
(BEEPING)
What do you want?
What is that?
People, please,
I told you
to get rid of
the cell phones.
It's my bio-feedback machine.
Oh, okay. What is that,
like a video game?
It alerts me when my
stress level goes up,
so I can try to calm down.
You have stress?
Yes.
During our
relaxation exercise?
PHYLLIS: Let me
get you some water.
No, no, I'll help you up.
I'll help you up.
Here we go. Here we go.
Let me get you up.
No, Michael.
Would you step back?
(BEEPING RAPIDLY)
Please, please.
Okay. All right.
A little further.
MICHAEL: Okay.
(BEEPING SLOWS DOWN)
That's better.
(BEEPING STOPS)
(BEEPING STARTS)
(BEEPING RAPIDLY)
Okay.
(BEEPING SLOWS DOWN)
I think that thing
is on the fritz.
(BEEPING STOPS)
Oscar, would you reach over
and touch his thing?
That's what he said.
Right, guys?
Because of gay.
Let's give this a shot.
Hello!
(BEEPING RAPIDLY)
Michael, I think
you're what's
stressing everybody out.
So it wasrt
Dwight after all.
Looks like I'm the killer.
You never expect
that you're the killer.
It's a great twist.
Great twist.
(TELEPHONE RINGS)
Dunder Mifflin. This is Pam.
Oh. Hey, Mom. No.
What did Dad say?
(DOOR OPENS)
What did you say to my dad?
What?
After you talked,
he called my mom
and said he was gonna look
for an apartment.
Oh, my God.
Pam, I don't know.
I...
Nothing, truly nothing.
I mean, I just
was honest with him
and I...
I'm so sorry.
I don't know.
I'll call him again.
50 percent of marriages
end in divorce,
so it was her parents
or my parents.
What could Jim have said
to make my dad
want to leave my mom?
And at what
point in our marriage
is he gonna say it to me?
MICHAEL: I don't get it.
Do I stress you out?
Nothing stresses me out.
Except having to seek
the approval of my inferiors.
Speaking of which...
Remember when
people used to say "boss"
when they were
describing something
that was really cool?
Like, "Those shoulder pads
are really boss, man."
"Look at that perm.
That perm is so boss."
It's what made me
want to become a boss.
And I looked so good
in a perm and shoulder pads.
But now boss is just slang
for "jerk in charge."
Okay, everybody,
I figured it out.
The reason
that you are all so
stressed around me
is that you are
too intimidated
to tell me
what you really think.
You are keeping
these feelings inside
and that is causing stress.
So, what is the solution?
Solution is honesty,
laughter and comedy.
In short...
A vacation.
What? No. No.
I'm talking about
a roast of Michael Scott.
Come on. Who here has
the Comedy Central
Roast Channel?
You've seen it, right?
Everybody gets together
and you start hurling
insults at the one guy,
and everybody's laughing
and everybody is
hugging each other.
Michael, are you serious?
Do you really want us
to roast you?
(IN SPANISH)
That's offensive.
It's not!
It's not offensive
during a roast.
Anything goes.
And I want you guys
to really get
cracking on this.
I want you to take me down.
Don't hold back.
I want you to really make fun
of anything about me.
It could be my race,
could be the fact
that I'm so fit,
or I'm a womanizer,
fair game. Whatever.
I don't want to write
your stuff for you,
but I just want it
to be good.
(GIGGLING) Oh, my God.
Oh, man. Oh, my God.
I consider myself
a good person,
but I'm gonna try
to make him cry.
MICHAEL: I can already
feel people's stress
starting to melt.
I think they're
very excited about paying
their respects this way.
I've got to make sure
that YouTube comes down
to tape this.
May I have your attention,
please? Sign in.
Sign in on the sign-in sheet,
the clipboard.
This meeting is mandatory,
if you do not sign in,
your name will not be counted.
Thank you.
Hey, this is
your apology letter.
It was the last signature
I needed.
(CLAPPING)
(WHOOPING)
Welcome, welcome,
welcome, welcome, welcome!
You are all jerks.
Just kidding.
Not yet, anyway.
Welcome to the roast
of Mr. Michael Scott.
If you are here for
the Grabowski wedding,
it is the second door
on the left.
So, we all know
how these work.
It needs to get crazy.
Take your best shot.
I'm going to sit
right over chair.
And whoever wants to come up
and roast me, you may. Okay.
Lower the mike
for the midget.
If you ever wondered
whether you were
Michael Scott,
here's a quiz to help.
If you ever put
sun block on a window,
you might be Michael Scott.
(ALL LAUGH)
I normally don't enjoy
making people laugh.
If you ever called
the fire department
because your head was
stuck in your chair,
you might be...
ALL: Michael Scott.
(LAUGHING)
(CLAPPING)
Hey, hey.
I don't go make burgers
where you work
and then tell you
how to make burgers.
I have made a list of people
that I would make out with
before I would make out
with Michael Scott.
A turtle, a fridge,
anybody from the warehouse.
(WHOOPING)
Yeah!
A wood chipper, Kevin,
a candle and Lord Voldemort.
Anyway,
happy birthday, Michael.
Yeah.
(CLAPPING)
You'd be so lucky. Good one.
Michael,
you ran over me
with your car.
(HITS DRUMS)
You posted a picture
of my bare boobs
on the bulletin board
with a caption
that said, "Gross."
Well...
Michael, you are
the reason I drink.
You are the reason
I live to forget.
(IMITATES GUNSHOTS)
(YELLING IN SPANISH)
No, no, friends only.
Friends only!
Several times a day,
Michael says words
that are way
beyond my vocabulary.
I know where
this is going.
Do you?
No.
Okay.
Remember spider face?
No.
Okay, because
the quote was,
"Cut off your nose
to spider face."
Spider... Okay.
(AUDIENCE LAUGHING)
Yeah, yeah.
How dare you all
attack him like this?
No, stop it.
Michael is
your superior, okay?
Dwight. No, no, no, no.
You should be bowing
down in front of him.
Hey, hey. Right now. Okay?
They don't understand
who they have.
That is the way
you're supposed
to do it, idiot.
You're interrupting me.
I'm trying to get your back.
I'm trying to...
Idiot, idiot.
Idiot.
Are you calling me
an idiot?
Don't you ever
talk to me that way,
you pathetic
short little man.
You don't have any friends
or any family or any land!
Yeah!
MAN: Yeah!
(ALL APPLAUDING)
Well, I just want to
take a minute to
talk to you all
about something
very serious.
Once every hour,
someone is involved
in an Internet scam.
That man is
Michael Scott.
(AUDIENCE LAUGHS)
He's supporting about
20 Nigerian princesses.
Hey, you know what?
Forgive me for caring, right?
Well, you know,
Michael is
a great delegator.
He never does
any work himself, ever.
And one time
I walked in on him naked
and his thing is so small.
(ALL WHOOPING)
KEVIN: How small is it?
If it were an iPod,
it would be a shuffle.
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
All right, can I make
just a little announcement?
In a professional roast,
usually the roaster
will say something nice
about the roastee
after they're done.
Something about
how much they love them,
so just keep that in mind.
Mike claims
we're all a family.
You know what...
We are.
We are a family.
Okay, so, what's his name?
All the way in
the back there.
Oh, very funny.
What's his name?
Uh...
(CHUCKLES)
I'm thinking Roy.
Roy left years ago.
What's his name?
I don't believe
I've had the pleasure.
Michael, I gave you
a ride home last week
and we spent
an hour in traffic.
What's his name?
Jefferson.
Nope. His name is Michael.
(PLAYING UPBEAT ROCK MUSIC)
(AUDIENCE CLAPPING ALONG)
(SINGING)
What I hate about you
You really suck as a boss
You're the laziest, jerkiest
And you're dumber
than an apple sauce
We're stuck
listening to you all day
Stanley tried to die
just to get away
Well, it's true
That's what I hate about you
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDING)
(AND Y VOCALIZING)
Yeah!
And now a man who
deserves no introduction,
Michael Scott.
(SCATTERED BOOING)
Thank you very much.
Thank you. That was great.
Great job, some great laughs.
Really, really went after
my intelligence there.
(CLEARS THRO AT)
Dozens of online IQ tests
might prove you wrong, but...
And my thing isn't tiny,
it's average,
so get your facts straight.
(CLEARS THRO AT)
So when I heard that
there was going to be a roast
in my honor, I thought...
(GRUNTS)
Sorry. I think I have
a frog in my throat.
Um...
(SIGHS)
I decided to jot down
some quick thoughts
about you people.
Um...
First up, Phyllis and Kevin.
(SIGHING)
(TELEPHONE RINGS)
Dunder Mifflin. This is Pam.
I'm sorry, Michael's
not here right now.
Can I take a message?
Great. I will. Thanks.
It's very unusual for Michael
not to show up to work.
My guess,
he's either deeply depressed
or an icicle has
snapped off his roof
and impaled his brain.
He has this terrible habit
of standing directly
underneath them
and staring up at them.
And I always say,
"Michael, take two steps back
"and stare at the icicle
from the side."
And he's like,
"No, I like the way they look
"from standing
directly underneath them."
It was only a matter of time.
Michael is so dumb
that he tries to
put his M&M's
in alphabetical order.
(LAUGHS)
All right, Kevin,
enough with
the Michael jokes.
I think he got it
bad enough yesterday.
I'm almost done.
That reeks
and I'm trying to eat.
Attention, everyone,
I've just got
a text from Michael.
He says "personnel day."
Are we hiring?
Yeah. You're being replaced.
I think he meant
personal day.
I don't know.
That's quite a leap, Pam.
I hope he's okay.
I feel bad.
Give it up. He's dead.
He just sent a text.
What's a text?
(CAWING)
You know, sometimes
to get perspective,
I like to think about
a spaceman on a star
incredibly far away,
and our problems don't
matter to him
because we're just
a distant point of light.
But he feels sorry for me
because he has
an incredibly
powerful microscope
and he can see my face.
I'm okay.
No, I'm not.
Phyllis, there's
a package for you.
Oh.
Sign here.
Okay.
What?
Got it!
Sam, Sam, Sam.
It's not that you
dumped my granddaughter,
and it's not that
you want children,
it's that you lied to me.
Can't you see that?
Can't you see?
I can never trust you.
Lily, no. Lily.
Lily, please.
Lily, stop!
I don't care how
much time we have left.
I don't care
what my friends say.
And I don't care
what your mom thinks.
Frankly, I'm pretty sure
she's not making any sense.
Please, move back
to my apartment.
(RESTRAINED SOB)
Lily, I'm not giving up.
I'm not giving up.
Lily, Lily!
Push the reverse button!
Reverse the button!
(SOBBING)
(ANDY SOBBING)
Sam. Sam.
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
Hey, Dad.
No, I know.
Mom told me.
Okay. Yeah,
I'll see you then.
So what did he say?
Was it my fault?
Yeah.
He said that you told him
how much you love me,
about how you feel
when I walk in a room
and about how
you've never doubted
for a second
that I'm the woman
you want to spend
the rest of your life with.
I guess he's never
felt that with my mom,
even at their best.
You okay?
Yeah.
(SNIFFLING)
When you're a kid,
you assume your
parents are soul mates.
My kids are gonna
be right about that.
I guess it also means
that sometimes
love affairs look different
to the people inside them.
I'm not insightful enough
to be a movie critic.
Maybe I could be
a food critic.
These muffins taste bad.
Or an art critic.
That painting is bad.
(DOOR OPENS)
Michael, it's
really good to see you.
Hey, why are you
wearing a turtleneck?
You all right?
Michael, I feel I was
a little harsh yesterday.
Yeah.
JIM: Yeah,
we're really sorry.
I spent the afternoon
in the park trying
to feed the pigeons.
I guess they all flew
west for the winter.
And I just had some thoughts
that I wanted to share
with you people.
What?
Well, I wrote them down
so I wouldn't forget.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Jim, you're 6'11"
and you weigh 90 pounds.
Gumby has
a better body than you.
Boom. Roasted.
Dwight, you're a kiss-ass.
Pam, you failed art school.
Boom. Roasted.
Meredith, you've slept
with so many guys
you're starting
to look like one.
Boom. Roasted.
Kevin, I can't decide
between a fat joke
and a dumb joke.
Boom. Roasted.
Creed, your teeth called,
your breath stinks.
Boom. Roasted.
Angela, where's Angela?
Well, there you are.
I didn't see you
behind that grain of rice.
Boom. Roasted.
Stanley, you crush
your wife during sex
and your heart sucks.
Boom. Roasted.
(LAUGHING)
MICHAEL: Oscar, you are...
(MICHAEL LAUGHS)
Oscar, you're gay.
Wow.
Andy, Cornell called,
they think you suck
and you're gayer than Oscar.
Boom. Roasted.
KEVIN: Boom. Roasted.
(LAUGHING HEARTILY)
(LAUGHS)
All right.
All right, everybody.
You know I kid.
You guys are the reason
that I went into
the paper business.
So, good night, God bless.
God bless America.
And get home safe.
Yeah.
They say that laughter
is the best medicine,
so, Stanley, you can
throw away those pills.
You are cured.
Actually, better hold on
to the pills, just in case.
(LILY MOANING)