Hi.
Good morning.
Can I help you?
Yes. I'm from
Tech Star, about
a new phone system for you.
I was wondering
if I could talk
to Michael Scott?
I'm sorry.
He's not in right now.
SALESMAN: Really?
He's never around
when I come by.
Shoot.
They have new
phone systems now
that can ring
directly to a salesman,
or someone presses star
and they go to accounting.
Basically, 95% of my job.
But I'd like to see
a machine that puts out
candy for everyone.
Vending machine.
How about I make
an appointment
to come back?
That way I know
he'll be here.
That is a great idea.
Great.
Oh, boy!
Let's see.
He's really...
Michael Scott, manager.
Hi, how are you?
Hi.
There he is.
Nice to meet you.
Great. Look at that.
I can assure you
we don't need
a new system, though.
We're happy with ours.
Hello. May I help you?
Jim-bo.
Jim.
Aye!
ALL: Aye!
Okay. I'm going
to get going then.
ALL: Aye!
(LAUGHING)
What was that?
That was funny.
Let's go do it
to somebody else.
Aye!
Look at that.
Cupids and hearts.
Really shoving our
faces in it this year.
You doing okay, bud?
I miss Stacy.
Yeah. I hear you.
It's been four months
since I was with Holly
and she was way
hotter than Stacy.
So if you think
you're hurting...
I can't even imagine.
(MICHAEL SIGHS)
This is our first and only
Valentine's Day as fiances.
You're only engaged once.
Well, present
company excluded,
but...
Really, Jim?
On Cupid's birthday?
Yeah.
She's fine.
So I received
my first Valentine
from a secret admirer.
"Roses are red,
violets are blue.
"It's time for
your dental cleaning
and maybe a checkup too."
Wow. Look at those.
How nice for you.
Up there,
front and center,
beautiful.
I think they would
look better right here.
They're very pretty and
I wouldn't want them to fall.
(GRUNTING)
MICHAEL: Just about
everybody in this office
is single right now.
Including me.
And everyone is experiencing
an incredible amount
of emotional pain.
Especially me,
because of my great
capacity for emotion.
And it is my first
Valentine's Day
since Holly,
so I think that I
am well qualified
to understand
that these people
need to be protected
from having love
shoved into their faces.
Pam, really? They're back?
I can't see them when
they're on the floor.
They're for her
to look at, Michael.
Can I have a word with you?
Yes, let's have a word.
Yes. Jim.
(WHISPERS) Today is a very
difficult day for a lot of
people in this office.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
And the sexy looks
between you and Pam,
the general sexiness,
the flowers,
it's creating
a bit of a hostile
work environment.
I understand.
It's so sexy it
becomes hostile.
I actually thought
we were keeping it
pretty low-key.
Well, if you guys insist
on having your own
private little love fest...
We do.
...that none of us
can be a part of...
You can't be a part
of our relationship, Michael.
Then we are going to have
our own private
Valentine's Day party.
That sounds fun.
So suck it.
DWIGHT: Yeah.
KEVIN: Yes.
Hey, everybody, I just
invited Jim to suck it,
and I am cordially
inviting all of you
to a special convention,
a lonely hearts convention
this afternoon.
Singles only.
Yeah. Deal with it, Pam!
So, we may not have
someone in our lives
that we love,
but we do have each other.
Having trouble
finding a vein?
Yeah. A little.
How about now?
I trained my major
blood vessels to retract
into my body on command.
Also I can retract my
penis up into itself.
I am about to give blood.
The gift of everlasting life,
the transfer of
my bodily fluids...
Wow, that's a big needle.
You're going to
need to lie down
right over here.
Okay. Hello.
Hi. I can't
talk right now.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
I'm really nervous.
Yeah. Me too.
Yeah?
When I get nervous,
I sort of clam up and...
Well, that's fine.
It's better for me
just to be quiet. Yeah.
Yeah. Can I point
something out to you?
Sure.
You're actually
talking a lot.
Yeah. Sorry.
That's the other thing I do
when I get really nervous.
Okay. Here we go.
NURSE: All right,
here we go.
Oh, God.
NURSE: Just relax.
Yeah. I'm good.
I feel like
a human juice box.
Oh, God.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Hawaiian blood punch.
That's gross.
Type O-cean Spray.
God, stop. Stop it.
Yeah.
Wouldrt it be cool?
Hey. Why don't
you guys come have
lunch with Bob and me?
We'll take all afternoon.
(WHISPERS) Michael is
terrified of Bob.
What do you think?
I have a lot of work
to do this afternoon.
Those mines aren't going
to sweep themselves.
We're in.
(EXCLAIMS IN DISGUST)
What?
I looked at the bag.
I looked straight
at the bag.
That's not good.
Could you distract me
for a second?
Just talk about things
that don't have
blood in them.
Well, okay. Bags.
That...
All right.
That was bad.
That was mean.
A hat.
A hat with no blood in it.
That is full of soup.
You're cute.
What?
NURSE: You're done.
Already?
We did it.
Wow, I was
so nervous about this.
I don't think
I ate for three days.
Is he okay?
Oh, my God.
How long was I out?
What?
Excuse me, waitress,
where did the lady go?
She left.
Okay.
Wait a second. Wait a second.
That's hers. This is hers.
She left her glove.
I need her name
if I'm going to
return her glove.
I'm sorry, sir.
We can't give out
that information.
(SIGHS)
What are you doing?
Decorating.
I'll help.
Now it's just
a stupid baby.
Yeah. Thanks.
It is so nice to go out
with another couple.
Anything to get
out of that office.
PHYLLIS: I know.
I honestly don't know
how you can work
with that jackass
and that other jackass
and that new jackass.
He's talking
about Michael,
Dwight and Andy.
Yeah. I understood.
Well, here we all are,
alone but together.
No flowers for us.
Relationships. We don't need
no stinking relationships.
I think we should all
go around and tell our
worst relationship story
and then get past it.
Just blow through it. Yeah?
Kelly, what about
Ryan? He treated
you pretty terribly.
Well, his heart was
in the right place.
Yeah, but now his
heart is in Thailand,
along with
the rest of his body,
having random sex.
Okay. Sorry.
Let's... Who else?
Oscar?
I don't think so.
Come on, I'm sure
there's something you
need to get off your chest.
Thank you.
You want to...
Just anything? You sure?
I'm sure
whatever you did
wasrt your fault.
Okay, well, who else?
Everyone here
who's bowled a 280,
please raise your hand.
No way.
Wow.
A 280?
That's impressive.
Okay, now everyone
here who's bowled
under 70 raise their hand.
Yikes.
Come on, Bob,
raise your hand.
No, Bob.
No.
What?
One time.
You love bringing
up that one time.
Yes, I do.
Jim uses a six-pound ball.
That is a lie.
Yes. He bowled five frames
with this pink sparkly thing
until a little girl had to
ask for her ball back.
But that girl must have
had monstrous hands
because the holes fit.
No, you just have
little dainty fingers.
You could always
model lady's jewelry.
Nobody asked, Bob.
(ALL LAUGHING)
Do you risk telling
them how you feel?
Do you say something
that you can barely
admit to yourself?
God, what did you do?
Not that I approve
of any of it, but...
I was stupid.
I told him.
Was he into you in,
like, a gay way?
Moron, if he was
there wouldn't be a story.
He told me he wasrt gay.
(ALL EXCLAIM SYMPATHETICALLY)
Really sad.
OSCAR: I'm not done yet.
Oh, my God.
A week later,
a friend of mine
calls me up
and he says, "I just saw him
in a gay bar in Kansas City."
Well, then it's
a happy ending,
because he was gay.
You should call him.
My worst breakup
was actually two breakups.
Two different men.
I was in love with
both of them and
when things went bad
they had a duel over me.
Yeah, Dwight and Andy.
We were here.
No.
This was years ago
when I was living in Ohio.
John Mark and John David.
Angela, you had
two sets of different men
actually duel over you?
I guess I have.
All right, who's next?
Where's Andy?
He's on one of
his honeymoons.
What?
He made nonrefundable deposits
on his honeymoons,
so he's just knocking
them off one at a time.
I think today he's
hot-air ballooning,
and later he's got
a couples' massage.
My worst breakup
was with Stacy.
It was a Sunday morning.
We were reading the paper
and I said, "Oh, my God,
I think the Eagles could
clinch the NFC East."
And she said that we're done.
You know what, guys, I don't
think we need to do this.
You're right.
Okay, everyone,
back to work.
No, no, no, no.
I mean have
this kind of party.
I look around and
I see all these
beautiful people
who are alone on Valentine's
and I think that there
are other single people
out there, too.
We just need to find them.
There's a girl out
there for all of us.
Maybe even in
this office park.
There has to be
a way to get all these
lonely people together.
A net? A giant net?
No, not a giant net.
What do you have in mind?
I was thinking
maybe like a mixer.
Oh, God, that's
a terrible idea.
Old-fashioned
meat market.
No.
I don't think it is.
Lonely people
mixing with one
another, breeding,
creating an even
lonelier generation?
You're not allowing
natural selection
to do its work.
You're like the guy
who invented the seatbelt.
These people need love.
And I am going
to get it for them.
Who cares if we
sell a little bit
less paper today?
A great boss cares more
about the happiness
of his employees
than anything else.
I am going to be Cupid.
And I'm going
to shoot my sparrow
at unsuspecting victims
and they are going to get hit
and say, "I'm in love.
"I was hit by
Cupid's sparrow."
Funny little bird,
but he gets the job done.
Hey.
Hey. No movement.
Still early.
Yeah, it's not that early.
So how are you holding up?
I'm okay.
I feel a little lopsided
because of all the blood
they took out of
my right side.
No, no. I meant
about being single today.
Meh.
Meh!
Exactly.
Here we go.
Hello.
MICHAEL: Hello.
Dwight K. Schrute.
Why don't you introduce me
to your little friend?
Hi. Dwight.
Babe alert.
Hello. I'm Michael Scott.
Welcome to our little shindig.
Hi. I'm Lynn.
Lynn, follow me.
Come on in.
Here we go.
For you we have one
of our top people,
Kevin Malone.
Kevin, come out here.
Show your beautiful self.
Hello.
Hi.
So run with the ball.
Run with it, Kev.
Where are you from?
I'm from here.
Yeah, okay.
Well, he only
gets better.
Thank you, Michael.
Okay.
I can untie any knot.
I'm serious.
Name a knot, any knot.
Go ahead.
I believe you.
You shouldn't believe
everything you hear.
In fact, there are many knots
that I cannot untie.
So what's a woman as
charming as yourself
find herself employed
on a day such as today?
I work at a place
that does catalogs for
community colleges
and small businesses.
You must use a lot of paper.
Oh, God, tons of it.
(SIGHS DELIGHTEDLY)
What's the rule
about eating
when people are
in the bathroom?
I think if you
ordered hot food
you're allowed to eat.
Damn.
They've been in there
for like ten minutes.
Look at that.
Bob ordered hot food.
Yes.
And I think they
gave him too many fries.
We should help him out.
At the Circle Drive-in,
they show old movies.
It's really cool.
That does sound cool.
I used to go there
with my fiancee.
Before she left me.
I mean, before I left her.
She left me.
Shoot.
I think I blew it.
It all happened so fast.
So fast.
So, Erik, you
mentioned before
that you are in
tool and die repair.
I am.
Meredith recently had
a total hysterectomy.
So that's sort of a repair.
All right,
I'll let you guys talk.
It's going very well.
People are mixing.
A lot of hope,
'cause that's
what you hate to see,
when hope gets crushed.
Sorry. Thought I heard
somebody coming in.
So, it's not too late.
(SIGHS)
DWIGHT: And the kind of
discounts we're talking
about are not...
Hold on. Michael,
why do you keep looking
at the front door?
No reason.
Is somebody after you?
Why do you always
go to that?
Has anyone ever been after
anyone in this office?
Hey, it just takes one.
Nobody's after me. I just...
I met a woman when
I was giving blood
and I thought
she might come by.
You met a woman when
you were giving blood?
That is so romantic.
It's not a big deal, really.
I just, you know,
met somebody.
We hardly talked.
I picked up her glove
so I was hoping I could
give it back to her.
Oh, my God, that makes it
even more romantic.
This is like
a modern-day Enchanted.
It's like a fairytale.
She could be
your soul mate.
DWIGHT: Not likely.
With three billion
women on the planet,
most of them live
in Asia, so the numbers
just don't add up.
It's possible.
Could be.
Believe me, it's nothing.
I hardly even talked to her.
We just...
We were lying there
next to each other.
I think our
blood bags touched.
Aww!
Here they come.
What?
No. Just kidding.
Seriously though,
that's enough.
Why don't you cover it
with the broccoli?
Great, I have to cover it?
Do you think they
dined and dashed?
They didn't dine so, yeah,
maybe they just dashed.
I thought we were
having a nice time.
We were.
Yeah.
Empty.
Mine too.
(MOANING)
Oh, boy.
Oh, my God.
Okay.
Hi. Is this the party?
Nah.
(ALL SIGH DISAPPOINTEDLY)
Okay then.
So...
Where were we?
Bowling.
Yep, yeah, yep.
You didn't eat
much there, Jim-bo.
Initially I did.
Want some meat?
Sure, a little piece.
No mushroom, though.
I forgot.
Yeah. Thank you.
Hey, I'm sorry we did not
have a chance to talk more.
I get very nervous
talking to pretty girls.
Seriously,
feel how sweaty my hand is.
That's really sweaty.
Are you on e-mail?
Yeah.
Cool. Okay, bye.
Bye, Kevin.
Good Valentine's.
So basically
the greater volume
you decide to buy in,
the greater discount
we can give you.
Okay.
Okay? What's up?
Look, I'm going to go.
Before you go,
I'd just love to get
a firm commitment on this.
You know, maybe sign...
Look, we already
have a paper supplier.
Okay.
Well, thanks for wasting
my time tonight, idiot. God!
Hey. You don't
deserve her.
Thanks, Michael.
Hey, if anybody wants to go...
We can stay a little longer.
Really?
ANGELA: Yeah.
MEREDITH: Yeah. Sure, Michael.
KELLY: Yeah.
No, this is great.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
Thanks.
Michael, it's time.
You know what?
You guys can get out.
I'm going to soldier
on for a little bit.
Come on. We'll all go.
Yeah.
Yeah. Let's go.
Okay.
MICHAEL: Four months ago,
I dated a woman named Holly,
and this is
actually the first time
that I've even considered
getting back into
that arena again.
You know what?
Sometimes it's not about
whether Cinderella
gets her slipper back,
but it's about
the fact that the prince even
picked up the slipper at all.
There's a lot of
princesses out there.
You know, they have
all different sizes
and shapes of
feet and hands,
so I think...
I think my odds
are pretty good.
Pardon me, may I have
a chocolate chip cookie?
I gave blood earlier
and I'm still feeling woozy.
Of course.
That's weird.
You got a cotton ball
and tape and we've
been using Band-Aids.
I feel so woozy, I just...
Using Band-Aids.
Damn.