KEVIN: At least once a year,
I like to bring in
some of my Kevirs
Famous Chili.
The trick is to
undercook the onions.
Everybody is going
to get to know each
other in the pot.
Now, I'm serious
about this stuff.
I'm up the night before,
pressing garlic and
dicing whole tomatoes.
I toast my own
Ancho chilies.
(MOANING)
It's a recipe passed
down from Malones
for generations.
(EXCLAIMING)
It's probably
the thing I do best.
(BOTH CLEARING THROAT)
MICHAEL: Someone
is returning.
He started his own
company, and now
he's back.
Who could it be?
I'll give you a hint.
He is a man.
A man you have missed
with all your heart.
A man who has ruined
all other men for you.
Who is it?
(WHISPERING) Who is it?
(BANGING)
It's Michael Scott.
Hold up!
Conference room,
five minutes.
Well, I guess
the first order
of business
is to welcome back
me and Pam and Ryan.
(PEOPLE CLAPPING)
And how about Casual Friday
again, huh? Reinstituting
Casual Friday?
You all look great.
What I want to do right
now is try something
a little different.
I'm going to throw it
out there, starting
with this meeting.
I want you guys to
run it. I want you to
say whatever you want.
Take it away.
Your meeting.
(STAMMERING)
What are you doing?
If there is something
that you would like
to say as a group,
then by all means,
you may say it
to me right now.
Okay.
MICHAEL: Yes.
People are dressed
inappropriately.
Take it up with Toby.
What I want you to do
is I want you
to look inward,
and I want you to reflect,
and I want you to say
something different.
Can you give us a hint?
MICHAEL: When I needed
salespeople for my new
paper company,
everyone here turned
their back on me.
Am I going to ask them
to beg for forgiveness?
No.
Am I going to ask for
a big, crying apology?
No.
(LAUGHS) Am I going to
ask them to slit their
wrists for me? No.
I just want a tiny,
microscopic version
of that.
Oscar, what were
you going to say?
Nothing. I didn't
say anything.
All right.
Do I still have
a job here?
Not important.
Michael, she's...
Okay.
(ALL MURMURING)
All right,
yes, yes.
She deserves to know.
You have a job.
Frankly, you have
a job because
Ryan and Pam
are starting with us
as salesmen.
Wait, what?
How is that
going to work?
MICHAEL: It's going
to work very smoothly
because Pam and Ryan
are bringing over
a ton of clients
from Michael Scott
Paper Company and...
You mean the clients
you stole from us.
Yeah, aren't we
getting those
clients back?
No, you lost
those clients.
I call foul, sir.
Okay.
DWIGHT: You were bought out.
They...
So the company, then,
bought out all of
the stolen clients.
Okay, Dwight,
let me explain
something to you.
I set the rules,
and you follow
them blindly, okay?
And if you have
a problem with that,
then you can talk to
our complaint department.
It's a trashcan.
Don't fall in
love with me, kid.
(PHYLLIS CHUCKLING)
(CHUCKLES) Boscov's
at the Steamtown Mall?
It sure looked good
on the mannequin.
Well, you have
good taste.
Well, thanks.
I sure wish I had
more time to talk
to my clients, though.
What?
Isn't that what you said
to a bunch of my clients
when you were stealing them?
That I didn't have
enough time for them?
Oh, I, uh...
Close your mouth, sweetie.
You look like a trout.
The man is
wearing sandals.
I don't need to see
Oscar's toes at work.
Gross.
I mean, he looks like
he just got off the boat.
Can't you just not
look at his feet?
Excuse me?
Oh! You're so educated,
aren't you, Toby?
So trained to deal
with a hysterical woman!
I don't want to
look at his feet!
Do your job!
TOBY: Well, I was in
the seminary for a year
and dropped out
'cause I wanted to have sex
with this girl Kathy.
Followed her
back to Scranton,
took the first job
I could find in HR.
Later, she divorced me.
So, no, I wouldn't say
I have a passion for HR.
There you are,
my friend.
Oh. Thanks, man.
(CAN OPENING)
Pamela.
Thanks, Michael.
Yep.
Fresh, hot ink.
STANLEY: New file system?
Trust me, Stanley, you're
going to want to read
this memo very carefully.
I am not changing
the way I do my files.
No, no! This goes
for all of you.
Believe me, you are
going to want to heat
my words.
When held over heat,
the invisible ink
will reveal
that everyone should meet
at the warehouse immediately.
Do not ask me where
I got the invisible ink.
Urine. It was urine.
(CHUCKLES)
(SIGHING)
I'm sorry you're
offended by my shoes,
but I'm not going to
drive home to change.
Okay. I could loan
you a pair of socks.
No.
No, they're clean.
I was gonna wear them
to volleyball practice.
I don't think so.
(PHONE RINGING)
Andrew Bernard.
Okay, what are you
still doing at your desk?
What are you still
doing not at your desk?
Did you even
read the memo?
All my files are
now in reverse
alphabetical order...
No, you idiot!
There is a code
embedded in the memo.
Listen, you need to round up
all the salesmen,
except for Ryan and Pam,
and get them down
to the warehouse,
pronto.
Oh, it is on,
like a prawn who
yawns at dawn.
Stop doing
rhyming poetry.
Just tell them, please.
God, the simplest thing.
We're in crisis
mode here.
Do you understand
that two unqualified
so-called salespeople
are being favored
because they all
failed together?
And frankly,
I'm not convinced
that Michael and Pam
didn't have a thing going
while they were gone.
Can I address that?
No, you're too close.
Okay.
Stanley, how do you
feel about those two
taking your clients?
It's not right.
I don't like it.
He doesn't like it.
You don't take my clients
away and give them to
a secretary.
(SIGHING)
No offense, Jim.
I think she's very pretty.
Her face is okay,
but...
Jeez, what...
What are you
doing here?
I don't know. I saw
a crowd. Thought there
might be a dog fight or...
Get out!
We need to
do something.
I'm thinking maybe a coup,
or we take Ryan hostage.
Those sound too harsh.
No, I'm not saying
we do those things.
I'm saying something
like those things.
Of course.
What is like a hostage?
Excellent question.
We could write
a strongly worded
letter.
Words will never
be enough.
Strongly painted picture.
No, pictures are
too interpretive.
Can I just say something?
I know that tempers are high.
But I think the best
way to handle this
might be to just talk
to Michael directly.
Oh.
That...
That's a great
idea, Jim.
I totally see
your point.
Okay, we'll talk to
Michael directly, so, uh,
meeting is over, I guess.
I'll see everyone upstairs.
Great. See you upstairs.
Come on.
(WHISPERING) Listen,
now is the time for
action. I'm talking...
(LAUGHING)
That one's great.
I know.
PAM: Why are you so mad?
RYAN: You look so classy.
MICHAEL: I do? Well...
(PAM LAUGHING)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Where is that bowl?
Hi, you have a second?
Michael Scott
Paper Company only.
Yeah, I think you're
gonna wanna cool it
with that,
'cause it's starting to
upset the other salesmen.
Okay, well...
Tough.
I will... No. No.
I'll talk to them
when they all get back
from the bathroom.
This is awkward to talk
about, but there
may or may not be,
but definitely is,
a mutiny forming in
the warehouse right now.
Against who?
You.
Us.
What?
It's gotta be
because they all
want their clients...
The old Michael Scott
might have taken this,
but not the new
Michael Scott.
They are in for a bitter
surprise. I am not to be
truffled with.
Six weeks ago,
none of these people
wanted to come with me.
You two were the only ones
with the stones to follow.
Mmm-hmm.
That was us,
right there.
PAM: We were something else.
What you gotta do is
you gotta go down
to that warehouse
and you gotta crack some
skulls, Chiklis style.
MICHAEL: Mmm-hmm.
Yeah, The Commish.
Yes, but Chiklis
Shield style...
Okay.
...not Commish style.
Yeah, yeah. The Shield.
It's crazy, what's going
on out there today, huh?
(CHUCKLES)
I know. Yeah,
it's kinda...
Sometimes it's best
just to stay out of it.
That's true.
That's right, yeah.
Want to play a game?
Hey, gang,
where you been?
Lunch.
Where'd you eat?
A restaurant.
What did you
have, Stanley?
I had a salmon salad
with water, no ice.
I was going to get
a soda, but the waitress
talked me out of it.
Her name was Flo.
She had black hair.
I had Mexican food.
So since you
guys already ate,
you won't be eating the stuff
that you brought with you for
lunch, will you?
(EXCLAIMING)
Wow, Stanley,
is that egg salad?
Andy brought
some salmon.
RYAN: That looks great.
Dwight, is that
a meat sandwich?
You guys hungry?
I can eat.
I'm going to have
some of this
meat sandwich.
It's pony.
Mmm!
What kind of sauce
is on your salmon?
(EXCLAIMING)
ANDY: Dijonnaise.
MICHAEL: Thanks for
going out, guys.
PAM: Mmm-hmm.
Hey, Meredith, can
I talk to you privately
for a second?
About what?
Your outfit.
What? What's wrong
with my outfit?
(STAMMERING) You might
consider pulling it
down a touch.
It's riding up
a little high.
Bunch of prudes.
You know, Oscar's
allowed to wear sandals,
(ALL GASPING)
But I'm not allowed to
wear open-toed shoes?
Is that how it goes?
Meredith, your boob is out.
Fine.
(ALL GROANING)
Too far, Meredith!
Too far!
Damn it, Meredith,
where are your
panties?
It's casual day.
Happy?
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
KELLY: Toby.
PAM: Toby.
(ANGELA EXCLAIMING)
OSCAR: Toby?
No. If you do that,
I'm going to do that.
If you do that,
If you do this,
I'm going to do that.
What if I just do this?
You don't want
to do that.
I'm just hiding out
until all this
stuff blows over,
with Creed, playing
chess, at work.
He's winning.
I feel like
I'm describing
a dream I had.
RYAN: I'm sorry you feel
that way, Mr. Bart.
Is there anything I can do
to make things better?
(EXCLAIMING)
Give me the phone.
Exactly, if this is your
first complaint in 10 years...
That's my client.
...things have
been generally good.
Give me the phone.
Tell him Dwight Schrute
wants to talk to him.
Look, Mr. Bart...
DWIGHT: Hi, Mr. Bart!
...at these prices,
with this service...
Hey, it's Dwight here!
...you're not
going to find this
anywhere else.
Dwight Schrute here.
Hey, don't hang up,
Mr. Bart.
No, sir, don't listen...
Listen, I know times
are tough right now,
and I laud your thriftiness.
Look, let me...
Ryan, hand
the phone over!
Stop flustering me,
everybody!
(DWIGHT GRUNTING)
Who let this boy
on the phone?
Mr. Bart!
(GRUNTS)
I cannot believe
you lost that account!
He was my client
for 10 years!
You made him lose
the account by screaming
at him the entire time!
It's okay, Ryan.
You're a secretary!
What do you know?
And you're a temp!
And I'm taking your phone.
I'm confiscating this!
Hey, guys...
You know what I want
you to do? Shake hands,
get over it.
That was not
a shake, Dwight.
We want our clients back
or we quit, Michael.
Who quits?
Me.
And me.
Me, too.
You guys gotta be kidding.
No, we gotta be
deadly serious.
We'll start our
own paper company.
The Schrute-Bernard-Lapin-
Vance-Stanley Paper Company.
I love it!
I love this idea,
and I fully support you.
As a matter of fact,
I'm going to give
you some seed money.
There you go.
There's some
seed money for you.
And you can take it,
no hard feelings,
but if you stay,
I want an apology,
and I want a big one.
You want us to
apologize to you?
Yes, I do.
That's completely backwards.
It's frontwards!
Michael, you thought
you were attacking
Corporate,
but we were the
ones who got hurt.
You should be
apologizing to us.
ALL: That's right.
Michael, you always
said we were a family.
Then you went after us.
No matter how I look at
this, I am in the wrong.
And I have looked
at this thing like
100 different ways,
from my point of view,
from their point of view,
98 others, and bottom
line, I am in the wrong.
I'm the bad guy.
I need you
to arrange a meeting
between me and
the sales staff
without Ryan
and Pam knowing.
Gasp.
Are you talking
about a secret meeting?
(WHISPERING)
Whatever you guys
did earlier.
I don't know
the first thing about
secret meetings.
Just do it, okay?
Get them there.
I'll do the best
I can, Michael.
Are you kidding me?
Deceit does not
come easy to me.
Okay, okay, okay.
I really love
your outfit.
Thank you so much
for saying that.
I can't believe
that Toby thinks
this is inappropriate.
You look like J-Lo.
So, from the bottom
of my heart
to the top of
my heart, I am sorry.
Are you giving us
our clients back?
If we could just focus
and go down the line,
and everyone would say,
"Apology accepted,"
I think we would
all feel better,
and then we can break
out my gift to you,
complimentary
white chocolate bark.
Nobody likes that stuff,
except for you.
They wouldn't make it
unless people liked it.
Michael, just give
us our clients back.
That's all we care about.
Okay, if I give you
your clients back,
there won't be enough
clients for Pam and Ryan,
and I promised both of
them that they were
going to be salespeople.
So?
Fine, have your clients.
I can see that's what
you wanted all along.
ALL: Okay.
MICHAEL: However,
I rescind my apology.
ANDY: That's fair.
STANLEY: Absolutely.
You are not reacting
at all as I had hoped.
(MACHINE WHIRRING)
What did I tell you
about building forts
in my warehouse?
RYAN: Michael gave all
of our clients back to
their old salespeople.
So now there's not enough
for both me and Pam
to stay on.
PAM: He can only
keep one of us as
a salesperson now.
He'll make his decision
by the end of the day.
I think you
should get it.
You really
grew into it.
Oh.
I think you
should get it.
You've changed a lot,
and you'd be good at it.
If you really think
that, will you tell
that to Michael?
That would go a long
way, coming from you.
Yeah.
Thanks.
So, hey, I want to set
you up with my daughter.
Oh, I'm engaged to Pam.
I thought you were gay.
(CLICKS TONGUE) Then why
would you want to set me
up with your daughter?
I don't know.
Jim, could I talk
to you for a minute?
Sure, let me just
finish this turn.
And Bingo was
his name-o.
Let's go.
Challenge.
I need your help.
This whole Pam-Ryan debate
is screwing with my head.
Well, I don't want to be
biased, but I am very close
to Ryan. You know that.
You're close
with Pam, too.
Oh. She's nice,
I guess.
You know what?
Best thing to do,
pros and cons list.
Pro for Ryan, he went
to business school.
He's my number-one choice.
Well, that's...
I like his hair.
Cons, Ryan, he
defrauded the company.
He has never
made a sale.
Okay.
He definitely
stole my iPod.
That sounds pretty biased.
You didn't
hear my pros.
Environmentally conscious,
'cause his mom drives him
to work every day.
Okay. Pam, pros,
I like her.
Mmm-hmm.
I think that she
is a fast learner.
Cons, she doesn't
always follow through.
New York and the whole
art school thing.
And Roy.
She has a weird voice.
That's not true.
I don't need to
tell you that.
I think she'd be
a really good
salesperson.
I don't think you're being
totally impartial, though,
because you haven't said
one bad thing about Pam.
And I won't.
Okay.
So be it. Then you've
lost credibility,
and I'm going to
go with my gut,
and that's Ryan.
Okay.
You're right. Sometimes,
when she is tired,
she can be
a little bit shrill,
but that's not
a weird voice,
that's just...
(EXCLAIMING)
(LAUGHING)
Take it easy.
Oh. Man! Wow!
(SHRILLY) "Honey!
"I want you to
put the garbage out!
"'Cause I'm not gonna
have sex with you
"unless you bring
out the garbage!"
I have a very difficult
decision to make.
It's like last week
I was at the video store.
Do I rent Devil
Wears Prada again
or do I finally get
around to seeing
Sophie's Choice?
It is what you
would call a classic
difficult decision.
You don't understand
clothing, Toby!
You're dressed like
this amorphous blob
of khaki.
All right, look,
what you've got
to understand is
when you come to work,
(PEOPLE GRUMBLING)
You give up
certain rights.
Listen up, Flenderson,
you're being weak
and ineffectual.
I'm cowboying
this meeting, okay?
Here are the new rules,
okay? Earth tones only.
Also, women are
forbidden to
wear pants.
All right, come on,
sit down, Dwight.
No.
I'm running
this meeting.
That's debatable.
It's not.
Listen...
It's not. Sit down,
or I'm writing you up.
Hmm. Where's
this guy been?
Casual Fridays
are canceled.
What?
Let's just not
do it anymore.
That's not a solution.
No, it is a solution.
You're running
from the problem.
(ALL CLAMORING)
There's not a single
appropriate outfit
in this whole...
Except mine,
quite honestly.
Pam, could you
come in here, please?
Have a seat.
Okay.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Well, there's no
easy way of saying this,
so I think I will
just drag it out.
Since the dawn of time,
there have been...
Just tell me.
I gave Ryan
the sales job.
There just werert
enough clients for
the two of you.
So I had to...
I'm sorry. Sorry.
No, okay, okay,
I get it, yeah.
(LAUGHS)
Why are you giggling?
(LAUGHING)
Is this a joke?
Michael, is this...
Did I get the job?
Yes.
I did?
Yep.
For real? You're not
kidding? I did?
No, you're the best
person for the job.
You're going to be great.
Oh, Michael, thank you!
Okay.
Thank you. Thank you.
You will not be sorry.
You should have seen
your face. Oh. Man!
That was classic.
(LAUGHING)
I really thought
I didn't get it.
Oh. Really?
Yeah.
Man.
That was really good.
'Cause you said I didn't.
What about Ryan?
I don't know.
I offered him
his temp job back.
We'll see.
He was not happy at all
when I offered him this job,
and then I told him
that he didn't
get the job, so...
Yeah, maybe you shouldn't
fake-fire people anymore.
I don't appreciate you
telling me what to do,
so clean out your desk.
You are through.
Thanks, Michael.
Oh.
What's our
receptionist's name?
Erin.
Could you send her in?
Erin, Michael
wants to see you.
(EXCLAIMING)
Hello.
Hi.
Have a seat.
This is very
difficult to say.
But no one here likes
you in the office,
and we're going to
have to let you go.
Hank, would you come
up here, please? Hank
is our security guard.
Oh. I can go...
He will be
ushering you out.
(LAUGHING)
Oh.
Oh, your face.
Oh!
Is... Do the people...
No, I'm kidding.
You're not fired. Yet.
(LAUGHING)
Do they not
like me, though?
I don't know,
actually.
Okay.