Oh, my God.
I can't believe it.
I just won
an art contest.
(ERIN EXCLAIMING IN DELIGHT)
(LAUGHING)
(WHISPERING) Thanks.
I still don't
understand why you
wanted me to say that.
DWIGHT: Shut up.
(LAUGHING)
I got her.
(GRUNTS)
(LAUGHS)
Not cool, Dwight.
JIM: Not cool, man.
(CONTINUES LAUGHING)
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
(LAUGHING) Oh, no.
I still have the
lease on the Michael
Scott Paper Company,
so occasionally, I will
sneak down here for a
little coffee and dancing.
I actually dance
all the time.
MICHAEL: Tip-toeing
around corporate,
it is a ballet.
When I am breaking
all the rules,
I'm break dancing.
And espresso.
Guys, I'm scared.
I'm really scared.
I think I'm
growing into
a giant,
because look at
this normal-sized
coffee cup.
Looks so tiny in
my giant hand now.
Anybody want to
go to lunch with
me later on?
I do.
Okay, how about
a woman? Pam?
I can't do lunch.
I was just sending
you an e-mail.
Jim and I need to leave
early today to meet
with our contractor.
Really? Okay.
Just sent it.
What about
the rest of you?
At Dunder Mifflin,
there is a very strict
no-lunch-with-the-boss
policy,
and I don't know
who instituted it.
I think it started right
after my predecessor
stepped down.
But at the
Michael Scott
Paper Company,
I really enjoyed
having lunch with Pam
and Ryan every day.
So, rules be damned,
I want to have lunch
with these people.
Who else?
Who else? Ryan?
I don't do lunch.
I'm doing five small
meals a day now.
Now that I'm back
to doing the job
of a temp again,
I find that food
is one thing
I can control.
Okay, anyone?
Anyone at all?
Accounting, I am
a-counting on you to
go to lunch with me.
No, I don't want to
stay late to have a
two-hour lunch.
Michael, we have
a lot of work to do.
What?
Work.
(GROANS)
God. What happened
to you people?
(IN ROBOTIC VOICE) "We are
just office drones.
"We are office drones.
All we do is work. Is work."
If you don't take out
his battery, he just
keeps going all day.
Oh, no, your
battery fell out.
"I was just
learning to love."
ERIN: Hi, guys.
How are you doing?
Erin, how many times
do I have to tell you?
It is not necessary
for you to ask us
how we are doing
every time you
interact with us.
You're right.
I'm sorry.
(SIGHS)
Now, how can I help you?
Did somebody here leave
a map in the printer to
Youngstown, Ohio?
Attention, office.
Who here is planning a
trip to Youngstown, Ohio?
I will take your silence
to mean that you are
all hiding something.
This location is
the superior court...
So someone's going
to a court. Big deal.
It is a big deal,
'cause there's only
a handful of reasons
why someone
would ever go to a
courthouse in Ohio
and not be
charged with
a crime.
Claim an ineritance
from a deceased relative,
to obtain a learner's
permit at age 141l2
instead of 15.
Erin, let me see
your birth certificate.
Sure.
JIM: There are other
reasons to go to Ohio.
We're getting
married today.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
So, it turns out
it's the closest place
to get a marriage license
without a three-day
waiting period.
Tell them how it happened.
Okay, so we're
going through all
the wedding plans,
and, boy,
it is complicated.
And very expensive.
Very expensive.
'Cause you say you
want a small wedding
and that's great,
but then you have to...
You can't leave
anyone out.
No one.
Okay, just get
to the good part.
Right, so, this
morning, we are having
breakfast together...
Mmm-hmm.
...and I just looked
up from my cereal
and I said,
"You know what I
want to do today?
I want to marry you."
I had just woken up.
I didn't look cute.
That's how I
knew he meant it.
(KNOCKING AT DOOR)
(NEW WAVE MUSIC PLAYING)
Michael?
Michael, sorry to bother
you. Are you going to be
working down here?
Do you want
these down here...
No work! No work! No work!
I come here to
release frustration.
(EXCLAIMING)
Well, I like to swim.
That's good.
You've got a
cool place to come.
If you ever want
to come down here,
door's always open.
Lock's broken, so...
Thank you.
Give me your hand.
Hey, here we go,
here we go. Yeah.
There we go.
Now you got it.
Now I do got it.
Hey, you want
some espresso?
Yeah.
Gotta keep
yourself dehydrated.
That's rule
number one.
Okay.
I love it.
Guys, I believe
that I have figured out
what is up your butts.
There's no reason
to be scared.
The bad man is gone.
Charles is gone.
Charles really did
a number on these guys.
They are way too
focused on work.
When I was in charge,
this place was like
Dave & Buster's,
people just hanging out,
having fun, eating apps.
I don't know,
it's like Dave
died or something.
Daddy's here,
and Daddy is going
to take care of you.
Please don't refer to
yourself as our daddy.
I am your big daddy,
and I am going to
kiss the boo-boo.
(CHILDISHLY) Little
Andy is afraid.
Andy's afraid?
Yes.
Are you all afraid?
No.
Daddy's here
for you, my
little angels.
Okay,
I think that I have
figured a way to get you
guys out of your funk.
What?
Funk is the problem,
and the solution.
That makes sense.
I have taken my
downstairs office
and I have turned it
into a place to hang out,
a place where unattractive
and attractive people
can get together,
to meet, to greet,
to see the ones
that you love,
to love the ones
that you see.
Is this our punishment
for not wanting to
have lunch with you?
Why don't you get
over lunch, Oscar?
Everybody else is past it.
All work and no play
makes Michael a dull boy.
This is like a
haunted coffee
house thing?
No, Dwight is confusing you.
It's more of a disco.
It's like a haunted disco.
With coffee,
but without
the haunting.
It's a combo dance
house-coffee bar.
It is a daytime
disco on the
ground floor
of an industrial
office building.
It's a Cafe Disco.
Exactly.
Like a disco-cafe.
What? No. No.
Not even close.
I can't force you
to go down, but I
can entice you.
I'm going to
be down there.
Erin will be
down there from
time to time,
and all-you-can-eat espresso.
Well, Kevin, I guess
it is just me and you.
Yeah.
Holding down the fort.
This place
is great.
Thank you.
Oh, my God, Kevin,
I am still on hold.
You were supposed
to get the answer
from Michael
and come back up.
This is a no-work zone.
Please respect the lei.
Yeah, respect the lei.
Come.
Kevin, stay.
Kevin, come.
Stay, stay.
Come on, right now.
Cookie, Kevin. Cookie.
(LAUGHS) There is
no cookie, Kevin.
Is there a cookie?
Mmm-hmm.
Come on.
For goodness
sakes, Kevin,
there's no cookie.
There's no cookie.
Come on. Come.
I wanted a cookie.
Completely unacceptable.
Now I know what the founders
of Philip Morris felt like.
You just want to
give people a smooth,
fun way to relax,
and suddenly,
you're just some
terrible monster.
Here we go.
(DANCE MUSIC BLARING)
(EXCLAIMS)
(LAUGHING)
What the hell!
Hi, Jessica,
is Bob in?
He's on a call.
Well, I'll just
duck my head in.
It's pretty important.
He wouldn't want to
be disturbed.
Can I give him
a message before
he gets off?
Tell him I'm going
dancing downstairs
in the storage closet
between the bathrooms
that used to be a
utility shower, and he
should join me there.
I'll let him know.
Mmm-hmm.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
Phyllis?
Hi.
Hey.
Hey,
I like.
(CHUCKLING)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
All right.
Back... There you go.
There you go. You got it.
(EXCLAIMING)
Show me some attitude.
(LAUGHING)
(GASPS)
Mother (BLEEP).
God. No, no, no.
Back.
Wow, what did you do?
(LAUGHING)
You didn't do that.
You're okay.
Let's lie down.
Give me... You want
to go down? All right.
(EXCLAIMING) Sorry.
(GROANING)
Okay, that's okay.
Backs are a problem.
Okay, sweetie...
Right here.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
I got your text.
Who's Phillip?
No, no, no.
Who tipped you over?
Was it Phillip?
It's my back.
It's her back.
We just... We need...
God, call a doctor.
You know what?
We're going to
take care of you.
get you help.
Come on, come on.
Call Bob.
No, no, no,
this is no good.
Yeah, back
injuries are common.
Not as common
as knee injuries,
but more common
than wrist injuries.
I don't need a
history lesson, okay?
What do you
think history is?
Just... We need to
get her out of there
because no one
is going to want
to go in there
with a woman writhing
around on the floor.
Wait, wait, wait,
but most importantly,
we need to get her
some medical attention
ASAP, stat.
(EXCLAIMING) Here we go.
Here we go.
Ramming speed.
Okay, out of the way.
Move it or lose it.
Oh, my God,
what happened?
MICHAEL: You having fun
taking a little ride?
Just having
too much fun.
Phyllis, we're gonna
put you in here. Dwight's
gonna take care of you.
What? No, I thought
we were going to
the hospital.
DWIGHT: If you want
to get sick, you go
to a hospital.
Okay, Dwight.
Okay, good.
I do not want
anybody to worry.
What happened
to Phyllis?
(SIGHING) You know,
nothing. She's...
We were hanging
out at Cafe Disco
and she had
a flare-up of an
existing injury,
but she's a
tough old bird, so...
Can you please
go back to work
instead of
masterminding
these situations
wherein we
hurt ourselves?
Okay, fine.
Phyllis did
injure herself,
but she injured
herself having fun,
and I don't think
she would trade that
memory for anything.
(PHYLLIS SCREAMING)
I would like the
memory of a day
uninterrupted
by this nonsense.
You all took a
life here today.
You did.
The life of the party.
Erin, I want you
to go downstairs,
and I want you
to shut it down.
You mean unplug
the coffee machine
and bring it up here?
I don't care. Bury it.
I hope you're happy.
(PANTING) Okay.
I'm going to need
two able-bodied men.
Cafe Disco?
More like
crappy disco.
You're bad.
(DANCE MUSIC STARTS PLAYING)
There's girls
in there.
Where?
The other room.
What other room?
Down the hall.
There's girls there?
What did I just say?
You bring my sandwich?
Forget the sandwich.
Girls. Girls.
I guess they got
what they want.
I am eating alone.
Might as well be dinner.
Comfy? All right,
all right. Just relax,
relax, okay?
Dwight. Dwight.
Come on, relax.
This shirt wasrt
doing you any favors.
If my assessment
is correct, you
grind your teeth?
I do.
No kidding.
She sits three feet from me.
It's the most annoying thing.
(GRUNTING)
It's like children
singing Christmas carols.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
Yeah. I'm loving
the vibe down here.
Ashley. You made it.
You invited someone?
Oh. Yeah. Was I not
allowed to do that?
I don't know.
I've been here eight
years, and I've never...
Rude.
I'm not sure,
but I'm pretty sure
I'm in a dance-off.
Cafe Disco is dead,
but I can still hear
the music in my head.
I hear it, too, boss.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING)
It's better
than I imagined it.
It feels good, Dwight.
Tell me where it hurts.
Right... Right there.
Yeah, you've got
a knot in your crest.
DWIGHT: This remedy has
been passed down in
my family for generations,
and it always works.
My grandfather was told
that Diamond Dancer
would never race again.
They were wrong.
He came in ninth in
the Apple Creek Derby.
And his jerky
came in third
the following year.
A majestic beast.
So fast, so tender.
Welcome, welcome.
Cafe Disco. I am
Michael Scott.
Hey, Angela,
welcome to Cafe...
Stop!
Angela, Angela, Angela,
may I interest you
in a triple espresso,
or perhaps a dance?
No, I didn't come
down here to get
wet and wild.
I just need you
to sign these.
All right.
Here you go.
And, no, you need
to sign them all.
No, no, no.
Here is the deal.
One signature
for every song.
Look, I hate to
be "that" person,
but I just don't
like the general
spirit of music.
I know, I know. Angela,
a lot of people doubted
Cafe Disco at first,
but it is a magical
place. You have to
give it a chance.
If these walls
could talk,
they would say,
"This is a magical place.
You're safe here.
"We are talking walls.
We're not going to eat you."
No.
This is oil from
the gland of an otter.
It keeps their
fur water resistant,
as well as traps heat.
Now, I need you to
lie still for an hour.
An hour?
I can't stay
here an hour.
Whoa, whoa, girl.
Whoa. Whoa.
Boss, this used to
hang from my windshield,
but it belongs in here.
Hey, thank you, Creed.
You really get this place.
No problem.
I'll just have no idea
who's driving behind me now.
Look out.
(EXCLAIMING)
Yeah!
Yeah.
Finish it off.
Oh, no! Oh, no!
Here we go.
Okay, something's
gonna happen.
(ALL CHEERING)
MICHAEL: Here we go. Yeah.
(EXCLAIMING)
I'm going to go
with the python.
But the rattler's so scary.
No, please, I find
the rattle soothing.
Puts me to sleep.
I think Bob's
going to cheat on me
with his new secretary.
(LAUGHING)
What's so funny?
When I say
it out loud,
it's so silly.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Hey, hey, Angela, no.
No cleaning up.
You are forcing me
to be down here.
Am I not allowed
to have some fun?
No cleaning up.
These are for you.
They're beautiful.
You ready?
Yeah.
(MUSIC PLAYING IN DISTANCE)
We should probably
stop by. It would
mean a lot to him.
Hey. Hey. Man,
Jim and Pam.
Can you believe this?
It's really happening.
Want to dance, Dwight?
Ordinarily,
I would say no,
but you need to
move to reduce
lactic acid buildup.
Also, this song
is fantastic.
Mind if I steal my wife?
You can't steal
what is legally
your property.
Are those staples?
This dance
competition
is not over.
What dance competition?
I was just dancing casually
with my friend, y'all.
(LAUGHING) Yeah, right.
(DISCO MUSIC PLAYING)
You guys are the
best for coming.
You don't have to stay
if you don't want to.
I understand.
JIM: We're going to stay.
Really?
At least for
one more dance.
No, not me.
Not me. Get out
of here. Cafe Disco.
Hey, come on, man.
We're not even to "Y."
This is so cheesy.
Yes.
I like cheesy.
Me, too.
You know,
I think maybe I want
a wedding wedding.
Me, too.
Really?
Yeah.
Would you like
to dance?
No.
ANDY: Yeah. No,
well, okay...
KELLY: Stop squirming.
Well, stop trying
to poke me with
a sharp thing.
You wanted to
do this, okay?
Just be brave.
I know, but you're
not a professional,
and I'm thinking
maybe we should
have gone that route.
I'm doing...
No, I'm doing
it for free.
Just... You have
to stop squirming,
otherwise, I'm
going to mess up.
Are you sure
that's not the
gay ear?
Gay ear?
Are you 12 years old?
Well, I...
Look, I'm going to
count to three.
Count to 20.
No, I'm going to
count to three.
One, two, three.
(SCREAMING) Son of a bitch!
Andy, that was
just the ice.
It was?
Yeah, it was.