- You wanted to see me?
- Yes, Oscar, come on in.
Close the door, if you would.
Thanks so much for talking to me.
Yeah, sure.
I'm going in for a procedure today.
Is everything okay?
It's routine.
I'm just a little bit scared.
I'm sure everything will be fine.
What's the procedure,
if you don't mind my asking?
It is a colonoscopy.
In your experience,
what should I be expecting
in terms of sensation...
or emotions?
Is there anything
I can do to make it more pleasurable
for me or for Dr. Chaudry?
My main concern is
should I have a safe word?
The Office 6x02
- The Meeting -
You think you can get me a rundown
on the Buffalo clients by Monday?
You know what?
I'll do you one better.
Sunday, Sunday night.
Okay, I will get it Monday.
Hold on, big guy.
I'm gonna put it in the mail Sunday.
You'll get it Wednesday.
Jim, you want to hit
the conference room?
Good luck.
Right, this thing.
I remember now.
- What's this about?
- This is me and David, if it's okay.
That's okay with me,
he's gonna want me in.
It's okay. We got it.
Really?
Do you mind if I sit this out?
I have so much work,
I'm gonna blow my brains out.
Am I worried that Jim and David
are having a meeting without me?
Because we are
the Three Amigos.
And once in a while,
one of the amigos will go off
to the bathroom while the other two
have a secret meeting.
Let me escort you to your desk.
It's just...
three or four steps, but thank you.
You and Jim are close, huh?
I think the pregnancy
really brought us together.
What do you think
he and David are talking about?
- I don't know.
- You said good luck to Jim.
Did I?
Doesn't sound like me.
I'm not very superstitious.
If you're lying to me right now,
your baby is gonna come out a liar.
That's how it works.
They inherit things
through the breast milk.
Please don't talk
about my breast milk.
I just don't want you to lie to me.
I don't want you to ever lie to me.
Have I ever lied to you?
I just don't want you to.
I was rushing to fill an order.
I put the ladder up to grab
a box of three-hole from the top shelf.
Next thing I know, I'm on the ground,
ladder's on top of me.
And that's how you broke your ankle?
Interesting.
How did the ladder
end up on top of you
if you fell off of it?
This doesn't concern you.
You need to walk away.
Really? I'm sorry.
I thought this was a free country.
I didn't know
we were in communist Sweden.
If we were, I wouldn't have to worry,
'cause we'd have universal health care.
- Be quiet.
- I'm talking...
I will send this off to corporate,
hold on to your medical bills.
Feel better.
Thanks, T-man.
Later.
So long, Darryl.
Feel better.
He's lying.
He has a doctor's note.
From who, Dr. J?
You really need to investigate this.
People don't just fall off
of ladders.
Guy on my street fell off
painting his house. It was on the news.
Since when have you known Darryl
to rush to do anything
other than to come up here
for birthday cake?
"Y'all having birthday cake?"
That's not a very good Darryl.
How many foremen do you know
that pull boxes?
It just doesn't add up.
We did a little investigation,
and Dwight had a good point.
The ladder didn't reach
the top shelf.
I don't know if I believe it, but...
I am a fan
of the hardboiled detective novel.
"I'll punch you into mush, see?"
Well, if he doesn't like it,
you can tell that S.O.B.
that he is fired.
Sorry, I'm going into a meeting.
I will... I love you too. Bye.
- Who was that?
- Sorry about that. What'd I miss?
We would like to continue
this meeting in private,
- please, if you don't mind.
- I do not mind.
Yes, I do. No, I don't.
Yes, I do.
No, I don't.
Catch you on the flippity-flop.
This...
call waiting.
You tell the mayor
he just lost six votes.
They've been in there a while.
Can't be good.
Think they're talking about me?
No, I think
they're talking about me.
That makes way more sense.
Okay, thanks, boss.
What is Jim telling him?
That I can't handle this job?
That is bull crap.
Although it has been chaotic lately.
Corporate shut down
the Buffalo branch,
which left us to absorb
all of their clients.
I will tell you,
there has been work
every day.
Had to come in on a Saturday...
to retrieve...
I left my cell phone here.
So jealous of your boobs.
I just wanted to confirm
that you're not coming to the wedding,
which is totally understandable,
and more than fine.
Is Ryan going?
I don't know, he hasn't RSVPed yet.
We invited everyone in the office
to our wedding,
even though we realized most people
wouldn't be able to make the drive
to Niagara Falls.
Which is why we're having it
in Niagara Falls.
Then Michael
told everyone they could have
Friday and Monday off
if they came.
So now people have to decide
if they want to come to our wedding
or have to work.
Here's the deal.
I really want to go.
But I'm not gonna go if Ryan doesn't go,
because it's kind of a waste of time.
That came out wrong.
It'd be awesome if you get him to go,
I'd really like to be there for Jim.
What can I do for you, hoss?
- How are your sales doing?
- How are my sales doing?
Busted.
My numbers are down.
A little bit.
It's 'cause of the economy.
You're not buying it.
You're good.
Okay, the truth is...
I have been having trouble
focusing lately. I'm in this weird,
flirty,
nebulous
thing
with this cousin of mine.
And it's a total mind f'er.
Again with the cousin.
I'm sorry, Phyllis.
You explain this email, okay?
"Hey, Andy, let's go visit grandma
"and then get drunk together."
I'm just trying to figure out
what's going on in that room.
Wallace had to show up
on the one four-month period
that I'm completely overwhelmed.
You know when they say
it's so crazy it just might work?
I don't believe that.
I say go for the airtight plan.
And that is why I am having Andy
wheel me into the conference room
inside a makeshift cheese cart.
It is
just...
elegant.
- Be my eyes.
- You got it.
What have we here?
Just backing up and turning around.
We're gonna do this...
That's not for you.
Pardonnez-moi, monsieur.
I took the liberty
of preparing for you
a cheese platter, which I will
place here on the eastern wall
of the conference room.
- Cheese platter?
- Oui, oui, monsieur.
From the Wisconsin region,
a nice, firm cheddar.
Also from the great city
of Wisconsin,
an aged parmesan.
Here you will find
a cheddar-style spread,
which has reacted nicely
with the air
to form a light rind,
which I think you'll find
both challenging and delicious.
At that point,
I would recommend you take
a quick trip south of the border
to the great state of Illinois,
where you will find
this fine blue cheese dressing.
If I may be so bold,
it's a lot of fun
to let the goldfish
take a little swim
in the blue cheese.
Bon appétit.
I should go.
Thanks for this.
You've given me a lot to think about.
Promise me you won't do anything
until we speak.
I won't.
- Thanks for taking the time.
- Appreciate it. Thank you, Jim.
- Erin, is Michael around?
- I think... he's around here.
You must have walked right past me.
How you doing?
- Could we talk in your office?
- Yes, definitely.
It sounds like a...
EMD P40.
That's a GE.
The P40 is much higher pitched.
- You're into trains?
- I've been my whole life.
I'm rebuilding a turn-of-the-century
steam engine in my slaughterhouse.
That's so cool.
I'd love to take a look.
It's just a slaughterhouse,
but, sure, any time.
You know, 'cause of the trains.
- Someone's coming.
- Boy.
It's Darryl! Get down!
He's not using crutches!
Get the camera. Start taping.
- Drive!
- Worker's comp my ass!
I can't believe this.
You asshole!
You gonna eat
all that dog food yourself?
Man! You OK?
I just wanted to confirm
that you're not coming to my wedding.
Yeah, I might stop by.
It costs about $75 per person.
I once had a glass of cognac
that cost $77, so...
Can you just tell me now
if you're coming or not?
I'm coming.
- Ryan Howard yes?
- Probably yes.
Kelly Kapoor yes.
Are you sure you're okay
with these new responsibilities?
- Look who you're talking to.
- Just trying to figure out
the best way
to utilize everyone's talents.
I would say that my greatest talent
is being the best man,
woman or child
- to have ever run this branch.
- And what about Jim?
You think Jim is ready to move
into a management position?
- Permission to speak on the record.
- Please, do.
Jim is like...
Big Bird.
He is tall
and yellow
and very nice.
But when I put him in charge, no.
I don't think so.
Big Bird doesn't make
the tough decisions.
If I was going
to put someone in charge,
I would put Bert in charge.
Or I would put
one of the real grown-ups, like Maria.
- Or Gordon, maybe.
- I thought you liked Jim.
Very much.
Jim is my best friend.
But...
Here's his performance report.
Right here.
Now, this was written by Toby.
Who we all know is extremely...
reliable.
"Constant office distraction.
"Spends way too much time
at reception.
"Antagonizes other salesmen.
Not at all what he thinks he is."
It's not very well written.
But you get the gist.
Is there anybody else
could run the day-to-day of the branch?
I could continue to run it myself,
that's...
Jim had an interesting idea
to help you
with this extra workload.
And it involved
you being promoted to oversee.
All Northeast sales.
And then Jim would be promoted
to your position.
This was Jim's idea?
I'd have to talk to my mother
and my guy at H&R block.
Here's the thing, though.
The plan doesn't work
unless we have someone to replace you.
I was hoping...
Plus, we have to worry about Jim.
He has another job offer.
We may have to replace him.
I didn't tell Michael because...
I thought he'd try to help.
Example: he handed out jell-o shots
at the 23rd mile
of the Steamtown Marathon.
- Can you walk me down to my car?
- Sure.
I can't help
but feel partially responsible.
Little pick-me-up.
Those are the best.
Sugar rush.
When you were talking to Wallace,
did I come up at all?
We did talk
about how handsome you are.
Why don't we head in your office?
What did we...
We said...
I know
there were certain things we said.
I'll just be honest with you.
Earlier today,
I spoke with Wallace
about a promotion.
And I actually think
that talk went really well.
Then after he spoke with you,
for some reason,
it felt like things had changed.
That's weird.
Kind of weirding me out.
Did you know that
Lincoln's secretary was named Kennedy?
Did you say anything?
Tell you what,
when you leave this office,
I'm going to call Wallace and tell him
that you should get that promotion.
Really?
You will?
Wanna do it right now?
I tried to keep Michael in the dark.
I should have known that he can do
just as much damage in the dark.
I need to see your pupils.
See if they're dilating.
Is that them?
Definitely.
You come to my house,
bust up my trash cans,
Call my baby sister an asshole
and told her to eat dog food?
We thought that she was you.
Why would you think a lady is me?
Are you serious?
Because you look exactly alike.
Am I the only one?
Are you getting this?
- I don't see it.
- Here's what I'm gonna do.
I'm calling corporate and I'm filing
a complaint against both of you.
Come on, Gwyneth.
Sad.
This is David.
David, this is Michael...
Just wanted to talk to you
about Jim Halpert.
I understand
that he did not receive
that promotion.
And I wanted to see what I could do
to nudge you in the right direction.
You're changing your mind about Jim?
Absolutely...
not!
Like I said before,
Jim is fantastic,
and he deserves this job.
It seems
like you're cutting in and out.
This is not what you said earlier.
Here's the thing.
Jim is the best man for this job.
I think you should give it to him.
It doesn't change
what you showed me in Jim's file.
That was an anomaly.
That file had been...
falsified.
Toby Flenderson is doing drugs.
I really don't know
what's going on down there.
Damn it!
I'm getting pulled over
for talking on my cell. Damn it.
Darryl, look,
we're here to apologize.
- We're cool.
- Wait.
They're using the lift
as their own personal elevator.
He broke his ankle
climbing over the railing,
he lied about it
'cause it was a misuse
of company equipment.
- Case closed.
- That's stupid.
Really?
Then why is there new wood
only on one railing?
Let's just check the security tapes.
I don't think there's any reason
to check 'em.
But I supposed
if you wanted to be really certain...
All right.
Fine, so whatever.
You really did it.
Now I would like
to file an official complaint
to corporate
because Darryl lied on an official form.
I'm telling them
you sexually harassed my sister.
No judges gonna believe that.
We could all file complaints
against each other,
and just drown in a sea of paperwork.
But,
we'll just move on with our...
with our lives.
So Dwight and Darryl
came to an agreement
that they would both file
complaints with corporate,
and now I got to do
all this paperwork.
We worked it out.
It would make me feel really good
if you would punch me in the face.
All right? Just do it.
How many times have I asked you
to put me up for a branch manager job?
I never recommended you
because I didn't want to lose you.
And I don't want to lose Pam.
Now I don't want to lose the baby.
Instead, you screwed me?
That's what she said.
- David Wallace is calling.
- I'm in the middle of something.
- Should I tell him you'll call back?
- I'll tell him myself.
Let's both.
- You got Jim there with you?
- No, it's just us.
Can you call Jim in?
I want him on this.
Please.
Here he is right now.
Come in.
So I spoke to Alan.
We had kind of an unconventional idea,
which I think is pretty cool.
But it only works
if everyone's on board.
Just as long as it means
Jim becomes a manager.
We were thinking of having
two branch managers in Scranton,
Both of you guys
working as co-managers.
Jim would handle the day-to-day,
and, Michael, you would focus
on clients and big picture stuff.
- That sounds pretty cool.
- I like that!
So manager and co-manager.
Co-manager and co-manager.
There are a lot of moving pieces,
and this is the only way I can sell it.
That might be a little confusing
because they know me as manager.
Michael,
can you pick up for one second?
Okay, look,
I'm not gonna force you into anything.
If you're willing to lose Jim, fine.
You just say so.
We'll find another solution.
Is that what you want to do?
- OK, people, listen up!
- Everybody...
I have an announcement to make.
Fraud was committed...
- You have an announcement?
- I was making it.
Everybody,
David Wallace and I've talked,
And we have decided to promote Jim
to the position of co-manager.
- Co-manager of what?
- Of your butt!
And your butt, and your butt...
All of Scranton branch butts.
- What's happening to you, Michael?
- What's happening to me?
I am also being promoted
to co-manager.
We will be co-managers together.
Welcome.
Niagara falls in October?
Hells yeah!
Do you think that you could
send in your RSVP card?
I'll just tell you now.
Easier.
You've to choose a food option,
and there's information in there
about directions and lodging.
I'll just have whatever's fanciest,
unless there's ribs,
I'll get the other information
the day of. I'll text you.
You're going to text me
the morning of my wedding
to ask for directions?
And you will eat
whatever is fanciest?
Unless there's ribs.
Rude.
So rude, right?
My gosh.
I have been chasing people down
all day.
- It's incredible.
- My bag was there.