Good morning everybody!
Who'd like an authentic NY bagel?
- Stanley?
- Thank you.
Oh, no, no, no.
I got a pumpernickel just for you.
H and h.
You went all the way to New
York City to get us bagels?
Oh, why, is there a place
closer that sells them?
This was really nice, Dwight.
- Thanks.
Oh, don't mention it.
You owe me one.
You all owe me one.
- Good morning, Michael.
- Good morning, Dwight.
Hungry?
No. I had a fish stick sandwich.
Actually, I had two
fish stick sandwiches.
My girlfriend didn't want hers,
because I guess I'm the
only aphrodisiac she needs.
Fish sticks are not an aphrodisiac.
You're thinking of deer penis.
It worked.
Regardless, that was over two hours ago,
and it is now a scientific
fact that you are hungry--bagel?
I don't mind if I do.
Okay, I brought cheese too.
I'm taking one for my lady friend.
- Excellent.
- Brain food.
- Thank you very much.
- Okay.
You owe me.
Can't a guy just buy some bagels for
his friends so they'll owe him a favor,
which he can use to get someone fired who
stole a co-manager position from him anymore?
Jeez... When did
everyone get so cynical?
Pam, would you care for a bagel?
Oh, no, thank you.
Oh, that's right, you're a woman, and
you need to refuse food the first time.
I'll try again.
Please, Pam, reconsider and have a bagel.
I have an early lunch.
Michael's been trying to get Jim and me to
hang out ever since he started dating my mom.
I don't know, I really hoped
this thing would just die out.
But today he's planning a birthday
lunch for my mom, and we have to go.
No way out.
These are amazing.
You took all these?
I've always found beauty
in uncommon places.
Homeless people.
Graffiti photography
lets me capture all that.
Have you ever been photographed before?
Just by, like, friends.
Well, here's what I've
been doing around here.
It's for a series on
exposure in the workplace.
Pammy?
- Hey...
- hi.
- Happy birthday.
- Thank you.
Girls...there they are.
Birthday
lunch. Birthday lunch--
there's no better medicine
than birthday lunch.
It'll cure all of your, "Gee, I don't know
if Michael should be dating my mother, "
and fixes all occurrences of," I
don't really see them together.
'so open wide, Pam, and take a big ol'
spoonful of birthday lunch medicine.
Take with food.
Pam, aren't you gonna introduce
us to Michael's girlfriend?
I think you guys all remember
my mom from the wedding.
Yeah, I think everyone's
met Helene. Shall we?
Wait a minute, is that another
birthday present for me?
'Cause you already gave me a necklace.
Oh, my god, I love it.
- Tell her how you gave it to me.
- No, that wouldn't be...
he put it around my neck while
I was still asleep this morning.
What a nice way to wake up.
Yeah, the rest of the story has been
censored due to inappropriosity.
- Because of sex?
- Kevin!
Hey, please, Kevin... You're fired.
Sorry.
Work with a bunch of idiots.
- Shall we go?
- Yes, let's go.
Oh, wait.
Swartz lumber is on the phone for
you, Pam, and they say it's urgent.
You guys, just one second.
Oh, my gosh!
Are you serious?
Shipping emergency.
I don't think I can go to lunch.
Oh, man, that's crazy.
We were on our way out too.
I know. Isn't that always how it goes?
Rarely, if ever.
Let me give it a whirl.
- I want to handle it.
- That's okay.
- I feel like.
- It's my pleasure.
Hello? Well, that's great.
Turns out the paper was there all along.
Oh, thank god.
Something's up.
That paper was never supposed to arrive.
So, Pammy, are you still liking sales?
Yeah. It's exciting.
Uh, you know, Michael and I were talking,
and maybe if you put in a little more
face-to-face time with your clients,
you could improve your sales.
Pam's sales are fine, actually.
Just want you to succeed, Pammy.
You know what? We shouldn't even
be talking about business today.
Thank you.
Today's about family.
Why did I get in the car?
I could have struggled.
I have a whistle in my
purse. I didn't even blow it.
Oh, Dwight, I have a
little surprise for you.
Let me guess, you ate the
bagel I gave you and loved it.
Yes.
And I wanted to return the favor.
I was polishing my loafers,
and I happened to look over and notice that
your briefcase was a little worse for the wear.
So a little elbow grease, and she's
polished right up, back to her former glory.
- Oh, well...
- Feel it against your cheek.
I will.
You give me a
gift- Thank you note.
You invite me
somewhere--RSVP.
You do me a
favor--Favor returned.
Do not test my politeness.
Let me get that door for you.
- There we go.
- Thank you very much.
- And I got it for you.
- Oh, goodness. Thanks
Hey, you know, here's
a healthy fitness tip.
If you clench your buttocks
together while walking,
you can really take the
pressure off your knees.
- Is that right?
- Observe.
- Right?
- That really works.
Yeah, feel free to use that anytime.
- Okay...
- hold on a second.
Do not walk around with
your jacket cattywampus.
And that needs to be
straight as an arrow.
Thank you very much.
- Oh, boy.
- Okay.
Thank you very much for that.
- Have a seat. Please.
- Have a seat yourself.
You know what, I am going to preemptively
change the batteries in your wireless mouse.
- Not necessary.
- No, no, no.
You don't have to do that.
Andy is complicating things.
But I'm not worried.
This will only up my game.
Hello. "Scott," table for four.
Welcome, Scott family.
It'll be just a moment.
I used to love coming here.
The chicken parm is good.
Big part of my childhood.
Oh, maybe Michael will
start dating that too.
What table should we take?
So many to choose from.
- Oh, my god!
- What?
All I see are boring old tables
with no birthday decorations.
Oh, wait a second!
You mean this one?
Michael, you did all this?
It's not about taking credit. Let's
just say we all did it.
Well, thank you. All of you.
Well, it was actually me alone, so....
Wow, look at this place.
It really makes me want
to go to Italy someday.
Oh, you'll love it.
You can have my guide books.
I think I'm done with those
really long plane rides.
Oh, thank you for-- thanks
for lending me the book.
So, mom, which birthday are
we celebrating this year?
Oh, sticking with 49.
49 again?
That's nine years in a row.
This is now our longest
family tradition.
That's funny.
Well, as long as you're running
numbers, Pam, help me out with this one.
Let's see, honey, you're
six months pregnant,
but you've only been
married for 30 days.
So what does that add up to?
Ooh, burn. Burn on you.
And a little bit on me too.
You're 54 years old.
No, I'm 58.
You're 58 years old?
Congratulations.
The only time you should care about a
woman's age is if she is too young for you.
And I am not robbing the cradle.
If anything, I am robbing the grave.
Mom, have you decided what
you want to be called?
I like "Nana."
but I also like the classic "grandma."
- Please be grandma. I want you to be grandma.
- Definitely a grandma.
Michael, what do you think? Grandma?
Grandma.
Hey, would you guys ever
do a triathlon, you think?
Maybe.
Helene?
Oh, oh, no.
I don't think so.
I am.
I'm definitely gonna do it.
I've already got the run
and the bike thing down.
I just need to learn how to swim.
Come on, you in?
No, no, I think a triathlon is pretty
much something I can rule out.
It just doesn't interest me.
So it's a matter of interest.
Good. Okay.
It's not anything you
would have ever done.
Mm, I might have done
it when I was younger,
but now there are just other things that
I'd rather be doing than running and jumping.
Well, there's no jumping in a triathlon.
You're thinking the broad jump.
Would you try...
- Bungee jumping?
- No.
- Snowboarding?
- No, no.
You want to go snowboarding?
I might.
Michael, what are you talking about?
Nothing.
Just life and... Doing
things... Before you die.
I don't know.
Do I really want to go snowboarding?
No.
But I-- I would like
to if I wanted to.
What's going on in here?
Andy bought lunch.
Oh, no, really?
Took a page right out of the
old Schrute book of niceness.
There is no book. There's
only a survival guide.
You bought breakfast for
everyone, so I got lunch for everyone.
Okay, well, allow me.
You know
what--
gosh, these tacos are
awfully complicated to make.
I will make everyone's tacos.
So we should get the check?
- What about your gift, Michael?
- Oh, no, no, no.
No, it's stupid. You'd hate it. I hate it.
- I'm sure I won't.
- Yes, you will.
He locked himself in his office
all morning working on it.
Oh, gimme! Look at this wrapping paper.
It's got the word "love"
on it in every language!
I literally--I put no thought
into the wrapping at all.
Might as well have been toilet paper.
Toilet paper...
"a scrapbook of our first
memories," by Michael Gary Scott.
For my girlfriend
Helene on your birthday."
That's just an arbitrary title.
Okay, here's a penny.
- What's that from?
- Penny for your thoughts.
It was from the wishing
well at the mall.
You threw it in, and I went back
later, waded in, and I found it.
That's amazing!
It's not amazing at all.
It's sort of weird that
I went and did that.
And now your wish won't
come true, so that blows.
- A poem.
- Oh, that I plagiarized, I think.
"I cannot go to school today
said little Peggy Ann McKay,"
- is that Shel Silverstein?
- Yeah.
"I have the measles and the mumps, a
gash, a rash, and purple bumps,
and my teacher's really mean--
happy birthday, I love you, Helene."
that's really nice, Michael.
Well, I think it sucks.
I think it's
wonderful. Absolutely wonderful.
Well, that's because you and
I have very different taste.
And you like lame things.
It's a generational
sort of gap between us.
God, a scrapbook.
Home run, Michael.
- You set the bar so high.
- That was a bunt.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, Dwight, I'm gonna do this.
Hey, hey, hey, relax.
I got it covered.
- No, no, no.
- No, I insist.
Okay, Dwight, this is ridiculous.
Don't worry about
it. You can just owe me.
Hey, where'd you go?
Oh, just went to the bathroom.
And then you stopped at
the bar on the way back?
Got thirsty.
Okay, weirdo.
Come on, it's time for cake.
Oh, okay.
Honestly, for a long time I thought
I was going to grow old with holly.
And then I met Helene, and she is great.
And she already knows and has done
everything that I have ever wanted to do,
and can tell me about it.
But I think I want to
do those things myself.
The cake's really good.
Oh, I know.
I love it when they use
butter-cream frosting.
Finish your cake, Helene.
I want you to enjoy that cake because I
have something terrible I need to tell you,
and I want you to enjoy your cake before
I tell you this terrible, terrible thing.
Al Helene, I think you're
a wonderful person,
and I--god, I've enjoyed dating you
and being your boyfriend so much.
But I've to consider Pam's feelings.
As a friend and a -worker,
I cannot in good conscience continue to
date you when I know what this is doing to her.
Michael--
Michael, it's- it's okay.
No, it's not.
I know that it took me a
little while to come around,
and it's still a little weird to get used
to, but you obviously make my mom very happy.
And that makes me happy.
Wow, that just--
you've really grown.
Well...
Oh, thank you, Pam.
And I hope you're as gracious
during this next part.
Helene, once again, you are a wonderful
person, and you have lived a great life.
And I envy it.
And I want it, someday.
But just in the future.
You need somebody who-- o
understands your references.
Who is Kafkaesque?
I've never--I
don't know him.
There's another woman, and
her name is Italy...
and skydiving... and bungee jumping.
Okay, so...
And I want kids.
And you, unfortunately, have already completed
that part of your journey down there.
- Michael!
- It's not my decision. It's mother nature.
And mother has very strict rules about...
fertility.
Yeah, I, um... I got it.
I'm 58.
What am I supposed to do now?
- Well, hobbies...
- Stop.
- What's going on?
- Stupid thing wedged up there.
No one in this office will help me.
Move it.
What if Dwight dies and
I still owe him something?
That is a recipe for a ghost.
- Oh, yeah, you're gonna owe me big time.
- It's like a little envelope...there you go.
Got it. "To Dwight"?
A Starbucks gift card.
Surprise!
It's for everybody.
$15 value.
Damn it! I am no closer to taking Jim down.
Ugh, what a waste of the day.
I could have grown poison mushrooms
that'd be this high by now!
They're mushrooms.
They don't get that high.
Pamela Beasley Halpert.
- What?
- May I have a word with you in my office, please?
I am working.
Well... This is a work-related matter.
- Really?
- Yes.
Join me, please, won't you?
- I'm going to give you a raise, Pam.
- Why?
Because of all the good work you've done.
I have the lowest
sales record of anyone here.
No, no.
It's not about numbers, Pam.
It's about attitude.
I have the worst
attitude of any person here.
Do you want the raise or what?
- Yeah, I'll take it.
- Okay.
Hey, Pam.
With this raise there
are strings attached.
And the string is attached from
my heart to your mean attitude.
You're bribing me.
No, no. No, am not.
Unless you want me to. You want me to?
'Cause I will. I will bribe you.
No...your face is saying don't.
Unless I haven't offered you enough.
Your face isn't changing.
What is it?
Talk to me, face. Tell me
what Pam's brain is thinking.
Oh, come on, what do you
want? What do you want?
Do you want a million dollars?
Do you want to hit me?
You want me to get down
on one knee and beg you?
- I want to hit you.
- What?
I want to hit you. I'll do that.
Okay. What?
I don't-- are
you kidding?
No. Are you kidding?
Ye--no. I don't--
all right, come on.
I'll take off my jacket and
tense my stomach, and you just...
No, I don't think I can
hit you in the office.
Ok.
So we'll do it after work?
In the parking lot.
In front of everyone.
I'm gonna hit you as hard as I can.
Okay.
- Okay.
- See you then.
- See you.
Quick question.
Are you scared?
Never.
About what?
A little. What are you talking about?
Heard about the punch.
- What punch?
- Pam.
She's gonna punch the crap
out of your face after work.
I'm pretty sure we said "slap."
No, it's a punch.
And Pam has that crazy
pregnancy strength now.
I'm getting concerned that you don't seem
to understand what's going to happen.
Do you?
Uh. I'm good.
All right, see you there.
- Do you and Pam ever get frisky?
- Inappropriate.
I mean, do you ever
wrestle with each other?
- All the time.
- Really?
- Is she strong?
- She wants it bad, Michael.
Can you stop this?
- I can.
- Okay.
- And I don't support her choice to hit you.
- I don't either.
But at the same time, she goes crazy.
And I do understand her reasoning.
I know.
I just need some time.
- Give me some time to think about it.
- You gotta do something.
- Give me some time to make a decision.
- How much time do you need?
- No me than a week. Maybe two.
- Come on, man!
Pam, can I talk to you for a second?
I heard about the hit.
Just to be sure, it's off
company property, right?
- Right.
- Okay
I think it should probably be okay.
- Okay.
And... The--the power
comes from the back foot.
So it's all one motion through the body.
So there's-- you
stay a little low.
There's a twist.
You keep your shoulder down.
You kind of throw out the arm.
Okay, wait.
It's-- you're saying
it comes from the foot?
Yes.
Okay.
Yeah. Okay.
Hey, everybody, he's not in the men's room,
although the seat was warm, so
we may have just missed him.
My money's on Pam.
It's not a fight what other
outcome could there be?
Michael could win.
How?
He can't hit back.
Why can't you just
agree with me sometimes?
Am I scared of getting
hit in the face? No.
Every day, weirdos pay dominatrices
hundreds of dollars for that very privilege.
I'm scared I'm gonna love it.
Let's do this!
It's okay, guys, I can handle this.
Everybody can go home.
We're here for the show, Michael.
You're just a bunch of voyeurs.
Are you eating popcorn?
Has almost no calories.
You ready?
Yes.
- You have to keep your hands down, Michael.
- I know.
Okay. All right.
No! God!
Michael! You have to keep your hands down.
Put your hands in your pockets.
Okay.
Pam! Pam...
I'm really sorry. I'm sorry.
What are you sorry for?
So many things. I don't
know, it's hard to choose.
How' bout for dating my mom.
- Maybe that's...
- And dumping her on her birthday.
Yes.
Okay, just... Don't ever date
a member of my family again.
Okay. No problem.
For the record, your mom came on to me.
Holy crap!
- Are you okay?
- No!
You're okay.
Feel better?
No. You were right.
Com wait, why are you limping?
I don't know.
Let's get some raw meat on that face.
I've got a chicken in
the freezer upstairs.
As I watched Pam's big, strong
hand coming toward my face,
I saw my entire life
flash before my eyes.
And guess what.
I have four kids.
And I have a hover-car
and a hover-house.
And my wife is a runner, and it shows.
And Pam and Jim are my best
friends, and our kids play together.
And I am happy, I'm rich, and I never die.
It doesn't sound like
much, but it's enough for me.
Good, good. Just keep it on
there for another five minutes.
Let the swelling go down.
Oh, thank you.
Thanks. I owe you one, Dwight.
Fire Jim.
No.
I'm cashing in the favor. Fire him!
- What are you talk...
- do it!
Promote me.
- Tri-managers?
- Forget that.
- Can I have an office?
- No.
You know what? You can keep your
stupid favor. It's worthless.
And this is my dinner on
your face. I'm keeping it!
Oh, that feels better.