Not again.
Bow down before recyclops.
Five years ago,corporate said
we had to start a recycling
program for earth day.
So dwight took the lead
on that and introduced us
to a very close friend
of his named recyclops.
Happy earth day,everyone,i'm recyclops.
Did you know that an old milk carton
can be sawed in half
and used as a planter?
The next year he really
stepped things up.
Who has put a number seven
plastic in a number four bin?
A year after that,recyclops
really began to take shape.
Recyclops will drown you
in your overwatered lawns.
Then tragedy struck recyclops
when his fictional planet was attacked
by some other fictitious thing.
I can't remember.
Recyclops will have his revenge.
I think this was also the year
that he renounced earth day
and vowed to destroy
the planet he once loved.
Oh,my god,you guys,look,it's recyclops!
Recyclops destroys!
- Oh,is today recyclops day?
- Yes.
I thought you were killed
by polluticorn or something.
Polluticorn wishes.
That's aerosol spray.
It's terrible for th environment.
Humans are terrible for the environment.
The thing I like most about recyclops
ishat he's creating a
different world for our child.
A world where you truly
can be anything you want.
God bless you,recyclops
and your cold robot heart.
Okay,okay,how about this?
- That's great.
- I want it to be better than great,pam.
How about I remain seated and I just do a
little bit of a nod. Sort of a humble thing.
Sure.
No,then my face is down
and they can't see my face.
And it looks like you're taking a dump.
Alan brand is the ceo of the company,
if title's important to you,
has personally invited moi to go to
new york to the shareholder's meeting
and sit up on the stage
with the board of directors.
And at some point they
are going to introduce me
as the most successful
branch manager that they have.
And then michael scott turns and waves
to the crowd and the crowd goes wild.
Ladies and gentleman,from
scranton pennsylvania,
please welcome michael
"the machine" scott.
- Don't do the twirl.
- Lose the twirl.
- Twirl sucks.
- Michael,I hated the twirl.
Hate the twirl.
Okay,obviously,I'm not
going to do the twirl.
I only did it cacause I nailed the wave.
Yeah,good,don't do it.
I'm not going to do
the twirl. All right?
It's not even a twirl,it's a spin.
I might do the spin.
The long term problem is bad
investments that they need to dump.
The short term problem is the company
has no cash and there's
nowhere to get it.
Okay,oscar,I don't need the whole
enchilada just bullet points.
Those are the bullet points.
Well,could you condense it please?
That's as simple as I can make it.
Michael,the limo's here for you.
It's not a limo,it's a town car.
Town car's are actually better though,
better torque,better handling.
He said limousine so...
Check it out,guys.
There's a limo down here.
Michael,look.
Oh,man.
They sent a limo.
Town cars suck. A town car is something
that a company sends when they're in trouble.
A limousine is something
that a company sends
when they have cse for celebration.
And in this case,I think
we are celebrating me.
Oh,wait! Wait!
wo Wow!
Ohoh,no way. Look at that.
What kind of mileage does this baby get?
It's like what high school
kids take to prom on tv shows.
This is so typical of management
to spend money on this.
Uh,they're a bunch of boobs.
Hate to break it to you,oscar,but
some of us like boobs.
Calves,calves all the way.
I'i'm so jealous right now.
Hey,you know who you should be jealousf?
Yourself because you're
invited,and you're invited,
and you're invited,and you,and
you,and you,and you,and you,and you...
Car seats eight. And you...
- What?
- The car seats eight.
The limo seats eight. Okay,then
jim and pam,and ryan plus a guest.
- No thanks.
- no.
I'll use it when you're done.
I'll go...
me.
The dunder mifflin stock symbol is dmi.
Do you know what that stands for?
Dummies,morons and idiots
because that's what you'd
have to be to own it.
And as one of those idiots,I
believe the board owes me answers.
I wish the windows weren't tinted
so people could see us in here.
Hey guys,do you thinknynyone
might have had sex in here?
- Definitely.
- Sounds like it.
Definitely. Look,they got pillows.
That,that's bigger than my bed.
- Word!
- Yeah,yeah!
Who's playing with the button?
Hey,ryan,could you start consolidating
all of our rolodex
information into outlook?
Uh,itoeoesn't seem like there's much
of a point if the company's going under.
But if the company doesn't go under,
then we'll finally have all
our contacts in one program.
- The company's probably going under though.
- It could go either way.
Seems like it's leaning one way.
Maybe we should just wait and find out
- definitely.
- Okay.
So should we wait to find out
before we start doing all this stuff?
Nah,might as well do it now.
Michael,what if somebody asks
you a question at this meeting?
Are you just gonna wave or what?
I will have to answer.
I'll ask you a question.
Make it a softball.
Something he can,like,crank
out of the park.
Michael scott,you run
ththe most profitable branch
of dunder mifflin,how do you do it?
No,no,that's too hard.
Say you're name is
zamboni and I will say,
"well,we're sort of on thin ice.
" I won't say that,i'll
say something like that.
This is your big day,come on.
Oh,my god. This is it.
- Mr. Scott?
- Yes.
- I'm laurie.
- Oh,hi.
Thank you for joining us. Come with me.
Well,thank you and please call me...
Continue to call me mr. Scott.
Okay.
If you just wanna follow me
i'll take you up to the lounge.
Well,I guess that's as far
as I can take yoguys. So...
- Good luck,michael.
- See you later.
Officers. Thank you.
- Here is the lounge.
- Thank you.
- Michael.
- Hello.
- So glad you could make it.
- Thank you.
- How was the ride?
- Oh,it was awesome. Very,very sublime.
I'm glad. I want to
introduce you to everyone.
Uh,first we'll start with alan brand.
Alan,ceo,michael
scott,branch manager,scranton.
- It's nice to meet you michael.
- Nice to meet you too.
It's an honor and a privilege.
And seated we have the former
congressman chris o'keefe.
Ah,your eminence.
For those of you with questions,
please line up behind one
of the four microphones
that have been placed in the isle.
Coming through.
Excuse me. Excuse me. Excuse me.
H,h,damn it.
What... Okay.
I was hoping to lob michael
a soft ball question early.
I wanted to swing by
the garment district
and pick up a few crates of my shirts.
I got a shirt guy.
Can you believe this?
The money theypent on
this convention hall.
Excuse me,miss.
I just want to take those stupid
board of directors by their necks.
This is so simple.
Oh,yeah. Well,you should
do that. Get in line.
Oh,what a great idea and
lose my job. No,thank you.
Look,don't you wanna be
able to tell your grandkids
you stood up for yourself during
america's biggest financial crisis?
How is he gonna have grandkids?
You guys ever protect the president?
no.
What about madonna?
Obama twins? Anybody famous?
Not supposed to talk about it.
Nelly furtado.
All right,guys.
Are you ready?
Rock and roll
all: boo!
**** Company.
We are poised to come through this more
streamlin a and profitable than ever.
This is not as much fun
as I thoug I it would be.
It was fun when we weren't
on the brink of bankruptcy.
We're going bankrupt,you think?
They are really angry.
I'm just gonna run to the
bathroom,will you save my place?
- Sure.
- no. You will not.
Excuse me?
Oh,I'm sorry,were you raised in
a household with no consequences?
It'll just be a second.
Oh,if onlys and justs
were candies and nuts
then everyday would be erntedankfest.
There are many things to be optimistic
about in dunder mifflin's future.
And one of them is here with us today.
Michael scott,scranton branch manager.
Yes!
In these uncertain
times michael has managed
to maintain steady profits
from the scranton branch.
We all thank you,michael.
Another bright spot in the
dunder mifflin landscape
our new waste-pulp
re-purposing plant in milford.
Hey,phyllis,are you just
getting back from lunch now?
Bob took me to capello's.
We got a little tipsy.
Okay,shouldn't be telling me that stuff
and also shouldn't be taking two
hour lunches without telling me.
Oh,it's okay,michael esesn't
really care about these things.
I care about 'em and I'm just
as much of a boss as michael.
What's so funny? I'm a co-manager.
That doesn't make you a boss.
It's not like you can
fire people or anything.
Well,who... How did
you... Who told you this?
- We can't say.
- Ryan.
Sorry,I'm plastered.
Okay,who else has heard the rumor
that I am not as much
in charge as michael?
Stuff gets around. I don't participate.
Who here heard it from ryan?
Does an email count?
- Yes.
- Then yeah.
I am just as much of a boss as michael
and I can do anything that
michael can do. All right.
Who here believes that I
have as much power as michael?
I forgot I have to
support him no matter what.
Close one.
These questions are bush league.
You should get up and say something.
You gotta be true to what's
in there. Don't be a wuss.
I've always been the guy who
can rally other people to rebel.
In high school,I organized a walk
out over standardized testing.
Got over 500 students
j just skip the sats.
At the last second I chickened
out,took it anyway,got a 1220.
Always regretted it.
I feel lachrymose.
Believe me,everyone
is working very hard,
working weekends,struggling,trying
to right the ship.
You're criminals!
Hey,hey! I'm sorry
these are not criminals.
They're nice.
They invited me to come here today,
they invited me to
their hospitality suite,
where I had free
food,and it was delicious.
Get this,you know how nice they are?
They sent a stretch limo all the
way to pick me up in scranton.
- Limousine?
- Yes.
You're all corrupt.
You should be in jail!
Quiet! Quiet,please!
Please,quiet! Quiet,please.
We want to hear your questions.
Do you love her,or do
you love the idea of her?
I don't know,man. I just don't know.
I gotta make an example out of him.
Should I just fire him?
Can you actually fire people?
To be honest,I don't know.
But maybe I could just yell
at him in front of people.
Well,I can't really imagine
you yelling at anyone.
Oh,I yell. You've heard me yell.
Okay. I've heard you exclaim.
Like the time you said,"hey
look,we parked over here.
" well,that was apple picking day.
There's no need to yell that day.
You know,I was just
excited to find the car.
Perfect end to a perfect day.
Well,you'll figure it out.
Okay,we're gonna take a 15-minute break
and then we're gonna
answer more questions.
You haven't said anything yet
and we're headed rr bankruptcy.
Yeah,well,that's not gonna happen.
That's not gonna happen.
We'll be back with se answers.
What? What answers?
I... Okay,I know,that you're mad at
me and you're mad at all of them...
How are you gonna fix the company?
Okay...
All right,we are gonna...
We're gonna go out
there during this break
and we are gonna come back with a plan.
We're gonna come back
with a plan for you.
It's a 45-day plan.
45 days to get us back on track.
Yeah!
45 points.
It's a
45-day,45-point...
One point per day...
We get 45 points we're back in business.
And you can take that to the bank.
And limo lady,we are going
completely carbon neutral.
I love you,new york!
*** How's it go...
Here's the thing,um,I've tried it like
five different ways in my head and...
Oh,got one,um,I'm such a perfectionist
that I'd kinda rather not do it
at all,than do a crappy version.
Simple data entry though,so
there's really only oneay to do it.
Sounds like you have a
really specific vision for it.
Do you wanna,maybe,just
take a whack at it?
- You know what?
- What?
- I think I know the problem.
- Great.
I think you seem distracted.
Yep,that is the problem.
And you know what,I came up with something
and I think it's really gonna help.
Well,I'm glad you're
finally being proactive,jim.
I am too. Let me show you.
Wow,things are really picking up.
- What was that about?
- What?
You were suppose to wave.
I did wave. I did a lot more than wave.
What are we suppose to tell them now?
Okay,you've dug us quite a hole.
We tell them the plan. Right?
There is no plan.
Here's what we're gonna do.
The 45-day thing that I
outlined,we go with that.
Day 45 company saved. Day 44,go.
What have we got? We have 15 minutes.
Excuse me?
Just whatever comes
to mind,shout it out.
Who the hell is this guy?
I am the guy who roused that crowed...
- Yes...
- Got 'em on their feet.
- They were so happy down there.
- Yes. Who cares?
Okay,all right.
Well,I know a guy... This mexican guy.
Is a math whiz,he knows economics
as well as he knows bullfighting
and I am going to
call in a little favor.
No,no,don't call anybody,michael.
Well,I'm texting him so...
Please do not text anybody now. Michael.
It's done.
Oh,there he is. Come on in. Come on in.
Gentleman,I would like u to meet
oscar... Come on in. Don't be shy.
This is oscar martinez.
Oscar,why don't you come
over here? Let me present you.
Step up,step up there.
Oscar is an accountant
extraordinaire at the scranton branch
and he has a wonderful idea as to
how to get us out of this murky
murky situation. Take it away.
I think this is really gonna help.
If you can just hold up here one second.
Hey,guys,just a quick announcement.
If I could have everyone's attention.
I just figured you needed a place
where you could concentrate and
not be bothered by bothering people.
- Okay.
- Let me show you what I mean.
Your new office.
How great is that,right?
For a job well done.
Well... Not done.
I will,uh,I will do my work right now.
- I will stay late tonight.
- Right.
Um,I'm very sorry about everything.
You're a good kid. You kn what,it
gets bigger once you're in there.
Enjoy it.
Is there internet?
Um...
Tell them what you
told me. This is genius.
Tell them about the cash flow.
And the dumping of
properties and this is all...
It's all good,it's all good stuff.
Lay it on 'em.
I feel,as does Mr. Scott,that we are
in the best of hands,uh,capable hands...
That wasn't what you were sayin' to me.
He was much more articulate
and that was better.
- Much better.
- I think this has gone very well.
I... And I thank you.
Okay...
Hey,hey. What are you doing?
Michael,I didn'ask to come up here.
Wow,man,that... That was embarrassing.
- For me.
- For me too.
- For you?
- You embarrassed me.
You...
Well...
That was a waste of a text.
Let's get down to brass tacks.
I think that we might be in trouble.
We don't seem to have
a plan so I'm thinking,
I go down there,maybe rattle off a
few jokes congressman could follow.
He's our best manager?
Where's the off button on this moron?
Uh,I'm not a moron.
Time after time,my
branch leads in sales,
I have personally won over 17
dundee awards,so I am not a moron.
And I'm just trying to help,you
know,so you're the moron.
Yes,it is a thrill to be
honored by one's company.
To have the people that you
work for stop for a minute
and say,"wow,great job.
That's what it's about.
" he canaake the bus.
He's had his limo ride.
That is what it's all
about,not the perks.
The perks... The perks,I
could take or leave the perks.
Oscar! Oscar,come on!
But limos are for people
who make the company money
not lose millions and have no plan.
So we're leaving early.
Woo-hoo!
Go,go,go,go,go,go,go! Go,go,go!
Did you steaththat?
After all,we are the only ones
with anything to celebrate.
All:
scranton,scranton,scranton,scranton!
Dunder mifflin!
The gentleman in the, uh, glasses...
Dwight Shrute... Scranton branch.
I just want to say that I have been
standing in this line, all day...
And if this line is any indication
of how this company is being run,
...then we are in big trouble!
Yes!   I know!
And I just wanna say...
That I believe that
there are options out there...
A 'take-a-number' option,
like they have in a deli...
What about line varieties?
Like an express line...
For quick comments, of ten words or less -
they could move much more efficiently.
What about ropes, along the lines,
that you can hold on to?
Thank you...
Thank you for your suggestion.
Yes.