Buenos dias, erin.
Buenos dias, miguel.
Hello, dunder-mifflin.
No, no, no, no.
Solamente, en español,
por favor.
I believe that every man, woman,
and child in this country
Should learn how
to speak spanish.
They are our neighbors to the south,
And this would be a healing thing for all
of North America,
And I am going on a vacation this week,
to cancun.
Buenos diaz, jaime.
Buenos diaz, miguel.
Como estas?
[speaking spanish]
Ha ha!
Buenos diaz, dwight!
Guten tag, herr Michael.
I don't understand why Michael
Is wasting his
time with spanish.
I have it on very good authority
That within 20 years,
Everyone will be
speaking german.
Or a chinese-german hybrid.
La telefona.
El telefono.
Michael's having a hard time
with the gender part of spanish.
So I told him to mark everything
With the international
symbol for gender.
And, um...
I should have been
more specific.
Your office is
full of genitalia.
oh.
Eso es lo que dice el.
"that's what he says"?
Damn it.
Ah, angelo.
Angela.
Michael.
Yo soy cancun.
Uhh!
All right, so I'll finish
up on bulk pricing,
And then you go into
delivery guarantee.
You know, maybe
there's an opportunity
For a joke there.
Like, um...Like,
"I just delivered a baby.
They didn't offer
me a guarantee."
Yeah, or maybe we
don't even need that.
Can you smell the
power of halperts?
Power couple.
You know what?
I should be getting
this client, Michael.
My numbers are better
than either of theirs.
I went with the people
I thought would put the
best face on the company.
If you want people
To put the best
face on something,
Why would you get two people
Who probably have
never cut the face
Off of anything in their lives?
that's a good point.
This is our first
joint sales pitch.
I think we're gonna work
really well together.
Yeah, I think we have
complementary strengths.
Jim-We understand each other
Pam-We have good give and take
I give he takes
[Whispering] I don't even
know who you are anymore.
Yee.
Hi, uh, Donna Newton,
here to see Michael Scott.
Oh, hey, Ms. Newton.
Hi, I'm Jim.
How are you?
Did somebody order
a hooker over here?
- oh, stop that.
- Hi.
How are you?
There's this woman I
met a few weeks ago.
Her name is Donna,
The manager of Sid & Dexter's.
And, right now,
we're in the midst
Of a passionate love affair.
Um, no. But she is
coming by today.
Maybe to buy some
printers, so...
Right here,
we have the wonder twins,
Jim and Pam halpert.
They will be
assisting you today.
You look exactly alike.
Oh, no, we're actually married.
We're not brother and sister.
I have a sense
about these things.
All right.
You have some
ancestors in common...
Somewhere back.
I knew it.
You should see their baby.
So, yes, laser printers
are more expensive.
But they cost less to operate.
so it's a tradeoff.
Hi, Sorry to interrupt. little time sensitive.
Do you Donna by any chance shop at Victoria Secret?
Because I keep getting these magazines sent to me
Via the address of the woman
who used to live in my condo
Before me.
None of this is time sensitive.
Uh, yes, uh, the sale
is on now through may.
Oh, yeah, thank you.
Okay, I have more of them.
You would have
weekly conference calls
With executives in corporate.
A two-week training program
At the yale school
of management,
Obviously, you would
be high on the list
For advancement opportunities.
Sounds all right.
What is this?
Oh, this is "print
in all colors,"
Sabre's minority executive
training program.
It doesn't just sound a'ight,
It sounds amazing.
I didn't say "a'ight."
How do I apply?
You have to be a minority.
Uh, glasses wearers.
Cholera survivors. Geniuses.
Non-organic family farmers.
The list goes on and on.
You want me to keep going?
Those don't really count.
We're thinking more ethnic
and racial minorities.
Come here.
Come here. - Hmm?
Ten seconds ago,
this guy was driving a forklift.
Okay? Now, all of a sudden,
he's cinderella of the office.
What are you guys thinking?
Well...
I like the sound of this.
Maybe one day I'll be
sitting in Michael's chair.
Wouldn't that be something?
One minority from this branch
Is going to get
into this program.
Who would I prefer? Hmm...
The competent, hardworking one
Who does things his own way,
Or the malleable simpleton
who can be bought
For a few fashion magazines?
This is the second time
That you've sent
me the wrong size.
I mean, I know what a
four should feel like,
I've been a four my whole life.
You know what?
You can go to hell.
All right? Thanks for nothing.
Oh, man.
White people, right?
I don't know if she was white.
Well, you can kind of
tell from the voice.
Yeah.
I bet you get pulled
over by the cops a lot,
Just because of your race.
Well, they say it's
because of texting,
But maybe you're right.
I think you should
consider applying
For the executive
minority training program.
Never thought of myself
as an executive before.
I know, 'cause you
have no role models.
How many Indian ceos
can you think of?
I can't think of any ceos,
any race.
You could be the
Indian Bill Gates.
Indian Ted Turner.
I could be the
Indian Julia Roberts.
That's not-- she's--okay.
Yes.
I took the liberty to
scan a few things earlier,
And I want to show you--
There we go!
Whoa, look at those
vivid colors.
Look at my eyes.
Those are shrek-green eyes.
That is me again.
I think this displays the crisp,
dazzling white.
Mm-hmm.
And that would be a display
Of the crisp, gorgeous black.
Yeah.
It's subtle.
That's how it works.
I show her an image
that turns her on.
And then she looks at me,
then she looks at the image,
Then back at me,
then back at the image.
Soon, she doesn't
know what is me,
What is the image.
She just knows that
she's turned on.
This is a place
that I like to go
To be alone with my thoughts.
I've never taken
anybody there before.
Who took the photo?
- Ryan.
- Oh.
And that's it.
That's me.
That's who I am.
Not bad.
oh, thanks.
you're not bad, either.
Thank you.
Ahem.
Hmm.
Oh, my god.
Jim! Could you come
in here for a sec?
What was that printer
we were looking at?
You didn't see it, Pam.
She was giving me
all sorts of signals
That she wanted
me to make a move.
Shortbread? - No.
I'll have one.
Well, maybe you shouldn't
try to kiss people at work.
Oh, really, Jim?
What about Pam?
And you did a heck of
a lot more than kiss.
Maybe this could be my Pam.
Well, all that is irrelevant.
Maybe Michael has a point.
I mean, if she was
really that upset,
She wouldn't still be here.
Was it professional? No.
But I work in the
nightlife industry.
I get hit on all the time.
In my 20s, it would
have been annoying.
In my late 20s,
I find it really flattering.
Look, I know that I
screwed up in there.
I know that I probably
messed up your sale.
I just want to go in and fix it.
What if I back out,
And you finish the
pitch with Jim?
What?
What was that?
Just let him flirt with her.
People meet each other
all sorts of ways.
Pam, you know he's not
gonna get anywhere,
And he's gonna blow our sale.
Who cares? It's not
that huge a sale.
Hey, the schwab guy told
us to treat every sale
Like it was a huge sale.
Don't act like you understood
anything that guy said.
Good luck, wingman.
How has being a
minority affected you?
Well, there's a lot of
pressure from my parents
To settle down and
marry an Indian guy.
Oh, good, and you
resent this because...
Indian guys always
wear their cell phones
Outside their pants.
It's so dorky.
Oh, no, no. That's not dorky.
Look, it's easily accessible.
Boom, like this. 911, hello.
Scranton strangler's
in the house.
Inside the house.
Just put it in your pocket.
Look at that.
She's totally flirting with him.
You don't know that.
Some people can't
help oozing sexuality.
You ever notice you can
only ooze two things:
Sexuality and pus.
Man, I tell ya.
She just crossed her arms
together--that's bad.
Maybe she's just pushing
her breasts together
To make them look bigger.
Like that?
Is this--is this the best
you can do right there?
Uh, for that printer, yes.
Unfortunately, we don't
have a lot of flexibility.
Oh.
Well, I guess I'm just used
to the restaurant business,
Where, if you're in charge,
Then you can always
get discounts
For the people that you like.
So maybe we could find a
little wiggle room, right?
What's that?
Maybe we find some wiggle room?
I don't-- I don't think so.
I think we could.
I don't see how we could
possibly sell these
For that little
without losing money.
Delivery alone will cost--
Okay, well, sometimes--
Sometimes it makes
financial sense
To lose money, right?
Like for tax purposes.
Actually,
ran the numbers on this,
And in this case,
it makes more financial sense
To gain money.
Why don't you run them again.
What if she's just
flirting with you
To get a better price?
If she is, it's working.
Yeah, Michael, here's a trick.
As her if she wants a mint.
If she says no,
then she is not interested.
She does not like him.
You can flirt with someone
to get what you want
And also be attracted to them.
How do you think
we got together?
'cause I stopped by your
desk like 15 times a day.
I was after your money.
Well, the joke was on you.
Yes, it was.
Can you stop micromanaging?
I know how to do this. - Okay.
Hey... What are you guys doing?
This girls was really
rude to me at the mall.
So I created a fake I.M. Account
From a hot guy at
her high school,
And now I'm trying
to make her anorexic.
Tell her everyone in home
room thinks she's fat.
Oh, that is so good.
You know, we should keep
practicing for this interview.
Oh, that's okay.
Ryan coached me.
Ryan? What does he know?
It's easy--you just turn every
question around on them.
Do you think you're
treated differently
Because of your race?
Would you ask that same
question if I was white?
We're so in.
"we"?
When I become executive,
I'm gonna make ryan manager.
And then the two of
us are cleaning house.
Kelly will be even
worse than darryl.
If you'd have told
me this morning
That today I'd be
creating a monster
Capable of my own destruction,
I'd have thought
you were referring
To the bull mose and I
are trying to reanimate.
So corporate approval
of this contract
Is contingent upon
buyer and seller...
- Mm-hmm.
- Obtaining blahdy blahdy blah.
Boilerplate. Pound of fish.
Just kidding. -
Do you like mints?
Yes.
I carry mints with me sometimes.
- You ever tried those?
- Oh, I haven't tried those.
- No.
- They're good.
You want one?
Sure.
It's like cool...
"certified cool."
I like how they say "certified."
Like there's some
consortium of...
Michael!
I'm sorry.
I can't stop myself
from kissing her.
Yeah, now you know how I feel
Sitting next to
those m&ms all day.
Well, why don't you
just move the m&ms?
Well, why don't you shut up!
Okay, guys, guys, guys.
Just tell me it's
not totally insane
To try one more time.
It is totally insane.
Michael, he's right.
You are turning into a stalker.
Okay. What do you think?
I think it's over, man.
Andy?
Ehh.
Okay, some for, some against.
- Nobody's for.
- Pam?
- Hmm?
- What do you think?
Um...
I think it's really,
really unlikely.
- Okay.
- Really unlikely.
But I can't say that
it's impossible.
What?
I'm not saying she's
in love with him.
But she could have
left a while ago.
Most printer sales are
done over the phone,
Ms. Boob shirt.
I'm going with Pam's group.
Wait.
- Here we go.
- Michael.
Michael. - Okay.
- No, guys, guys, guys.
Guys, just-
thank you for talking.
Wish me luck. - No.
What sort of movie would
rudy have been
If he had just stopped,
given up,
After two rejections?
Would have been a lot shorter.
Probably been a lot funnier.
But it would have ultimately
been a disappointment.
I still would have seen it,
But that's not...
The point.
- Kelly is disqualified!
- What?
You said the program is
not open to caucasians.
Well...
Anthropologically,
she is Indian.
Indians migrated from the
caucuses region of europe.
Therefore, technically,
she is caucasian.
You're welcome, america.
Yeah, but she's not white,
though.
Well, obviously,
she is brownish.
But, come on, I mean,
Darryl is far more ethnic.
Darryl withdrew his application.
He said the yale program
Interfered with his
softball league, you know?
He's gone.
I got my whole life to
be a minority executive.
I only have about a year
left in these knees, though.
Kelly is the only applicant.
Yeah, unless somebody
else applies today.
Namaste.
Oh, dear god.
Okay.
Don't make any
decisions just yet.
Okay? I'll be right back.
Hello.
That's very nice.
I never noticed that before.
Sometimes my bangs cover it.
Yeah. I don't want to
be offensive but, uh,
May I ask you what that means?
I do find that offensive,
actually.
We should have your
contract done by Thursday.
Oh, great.
Great, I will look out
for that stuff, then.
- Okay.
- And, um...
You know, I just wanted
to say it was really...
Really nice to do
business with you.
Yeah, it was nice to do
business with you too.
Thank you.
Did I...Get everything?
I don't know. I think so.
Yeah, I think so.
okay.
So--oh, donna? - Yeah?
Do you need validation?
We don't-- we don't validate.
No, it's just in the lot, so...
- Thank you so much.
- You're welcome.
You're...Welcome.
Mmm.
Bye.
Ahem. So, um...
Okay, if you have--
If there's any other
questions that you have...
I don't have, uh,
any other questions.
I'm just gonna...
Make my way down to--
All right. Bye.
Bye-bye!
And have a good elevator ride.
Okay.
Oh, what's that out there?
Michael, how did it go?
How would one of you feel
If I told you I could
put you on a fast track
To an executive position
at this company?
Holy cow. I'd be so happy.
I wasn't talking to you,
pale face.
I know. I meant I'd
be happy for them.
What I'm offering is a
ticket on a bullet train
Straight to middle management.
Dwight, I know these programs.
"every color is important
because, together,
We make a rainbow."
Yes.
I'll slap you in the
face with a rainbow.
Mm!
Speaking of rainbows,
Oscar...
You are kind of a
double minority.
Gay.
So we at sabre could really
benefit from your perspective.
Dwight, we know kelly applied.
We're not gonna cross her.
No matter how good
the program is.
I can protect you from kelly.
Will you get out of here?
Seriously.
For hobbies, um, yoga,
belly dancing,
Snake charming.
Beds of nails,
I like lying on them.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
This is hide tohsi hasagawa.
He would like to apply for
The sabre minority
executive training program
"print in all
colors" initiative.
Dwight, what are you doing?
Helping heal america
In a dramatic fashion
In the 11th hour.
God, I hate you so much!
Caucasians, am I right?
Have a seat. I'll translate.
Why? I don't need translator.
You don't know what
you need. Just...
Why don't you tell me a
little about yourself, hide.
In japan, heart surgeon,
number one.
Steady hand.
Hey, Michael. How you doing?
I don't know. I don't know.
Can't really trust
my feelings anymore.
You know what, Michael?
For what it's worth...
I was wrong too.
I thought she was
interested in you.
She suckered you too.
Mm-hmm.
Was it the cleavage?
Yeah, and the shoulder cutouts.
- Yep.
- Michael, you know,
It's easy to get fooled.
Bob's warehouse guys flirt
with me all the time.
It--it's mostly harmless.
Usually I don't
let it go too far.
You know, when I tore my scrote,
I was, uh...
I was seeing this really
hot urologist about it,
And thought she was into me.
But now I think she was
just doing a bunch of stuff
To bill my hmo.
You know...
She's touching
around down there.
It's easy to get confused.
Michael, I think
donna left this here.
Should I put it in the
lost and found for 14 days
And then I can take it home?
God.
She left this here? - Yeah.
Okay.
Maybe she wants me to return
this to her at her work.
What? All: No.
Yeah. This could be a signal.
People don't just
take barrettes off.
It's not a signal.
It's just a coincidence.
No, it's not even a coincidence.
It's just something
that happened.
- Michael...
- Well...
She doesn't want you
to return the barrette.
She's not interested in you.
Yeah, I know. I know.
- I'm sorry.
- I know. You're right.
Thank you.
Thanks, everybody.
Michael!
Oh. You're still here.
I have your baguette.
Everyone,
It is my pleasure to
announce our newest member
Of the sabre minority
executive training program,
Kelly rajanigandha kapoor.
All right.
They're going to be pretty
pleased in tallahassee
That I snagged an
Indian for the program.
She'll be the first.
The program's mostly black.
It's almost too black.
That didn't sound right.
And the best part is is that
I get a business stipend
To buy all new clothes.
So you can totally buy
any of my old clothes
That I'm not gonna need anymore.
Oh, my god, thank you so much.
I love that denim
jumpsuit you have.
How much? - Oh.
Actually, I was
thinking about clothes
That I was just gonna
give to goodwill anyway.
Great.
Hey, kiddo.
Congratulations are in order.
You deserve it.
- Thank you, dwight.
- Oh.
I'll never forget everything
that you've done for me.
Gosh. Heh heh.
Because I never forget anything.
Just once, I would like
to be a puppet master
And have nothing go wrong.
Is that too much to ask?
You know what? Everybody told me
That you weren't interested.
Everybody.
And I didn't believe 'em.
And they were right.
So...
There's your barrette.
No, y-you were...Right.
Who?
You were right.
About what?
I'm sorry.
No, no. No.
- I'm sor--
- no.
What happened?
Kelly got into the minority training program.
Really? O that's great.
That's such good news. I did it.
I kissed, We kissed
No, I am serious, th.. this happen.
I  was down at the parking lot, I was.. I returned her barrette.
ok we did, we did.
You know what? it doesn't matter because I know it happen
and that is all it counts.
I did do it.