This here is a radon test kit, I
will be putting them everywhere.
And, please dont throw these out.
(Fingers Snapping)
This is a radon test kit.
Please don't throw these out.
See them all over the office.
Toby has been leaving
radon kits everywhere,
Like he owns the place.
The first time I
threw mine away,
I thought it was an ant trap.
But I figured I'd
rather live with ants
Than with his
creepy little disk.
The second time...
I thought it was one of those,
You know, the things you
turn over, and it moos,
Like a cow thing.
But upon closer examination,
It was another ant trap,
so I threw it away.
And the third time...
I did it out of spite.
- Pfffttt!
- Come on, michael.
You're interrupting.
You're kidding me? God!
You say radon is
silent but deadly,
And then you expect me
Not to make farting
noises with my mouth?
What is this? - Please sit down.
You know, we're not
gonna die of radon.
We're gonna die of boredom.
Yeah!
Right?
And if I had a gun
with two bullets
And I was in a room with hitler,
bin laden, and toby,
I would shoot toby twice.
- No.
- No!
- That's not...
- Okay.
You were being really funny,
and then you went too far.
I would kill bin
laden and then toby.
- No, that's still...
- Mm-mm.
Okay, geniuses,
how would you do it?
Curve the bullet
Like in my favorite james mcavoy film,
wanted.
All that does is help
you shoot around things.
Is there a curtain
rod in the room?
- I don't know.
- How about make believe land
Has anything you want?
Stanley, please.
This is serious!
Is this the thing where
they use an icicle
So there's no evidence?
Yes. We stab toby through
the heart with an icicle.
Come on. The whole two bullet
thing is a red herring.
Here's how you do it.
You line them all up,
you take one bullet,
Shoot them all through the
throat at the same time.
Watch this.
Phyllis, you're hitler.
Come up here. Toby, you're toby.
Andy, you're bin laden. Line up.
I don't wanna do this.
Throats together.
toby, just do it!
- Toby, come on.
- God!
Ready? One bullet.
And...Boom!
Puuuhhh!
Puuuhh!
- Yeah, that works.
- That works.
Good work.
What flavors did you get?
It's so exciting, pam.
The eagles are doing
a theme of ice creams
In honor of turning 60.
"despera-dough.
Witchy-womanilla."
Why do they do this?
Do you want me to go
back to the store?
No, no, no, it's fine.
I was just commenting.
We gotta get these out,
open 'em up.
This is all for michael.
Turns out his
girlfriend was married.
Yeah. And when michael
gets a broken heart,
This whole place
comes to a halt,
So we're just trying to
get out in front of this.
After his last breakup,
He ate 40,000 calories
in three hours.
Right, pam?
That's what pam told me.
Yeah. Or no--well--
I don't know. I'm sorry.
I was up all night with cece,
Otherwise I'd be running this.
That's okay.
You probably shouldn't keep
a baby up that late, though.
We have mr. Bean playing in
the conference room
And the pink panther movie
in his office
With half-hour shifts
to watch with him.
And we need bodies in
both these rooms, people,
So please sign up.
- He's coming.
- Oh. Okay.
Everyone, remember,
when he gets like this,
He will wallow if you empathize.
Keep conversations light
And if you get stuck and
you don't know what to do,
Make a random sound
effect, okay?
Farting noise, whatever.
Okay.
- Hey, everyone.
- No, toby!
- No! Out!
- Get out right now!
- Leave now.
- Leave. Get outta here.
- Please!
- Right now.
Oh, and if he makes a joke,
Just laugh it up,
no matter what.
Okay?
Morning, everyone.
Hey!
- Hey!
- Hey.
Hello. - Michael.
Nice tie or something.
Oh, thank you.
It's reversible, I think.
- That's hilarious.
- That's awesome.
You want some ice cream?
Oh--oh, wow!
Are those eagles' flavors?
Cake it to the limit.
That's my favorite.
I love that.
Too much for me
to have by myself.
Anybody wanna share?
Boi-oi-oi-oing!
Okay. Well...That's random.
I will dig into those later.
I don't follow this exactly.
Uh, "the descendants of any
replicants from this union
Shall have"--
Joint custody.
Are we talking about
your grandchildren?
- No.
Rather than spend
all day in court,
We've decided to
settle our dispute
Using a mediator.
It was an option spelled out
In our child-rearing
contract and...
- Alleged contract.
- Alleged?
I'm going to own your farm
by the time this is over.
Pff. Yeah, just try.
I will do legal jujitsu on you.
- Oh, yeah--
- gaah!
See? Don't even need
to make contact.
The law will do it.
So much of this is just
impossible to verify.
Item five, point "b"-- uh,
the beet juice cleanse.
I'm doing it. You know I am.
It's disgusting!
How do we know this?
I'd like to see a stool sample.
Dwight, look at my teeth.
Eh.
No secret crying.
Hasn't even opened the
tissue box in there.
Could he still be seeing her?
I don't think he'd do that.
So we're gonna say the
most likely scenario
Is that michael
matured overnight?
Well, it happened to tom
hanks in big.
Exactly. It happened in big.
No, I gotta go. Text me later.
I'm really too tired to do this.
- Me too!
- Then let's just not do this!
Do you have any idea
the risks involved?
- Hey, michael.
- Hey.
We were wondering if
you'd like to have
Dinner with us
tonight in our home
And play with our baby.
We could order in from hooters.
Oh, hooters to go. Nice.
We can watch a movie.
And play rock band.
- Billy joel rock band.
- That...Exists?
Yes.
Okay, well, I'll have
to take a rain check,
But thanks for the offer.
Michael scott,
are you still seeing donna?
Okay, pam...
She's not invisible,
so stop asking silly questions.
Oh, michael.
Since when is this an office
Where we delve into each
other's personal lives?
I like donna.
Is it wrong to keep seeing her?
Depends on who you ask.
I mean, if you ask
her husband...
Or you took a random poll,
yeah, it's wrong.
That is something
I would never do.
Well, I think we all know
What you're capable of,
meredith.
Hey, I have never cheated on,
been cheated on,
Or been used to cheat with.
I ask...Everyone in the room,
"are you in a relationship?"
People, this is scranton,
And many people
consider that to be
The paris of northeastern
pennsylvania.
And in paris,
It is rude for a woman to
have less than four lovers.
Uhh! Ryan, I do not want you
Hanging out with
michael anymore.
Okay.
Okay, I will have you know
that I asked donna about this,
And she is fine with it,
And just to be sure,
I asked her again afterward.
Same answer. - How
does he feel about it?
He is never gonna find out.
He is a high school
baseball coach.
He wakes up early.
He goes to bed early.
Look at how long it took
for him to find out.
It was right under his nose.
I had to tell him!
Now you're just being hurtful.
I'm sorry, it-- why is it okay
For stanley to cheat
or for phyllis to cheat
- Hey--
- on...Her diet?
He's a sports guy. He's scummy.
Dogfighting, drugs. They spit.
Did donna tell you that?
Real sports with bryant gumbel.
So you're just making
a giant assumption.
You don't even know the guy.
You know what?
You know what? I am declaring
a moment of silence right now.
Ten minutes of silence
honoring michael jackson.
Just sit there and think
about michael jackson.
My name is andy bernard,
and I'm a cuckold.
For those of you unfamiliar
with william shakespeare,
A cuckold is a man whose
woman is cheating on him.
I've lived the part.
And let me tell you,
I would so much rather...
Play the part on stage.
So...Here's the thing
about infidelity.
Mm, no, no.
When are you people
going to stop casting
The first stone?
I am not in the wrong here.
I am the good guy.
How does that work?
Do you think this husband
is a super sweet nice guy?
Do you think he's an angel?
I don't think so.
Why is his wife going off
And having a little
something-something with me?
There has to be a
problem with him.
In any cheating movie,
The person getting
cheated on is the hero.
You're ali larter. I'm beyonce.
I am beyonce always.
- Not this time.
- Yes, I am.
This guy's a high school
baseball coach, right?
Let's go check him out,
See what a horrible
person he is.
- I would love that.
- Yeah.
Those teams have games
and practices every day.
Let's go check it out.
I have work to do.
Oh, really? I thought
you were the boss.
Let's go.
I can't wait to see this jerk
Who is making me
cheat on his wife.
Should punch him in the nose
For what he's
making me do to her.
* bum bum bum bum *
* bum bum bum bum * - all right,
andy, please.
- Baseball!
- Shh!
Try not to draw attention,
please.
That's him. That's him.
- Where?
- Right there. The coach!
Stage right or stage left?
I played batboy in
damn yankees!
Right there. Look, look.
Follow my finger. Okay? See?
The grownup by the base?
and now, coaching third base
With two arms, two legs,
and no heart.
Capable of feeling pain.
All right.
Can you just--
Can you just act normal
for a second, please?
Whatever.
I'm the one blending in.
Guys?
- Pam.
- Mm. Hey.
Oh, hi, gabe.
Can you two please
join me in my office?
Now.
You were supposed
to be the lookout.
Yeah. Well,
it's really warm in here.
It's like a sleeping bag.
I don't wanna be the heavy here,
But honestly, guys,
this makes us all look bad.
- Sorry about that.
- So embarrassing.
Good. Okay.
End of the dressing down.
I just hate that part
of the job, you know,
The power dynamics.
Well, you were
surprisingly restrained.
We will be well-rested tomorrow.
Okay. That's great, actually,
Because I wanted to talk to
you about something else.
Excellent. Go for it.
I'm sure you got my email
about the printer fires.
The one with the
branching decision tree?
I actually designed that chart.
Kinda hoping it catches on.
Anyway, the question is,
What is the best way
To disseminate important
information in an efficient way?
Right? So, uh, let's, uh...
Finally there's a provision here
In the occurrence that the
child is born an old man,
A la benjamin button.
- Same page.
- Same page. Go to the next one.
Just keep moving.
Despite the provision covering
Whether this is all
part of the matrix--
Which we can't know.
- This is essentially...
- Unless we're unplugged.
Equivalent to a donor
or surrogate contractor.
And wake up in the future.
Which is actually pretty common.
So I have to tell you that
this is a solid contract.
What?
Look, I can't enforce
That anybody have a
child with anyone else.
- What?
- So essentially,
This comes down to damages.
Now, there is some precedence
for the range of $30,000.
What?
I don't have $30,
000 lying around.
I have it buried very deeply,
And I don't want to dig past
a certain someone to get it.
Chase dixon is up.
Could be a big play.
You have no idea what
you're talking about.
I know it's like cricket.
- You don't. No, no.
- And it's--there's--
Well, home plate
is like a wicket.
- You don't know. You don't-
- you don't know anything.
Look at him.
Look at him over there.
High-fiving?
He didn't even do anything.
Kid did all the work.
I bet he does that at home.
I bet it's like, "hey, donna,
why don't you wash the dishes?
"high-five, donna.
"hey, why don't you
bring me my slippers?
High-five. I'm taking
all the credit."
Seems pretty well
liked by the team.
Okay, well, that's because
he's paying their salary.
You do know that
high school coaches
Don't pay their players.
I know, I know, I know.
It--I'm--it-
that was a euphemism.
$30,000? There's
gotta be another way.
He has a 60-acre beet farm
that is worth a small fortune.
Look, I will not pay.
Well, I have an alternative.
"intercourse to completion.
Five individual times
rendered at my discretion"?
Look, I don't think
that's actually legal.
Agreed.
Five times for $30,000?
Not a bad stud fee.
Better than most horses.
But not in your bed. It's lumpy.
Those lumps are cats,
and those cats have names,
And those names are ember,
milky way, diane, and lumpy.
Fine. Five times.
Look, I can't legally
watch this unfold.
It's coming a little dangerously
close to prostitution.
- I want eye contact.
- No.
- Yes.
- Do you understand
How rare that is in nature?
I'm not some farm animal.
Great game, coach.
Shh! Okay, all right.
Don't--don't--
You guys are awesome!
Best game I've ever
seen in my life.
Yeah, right. You must be
rootin' for the other guys.
Ha. The other guys can go die.
- okay.
- Baseball!
Go talk to him. - No.
God. You go talk to him.
- Let's go.
- Shane.
Great game, man.
Do I know you?
No. Uh, just big fans.
Both of us.
Are somebody's...Parents?
Oh, are you guys...
Kenny's dads?
Ha. No. No.
But we're gay for baseball.
- Okay.
- But I have a wife, actually,
Who I really love a lot. - Okay.
Yeah.
I am so into the
institution of marriage.
Whoa!
I mean, isn't marriage
the best, you know?
Two good people
finding each other,
Getting all committed
to each other.
So you love baseball.
What else do you love?
Let's round you out as a person.
Hey, I'm really sorry,
I'm just trying to...
Focus here on the game.
I get it, man. I love it.
That's what makes
you a good coach.
You know, but as a fan,
it just helps me
Enjoy the game better if I
know the coach loves his wife.
Of course. Okay? I gotta...
Get back to this.
- Of course.
- All right.
But real quick, I want
you to meet my associate.
Sheldon! - No, no, no.
- Come on, get over here.
- I'm good.
Oh, my god. - Get over here.
Sheldon, say hi
to the nice coach.
Sorry. I got some
stomach cramps.
It's all right, all right,
just keep it going!
Well, that was not at
all what I expected.
Hoo hoo!
Whoo. My heart's still racing.
I just looked a man in the
eyes and I shook his hand.
All the time I was thinking,
"I'm sleeping with your wife."
And you know who does that?
James freakin' bond.
Okay, orange slices.
There ya go. - Thanks, michael.
Don't thank me.
Thank dylan's mom.
Here you go! Oh!
Ooh hoo hoo hoo hoo!
Why would you throw
something wet at me?
You love it. There ya go.
Now, were those for the team?
Uh, no, they didn't say team.
They just said coal hawks.
- Ah.
- I don't think those
Were yours to take.
Well, then it wouldn't
be the first time
I stole something
away from coach shane.
I just wanna go on
record as saying
That I do not
condone this affair,
And I even went so far
As to force michael to confront
the victim of his behavior.
- Did you talk to him?
- I did.
You talked to the man
Whose wife you're
having an affair with.
- Wow. That is crazy.
- Was there a fistfight?
No. We just talked.
He's very nice.
And it didn't change your mind.
- It did not.
- Michael, that's awful.
- Isn't it?
- Yes.
- I'm awful, aren't I?
- Yeah.
That's pretty bad.
I'm an awful guy! Ooh!
How can you live with yourself?
I am what I am, oscar.
And I want what I want.
And right now,
I want a piece of cake.
From now on, when I'm hungry,
I am going to eat
whatever I am hungry for.
That is a dangerous game,
friendo.
Well, because I thought
that it was a book
About anthropology the store.
I don't know why you were in
that part of the bookstore.
'cause it's next to the
baby section, okay?
All right,
that makes more sense.
You should have said
that at the beginning
When you said, " I read a
book about anthropology."
I don't really know why you're
screaming at me right now.
- I'm not scream-
- I'm not screaming.
That's meredith's cake.
It's her birthday.
I don't care.
I have an appetite for life!
Mmm.
Mmm! Oh, god.
That's lemon.
Good for you, man.
Good for you.
He takes what he wants.
You know what?
I think you're attractive,
and I wanna sleep with you.
What about kelly?
You read my mind.
is this a joke?
Yep.
It's hard to live that way, man.
You gotta really not care
what people think about you.
I-I don't know how
you do it, michael,
I-I-I can't be that cold.
You'll learn, baby.
You'll learn.
I am an honorable man,
and I will honor the contract.
But I don't have to
give her the good stuff.
Schrute sperm are strong,
But they're no match for
a grown schrute man.
let's see what she gets.
aah!
Uh, boss, we're out of paper.
- Yeah, I noticed that.
- Are you gonna add any more?
Nope.
He don't give an
"f" about nothin'!
I have got big balls.
I don't think I'm gonna make it.
what about an energy
drink or something?
It gets in the breast milk.
If I drink it, cece
drinks it six hours later.
Well, it doesn't mean
I can't drink it.
Well, it does and it doesn't.
Probably shouldn't
tell you this,
But a lotta guys
in the warehouse
Work multiple jobs,
so... We have a place.
- A place?
- A restful location.
Talk to glen. He'll
take you up in the lift.
You sleep in the warehouse?
Lightbulb's burnt out,
so it's dark.
And the heat from
the backup generator
Keeps it nice and warm.
Sometimes I think about it
When I'm trying to
fall asleep at home.
But as far as the rest
of the office goes,
It doesn't exist, okay?
- Okay.
- Pam.
Okay.
- For your signature.
- Okay.
Phyllis.
Okay. Look at me.
Phyllis, look at--
Okay, that's...
All right, all right.
You know what? I'm sick of this.
I'm sick of the little
disapproving head shakes.
If you think that's going
to have any effect on me,
It will not.
I am going to leave right now
And go to a motel to meet donna.
Why not your condo?
Because a motel is
dirty and it is sexy.
Like me. And like donna.
And frankly,
the stuff that we're into
Isn't very condo-appropriate.
Oh, michael, will you drop it?
Everybody's spoken their mind,
And no one's
changing their mind.
Okay, morgan
freeman-narrating-everything.
Do you want someone to stop you?
'cause no one's going to.
Nobody better try to stop me.
Good.
I could have stopped him.
- Are you warmed up?
- No.
God, angela, why is that
always my responsibility?
What did you do to yourself?
Never mind. Just never mind.
- Well, it better work.
- Oh, it'll work.
Mm. Stop kissing me.
It's not in the contract.
How do I feel about
breaking up with donna?
Good. Moral. I feel proud.
like a grownup.
That was not easy because
I really liked her a lot.
And I'm a little bit
emotional right now
Because I know that I absolutely
Made the right decision.
At the end of the day,
we have to do what's right.
And it was either
living with myself
Or...Being happy.
And I picked...
The...
Former.
- Michael scott?
- Yes?
Do you wanna make a
comment on the rumors?
um...
I have done some
very bad things,
Things of which I am not proud.
I would like to publicly apologize to..
the coach and the players.
and I vow to never listen to
my bodily instincts ever again.
I am talking the Sabra printers
that catch on fire.
Oh! ok. I was talking about the..
What the.. What's going on?