Everybody, can I please
have your attention?
Ryan and I have a huge announcement.
Oh my gosh.
Wow.
Over the weekend,
Ryan Bailey Howard and I got divorced.
- Sweet.
- Free ring.
Divorced?
Just so you know, it's totally amicable.
We're fine.
We don't need people here
to take sides.
The last thing that we want
is any kind of drama.
Wait, I...
Can you back up?
What's the story?
We were having a beautiful
weekend in the Poconos.
We were making love constantly.
We saw the sun rise,
and Ryan was crying a lot.
- That's not a relevant detail.
- And in the morning,
we walked by a chapel
and we stopped suddenly,
and Ryan said...
Both: "I don't think I should
be married to you anymore."
Wait, wha...
Sorry, when did you get married?
Um, like a week ago.
We got really wasted,
and it just felt right.
And you didn't invite any of us?
We are getting divorced, Andy!
This is such a raw time.
God, baby, you know,
with people's reactions to this,
I wonder if we made a mistake.
No, with the messed-up laws
in this country,
I don't want to be married
until everyone can be married.
You know what, Ryan?
I talked to the other gay guys,
and we're okay with it.
We all agreed it's fine
for you to get married.
No. No, Oscar.
Not... not until
everyone can.
Ryan, I changed my mind.
Okay, fine.
You know what?
This actually
isn't amicable at all,
and we actually do need people
to take sides.
Who's on my side?
And who is on my side?
[Upbeat music]
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
All right, bye.
- Bye.
- Let's go.
Just a minute!
- How long do we have to wait?
- For what?
You broke up with A.J. weeks ago.
Don't you have
a sales call to go on?
I don't understand.
I really don't, I mean...
We know we're gonna
start dating... Why not now?
- We don't know that.
- Sure we do.
Why is it such a certainty
that we're supposed
to be together?
Why does the sun
rise in the morning?
Why do magnets stick together?
Because everybody says so.
Everybody.
Michael, I can't keep getting
into a situation
where I date
whoever I'm working with.
Well you can
understand that.
Yeah, I understand.
I just don't agree.
Well, you don't have to agree.
Yes, I do.
No, you don't.
No, you can have
your own opinion...
I have my own opinion,
and my opinion
is to disagree with you.
He's gonna be a lot of fun
to drive around in a car with.
Ah, you'll get through it, hon.
Just make a game out of it.
A funny Jim game.
That's it?
That's all I get?
Even after all the hard work
I put into
celebrating your talent today.
All right, what'd you do?
Well, those things
that you consider doodles
I consider art.
Where'd you put it?
- Where'd I put what?
- Let's go.
Oh, sorry.
I gotta go.
- Say it. Where?
- Okay, fine.
Three hints: One,
when you're getting colder,
you're really getting warmer.
- The fridge.
- Two!
You have a better chance
if you think Bob Vance.
The fridge, got it.
- And the final clue...
- Let's go!
You know what?
Just think about it.
- You'll be fine.
- [Laughs] Bye.
[Door slams]
Holly is ruining Michael's life.
He thinks she's so special.
And she's so not.
Her personality is like a three,
her sense of humor is a two,
her ears are like a seven
and a four.
Add it all up,
and what do you get?
16.
And he treats her
like she's a perfect 40.
It's nuts.
Cheer up.
We made a sale.
Just drive faster.
I wanna get back.
Well, I'm going the speed limit.
Okay, fine.
My feelings don't matter to you.
What matters to you
is your precious speed limit.
Someone's in a bad mood.
No, I'm not.
I'm not in a bad mood.
I'm not, Jim.
Hello?
Okay, fine, ignore me.
Have it your way.
Let's just talk about you.
As always.
Sex different
after the baby, Jim?
All right, let me
turn on some music.
- I need to pee!
- No, you don't.
Yeah, I do.
My word against yours.
All right, well,
we'll be there in ten minutes.
What part of "I need to pee"
do you not understand?
I'm upset, my bladder is full,
there is no telling
what I might do, right now,
all over the inside of your
precious little car.
All right, well,
if I see a gas station,
- I'll pull over.
- Well, I hope I make it.
[Cell phone ringing]
Hello?
Hi, Jim, it's Helene.
Hey, Helene.
Is everything okay?
Everything's fine.
Baby's fine.
She has a tiny fever.
I'm taking her for a checkup.
Nothing to worry about, uh...
Okay.
A tiny thing.
I locked her in the car.
- What?
- She's smiling. She's happy.
- Oh, my God.
- Jim, I... Jim...
- I don't have a spare key.
Just... just stay there.
I'll be there in one second.
Michael!
Excuse me, sir, there's a...
There's a guy in the bathroom.
He's coming out,
but I have to go,
'cause it's an emergency.
Will you just tell him
to call the office?
Just call...
Call the office.
Thank you! Please?
[Engine starts]
[Tires screeching]
Hello?
[Engine starts]
[Toilet flushes]
[Phone ringing]
- This is Pam.
- Hey, it's me.
So, uh, don't worry.
Everything's okay.
- What's wrong?
- Nothing, absolutely nothing.
But you're not holding a cup of
coffee or anything, are you?
- Jim, what?
- Uh...Okay.
So Cece had a little bit
of a fever.
And your mom also
locked her in the car.
- Oh, God. What?
- No, no, no, it's okay.
So Cece's with daddy now,
and she is laughing
and she's happy,
and we're on our way
to see Dr. Barbara.
Okay, so she's okay?
Yes, and your mom got
a very well-deserved day off.
So here's the thing, though.
I left Michael at the gas station
on Bennett.
Understood.
And his wallet and phone are
on the seat next to him.
Got it.
I will put out an A.P.B.
otherwise known as
an "Ask Pam Beasley."
Did the phone cut out?
Nope.
All right, just call me
after the doctor.
- Okay.
- All right, bye.
Bye.
I know, I know.
You have a phone policy.
I understand.
But this is an emergency,
because my friend isn't here,
and I'm worried
that he has been abducted.
- No.
- And... and...
No, he ditched you, man.
I saw him drive away.
There's no way he ditched me.
There's no way that happened.
He's my... Okay.
May I please just
use your phone? Please.
Just make it quick.
[Whispers]
Thank you. Okay.
I will make it quick.
I will make it very quick.
And you don't have my numbers
on speed dial.
Aah, okay, what is it?
You don't know.
- Oh, co... come...
- You don't.
You know what?
I could dial 411,
get Jim's number...
He left you here
on purpose, all right?
I saw it.
He just drove away.
Actually, this is good.
I am going
to take this opportunity
to go walkabout.
Good, good.
No, get away.
No. That's enough.
Okay.
It's the gas station
on Bennett Street?
Yeah.
You know what?
Why don't you stay and I'll go?
Oh, no, no, no, I'll be fine.
It's kind of a sketchy
neighborhood, though.
I better come along.
Problem solved, everyone.
Space Orphan
and Princess Nincompoop
are off to rescue Michael.
Unbelievable.
I'm going.
You drive.
I got a car full of fox meat.
[Sniffs]
Cute.
Very funny, everyone.
Who wrote captions
under my doodle?
I'm not even kidding.
They're pretty good.
- Which one in particular?
- Yeah, which one?
Well, the first one
has a surprise factor.
"I'm a suck-suck-suckety Sabre."
Boo-yah!
[Laughter]
No. No, no.
No, no, no.
But, uh, I suppose the second one
is the better written line.
- You suppose?
- What's it say?
"I'm supposed
to be wearing red gloves,
but my color cartridge portal
got jammed again."
Okay, no, no, no, no, no.
[Laughs]
Gloves.
Keep it real.
You guys, if I knew you
wanted to do a caption contest,
I would have drawn
something more challenging.
- And I will take you all down.
- You?
I been reading
the comics to my daughter
since she was three years old.
Not once have I used the real
captions to Family Circus.
That crazy family is hilarious
to her for one reason...
Me.
Oh, it is on
like Genghis Khan
wearing Sean John in Bhutan.
Yes. You guys,
I have the perfect idea.
Okay, it'll just
take me ten minutes.
- Whoo-hoo!
- All right.
I want to do it.
Male, Caucasian, 40s, black hair,
facial type marsupial.
He answers to Michael,
Michael G. Scott,
Michael J. Fox, Mr. Fox,
the Incredible Mr. Fox.
- Yeah, he just left.
- Which way did he go?
Hey, hey, hey, hey,
let me answer this.
Stupid question.
He went back to the office,
obviously, which is that way.
Oh, really?
You don't think
he walked by that bakery
just for the smell of it?
She's right.
He went that way.
All right.
Don't get a swelled head.
You're no tracker.
Let's ride.
[Puppies barking]
Hey, you guys.
Listen to me.
Don't get hung up
on just one girl,
because there are a lot
of other girls over there.
Look over there.
See?
They look cute.
[Imitates parrot]
Hello.
You guys are so beautiful.
You're so colorful.
I wish I could understand you.
That's a metaphor, I guess.
You are disgusting.
You'll never find love.
Lecch.
Do you think she needs more time,
or it's just never gonna happen?
I'm being serious.
Seriously.
Dunder Mifflin.
This is Pam.
Has Michael checked in?
- Oh, hey, Dwight.
- I asked you a question.
- No, he hasn't.
- Okay, bye.
No, wait, um, hey,
while you're out,
could you pick up some paper
towels and chocolate syrup?
We have ice cream,
so I thought we could...
Pam, this isn't a shopping trip.
This is a manhunt-slash-rescue
mission.
Okay, I just...
When you're done,
or any time it's convenient,
I just thought
since you're out...
Pam, I'm obviously
gonna get that stuff for you,
so just shut up.
God.
Okay, well, it wasn't ob...
[Dial tone]
No word from Michael.
[Sighs]
Tada.
Okay, it's two giant dogs
with two giant palm trees
on a regular-sized island.
- Oh, I got one.
- Yeah?
- Yes.
- Okay, I'm sorry,
but I'm gonna have
to shut this down.
- Boo.
- Why?
Unless we can all agree
to some ground rules.
It's either that
or I can fax this to Jo
and let her decide
how to proceed.
Gabe, tell us your stupid rules
so we can start the game.
Number one,
and this should be obvious,
no captions that insult
the company we work for.
Irony is such a critical...
Number two,
no pop culture references.
- Seriously?
- Wow.
I think we can all agree
they tend to alienate those
who don't get the reference,
making them feel like the other.
Wrap it up, Gabe.
Okay, final thing,
and this is a fun one,
instead of writing the caption
directly under the picture,
let's all try using sticky quips.
All right?
New from Dunder Mifflin-Sabre.
Sticky quips are fun,
they're safe, they're handy.
I like to use sticky quips
as regular post-it notes
when I'm in a fun mood.
[Laughs]
Not every day.
Go get 'em.
Start quipping.
[Everyone muttering]
Pam, I think
I'm gonna send you an I.M.
Oh, okay.
Send me one too.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, put me on that.
- C.C.
- Ditto.
Hello.
I would like a hot dog, please.
Now, I don't have any money,
so here is what
I would like to do.
I leave you here with my watch,
and I come back later
and I pay for the hotdog.
I'm not a pawn shop.
Well, I understand that,
but this is a $45 watch.
Wow.
With that, I could buy...
Half the menu.
I can't just go
giving away hotdogs.
All right.
What do you do with the hotdogs
that you don't sell?
Throw 'em away.
Well, okay, instead of
throwing them all away later,
why don't you just throw
one away now into my mouth.
No.
Okay.
You've just lost my business.
Hey.
Hey, you were in there forever.
There's too many brands.
Where's Holly?
She wandered off like an idiot.
- Hey.
What are you doing?
Oh, just changing
my cell phone plan.
Okay. Okay.
Here you go.
I'll take my free
stress ball too now.
Sure thing.
Here you go, miss...
Okay, Fanny Smellmore.
- Real original.
- What?
You know what? Say hi
to Orville Tootenbacher for me.
Tootenbacher.
Orville Tootenbacher,
that's Michael's
millionaire character that...
Both:
Farts popcorn.
Of course. He was here.
She's the key. Amazing.
Holly.
Hey, where would you
like to go next?
Holly?
Are their egg rolls
really that big?
Oh, boy.
That was yummy.
Thank you so much.
You know what? I think
I left my wallet in my car.
Do you mind
if I run out and get it?
- No problem.
- Okay.
I'll be right back.
[Sighs]
Okay, you know what?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I don't have my wallet.
And I was...
I was gonna try to dine and dash,
and that was stupid,
and I realize I can't do that
to you fine people.
So you can't pay for your food?
Well, I can, but I will have
to come back later tonight
and pay you.
But the point is
I did the right thing.
You did not.
You have no money,
but you dined,
and you dined so much.
Well, the number three
is not such a giant feast.
Mr. Chu!
Okay, all right.
You know what?
You're trying
to steal food from us?
I am not.
I just have had a bad day,
and I...
Okay.
I'll be back later
with the money.
I'm just gonna leave right now.
You can't.
We'll stop you.
Well, I think
I can get through the door.
Excuse me.
Do you speak English?
We are looking for a man,
Michael, this tall,
black hair, Caucasian.
[Gasps]
It's Michael!
He just left.
- You knew!
- What?
No. Dwight asked
if I wanted an egg roll.
What... What are you
implying?
Uncanny.
Put a pin in that.
Which way did he go?
That guy!
When he leave here,
which way did he go?
We looking for him.
This way, this way, this way?
I don't know.
Do you know?
I think he was heading downtown.
He's heading downtown.
So what, no one's even gonna try?
- Guess not.
- Oh, come on.
My rules could not possibly
have been that oppressive.
You crushed our spirits, Gabe.
Congrats.
You're a big man, huh?
Takes a lot to destroy
the creativity
of a whole group of people.
[Notification tone]
[Laughter]
Hey...
[Clicking]
[Whispers] Click the "x".
- [Whispers] I'm clicking!
- In the box.
I am clicking.
Woman, you've had
a computer for years!
- Phyllis!
- Too late!
Oh. Ha.
An I.M. chat.
Very clever.
I'll just print that out.
Come on, guys.
Grow up.
I don't want to be
your babysitter.
Ooh.
"Darn it, Bob,
I told you not to buy
a Sabre brand lifeboat."
[Laughter]
- Nice!
- No, not nice.
Terrible.
Doesn't even include
the fact that they're dogs.
- Do the next one.
- "Wake up, Fred.
"The power cord
on your Sabre printer
"shocked you into a coma,
and you're dreaming you're a dog
on a desert island."
Dreaming he's a dog on an island.
Uh, excuse me, excuse me.
How does the speaker know what
the guy in the coma is dreaming?
Well, if you think
it's so easy, Gabe,
- why don't you try it?
- Um...
You don't have to sniff
my rear end anymore, Bob.
I'm the only one here.
Ha.
That's tasteless, Gabe.
- Tasteless?
- Tasteless.
More tasteless than this?
"Is that a palm tree,
"or did Gabe get skinner?
Either way, let's pee on it.
[Laughter]
Ladies and gentlemen,
I think we have a winner.
- Yes.
- Yes. Well done!
Whose is it?
Who wrote that?
Yeah.
Who wrote it?
Please. It was easy
once I decided
I wanted the dog to piss on Gabe.
Where did he go, Holly?
I have no idea.
Do you see a little clown
that you wanna follow, huh?
Is there a little bird
that's chirping to you,
"this way, this way."
I don't know.
Okay. Close your eyes.
We need you to think.
What is Michael seeing right now?
Can you tell him
that we miss him?
Michael, we're coming for you!
Will you stop?
There have been
a few coincidences...
That's all!
All right, then.
- Someone propose a plan.
- Okay.
- We fan out...
- Not you, Erin.
Stop looking at me like that.
Okay, look, let's just
go up somewhere high
and see if we could spot him
on the street below.
That is the stupidest idea
I've ever heard. No.
Tap into your common mind and
tell us what he would do next.
Look, I'm not playing.
I'm gonna go look for him.
- Good. We don't need her.
- Right.
I can do this on my own.
I can think like Michael.
All right...
I'm deep below the ocean's
surface in a submarine.
A torpedo's coming right at me.
No. Damn it, that's just
my own imagination.
Maybe he's bowling.
Michael?
Hi.
[Laughs]
How did you know I was up here?
What are you doing up here?
I got turned around.
I thought I could see
Dunder Mifflin.
Dunder Mifflin?
Yeah.
[Laughs]
Wow!
I just miss you so much.
I missed you too.
Really?
Yeah.
Can I kiss you?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Maybe that's not the best one.
Keep reading.
- Yeah, it was.
- Maybe it wasn't.
Oh, thank God, I had a horrible nightmare
that I was stuck in America with Gabe.
[Laughs]
No, that's not the one I was thinking of.
Keep going.
I know what it smells like
but I didn't roll in anything,
It's from listening
to all of Gabe's bullshit.
Isn't this the perfect
romantic getaway, Erin?
Sitting on a desert island
in dog costumes?
I'm Gabe and... I'm a weirdo.
[Laughs]
Gabe's mom...
Mm, Gabe's mom?
Wait, tall woman?
Looks like Gabe?
Yeah, I banged her.
Yeah, there you go.