Oh, a little help.
Wow, your hair is really thinning.
Standing as proven
to be healthier
increases productivity
and just looks cooler.
Picture someone doing
something heroic.
Now, was he sitting
or standing?
Not counting FDR.
Every second you sit there
is an hour off your life.
Look at all of you.
I feel like you're
in suicide cult.
No, no, no.
You're way off on that one.
Are you really comfortable
standing there?
I tried one of those,
and I just couldn't find
the sweet spot.
Hey, guys,
let's just all admit it, okay?
Dwight's better than us.
He had the guts
to stop sitting,
and he's never, ever
gonna go back on it, right?
That's right, Jim.
- Hey, man.
- Hey.
Taking a load off, huh?
No. Putting a load on,
more like.
Good luck with that.
Last thing I need is luck.
Thank you so much.
What are you up to?
Oh, look out.
- Just-- What are you doing?
- Too fast. Ha ha!
- Give that back. Come on.
- Prank!
Oh, that's real creative.
You know what, you're right.
It's not my best.
'Cause you could easily
just bend over
and pick that up, right?
I could, I just don't
feel like a loser.
- Because you're sitting?
- Standing.
- Okay.
- Don't!
- Because you're sitting?
- Standing.
You know I have to do this.
I know.
Whoaaa!
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Andrew...Baines...Bernard.
I think you can just
do it with "Andy Bernard."
Andrew Baines Bernard.
I love filling these out
'cause it's like, oh,
I'm taking a test,
but I know the answers.
In four seconds,
my wife is going to be
coming through that door.
I told her she could work here.
Under no circumstances
can that be allowed to happen.
There you are.
Honey...
How on earth did you miss
the elevator?
What was that?
I don't know.
He wasn't talking to me.
But if I were you,
I wouldn't hire his wife.
That's why my foundation,
the Dream For A Wish Foundation,
is gonna put them
out of business.
They're not gonna know
what hit 'em.
Everyone...
I'd like to introduce
my wife, Mrs. Robert California.
Mrs. California,
this is everyone.
- Hello.
- Hi.
- Welcome.
- Call me Susan, please.
Last night at dinner,
Susan and I were talking
about her returning to work.
So she's here today to see
if there's a good fit.
Something tells me
it just might work out.
This is Andy Bernard,
the regional manager.
- Hello. Nice to meet you.
- Hey there.
It's a pleasure.
Welcome.
Thank you.
Andy, would you be so kind
as to show Susan
around the office,
introduce her
to various departments,
find a place
where she'll shine?
I would love to,
but I have to be
completely honest
with you guys.
We're 100% staffed up.
Andy, let's see if there's
a good fit first,
then we'll talk.
All right.
♪ Knock knock knock
knock knock knock ♪
You don't have to say it
if you're doing it.
Remember how you said
that you were looking
for a place in the office
to do calisthenics
and aerobics?
Uh, weight lifting, yeah.
Well, today's your lucky day.
I have opened,
in this very office building,
Dwight Schrute's gym
for muscles.
- Wanna take a look?
- I'll take a look.
Your path from obesity
begins right here.
I've been meaning
to join a gym...For my health.
I used to say I wanted
to live long enough
to see a black president.
I never realized
how easy that would be.
So now I want to live
long enough
to see a really,
really gay president
or a supermodel president.
I want to see all the different
kinds of presidents.
Obese people
in my office building
are a drain on resources.
Chairs wear out faster.
It takes more freon
to keep them cool.
They flush the toilets
more often.
Plus, their massive BMS
bust the rivets on my pipes.
But a gym turns fat into cash.
All right, the DM express
is pulling out.
All right, well, it's really
nice to meet you, Brian.
Uh, it's actually Ryan.
- Oh, Ryan.
- Yeah.
Bitch.
We will start here
at Erinville.
- Hi.
- Reception.
You're classic
one-man operation.
Although,
I was watching a movie,
and Meryl Streep had
two secretaries.
I was watching a movie,
and a bunch of apes
took over San Francisco.
Just sayin'.
Two secretaries could convey
a sense of importance
and success to our clients.
Certainly worth exploring.
Wouldn't you agree, Andy?
- I'll explore exploring it.
- Good.
Seems like you have this
under control,
so I'll just duck out
and run the company for a while.
Okay, next stop
on the tour, sales.
Here we go.
Station stop Jim Halpert.
Oh, boy, our resident
truth teller.
All right, have at it.
Let her rip.
What do you hate
about this place?
Well, it's sales,
so you have to be able
to live in the world
of rejection.
Maybe you do.
Hi, I'm Dwight.
Sales is really not
so hard, okay-- It's paper.
We have it,
and they want it so bad
they are willing to pay for it.
Jim?
Well, it's not that easy.
It's kind of sometimes
difficult.
It's the second-easiest job
in the world.
- Being a mom.
- I love shopping.
And sales is just
the other side of that.
That's true.
You know, if you joined
our sales department,
you would be working
very closely
with our department head,
Mr. Dwight Schrute.
That's me.
Dwight, why don't you
tell Susan
about some of your hobbies.
- Oh.
- Survival skills.
- Mm-hmm.
- Ranking of animals.
Maybe over a beer after
she's closed her first sale.
Well, make that a red wine
and I'll tell you
my animal rankings.
How am I
supposed to pull this off?
The entire office is being
nicer to her
than they've ever been to me.
What I wouldn't give
for one of Phyllis'
classic room-clearing farts
right now.
Ready?
What do you think?
Huh?
Um, no, no.
This is not a gym.
This is like a scene
out of Saw V.
You haven't even
looked around yet.
Look..
Gravel bucket squat yoke.
Right?
Dedicated phone book
ripping station.
- You ever cut tin before?
- No.
Five yards in and your
forearms will be on fire.
Plus, I will buy the tin
back from you that you cut
for two cents a yard.
Now, let's go over membership.
I'm gonna need the first month's
and the last month's up front
for $49 a month.
But every third month
is $59 a month.
But the fourth month
is a discount month
at $19 per month.
Obviously, you know
how a gym works.
So you know I'm not
gonna pay money for this.
You want people
to come to your gym?
Make a real gym.
Darryl...
I was thinking accounting
might be a good fit
because I really clicked
with Oscar,
and I do have some experience
with bookkeeping.
But we already have
a surplus of accountants
as it is.
I would work
in customer service,
and, um, HR, even.
Those are fully staffed
as well.
Are you telling me
that there's no one
in this entire office
that could use
an extra pair of hands?
Yes.
I am the CEO, and I am telling
an employee of mine what to do.
Let me beat around
the bush for a second.
Our chairman of the board has
some very strong feelings--
- Robert, it's all right.
This is very uncomfortable.
Obviously, there's
no place for me here,
so thank you for trying.
- Why don't we just let it go?
- No. Absolutely not.
Andrew, there must be
something you can do.
There must be.
Think.
Well, there are a lot
of considerations.
I would be eternally grateful.
It's not a bad thing
to have the CEO owe you one.
All right!
Well, then, welcome aboard.
So what happens next?
We get you over to HR
and then get you set up
with accounting.
Hang on.
- Hello?
- Say "hello, grandma."
Hi, gam gam.
Hold one finger up to Susan.
You'll just be a second.
You numbskull!
You were given
a very simple task.
I could not have been
more clear with you.
Now say,
"are you taking your medicine?"
Are you taking your
med-meds?
Why can you not say
exactly what I tell you?
Undo this.
Undo it.
You didn't say good-bye
to your grandmother.
We promised we'd never
say good-bye.
Attention! I am now
accepting memberships
for the Dwight Schrute
gym for muscles.
First 20 members can
take advantage
of our "pay what you weigh"
promotion.
All I need is another gym.
As if I don't have
enough drama.
We have a gym at home.
It's called the bedroom.
Who's spotting who?
Don't use the bike
in the corner,
that's Bruce's.
Jeremy says--
Enough. Oscar, enough.
- Kelly?
- I have these sneakers,
which are basically just like
a gym for your feet, so...
That's okay.
I know how to build a business.
You gotta bet the black people
to do it
to get the white people
to do it.
Then you gotta get the black
people to stop doing it.
One step at a time.
Did you bring
your passport with you?
Who walks around
with their passport?
Well, I do.
Always ready for adventure.
- Have you had any?
- No.
Hey, guys.
So Robert doesn't want
his wife working here.
So now that she is,
we have to drive her away.
Andy, if he didn't want
her working here,
then why did you hire her?
Oscar, it was a mistake.
But one that can be fixed
by all of us being mean to her.
How can we do that?
She's simply wonderful.
This is all pathetic.
I am not asking, I am ordering.
How mean are we talking about?
It would he great if
she were gone by lunch.
Erin, you're up.
Find her a place to work,
but not too comfortable.
Got it. I know exactly
which stapler to give her.
Here you go.
Um, do you think
it would be possible
to move to that desk
over there?
Because this seems
a bit cramped,
and I don't have a computer.
Well, that's a sales desk.
Yeah. You need to be
over here with us accountants.
Just sit here and be quiet.
And if you have a question,
just raise your hand.
But I'm gonna save you
some time, sweetie,
and give you the answer now.
I...Don't...Know.
No, I don't think
we should be trying
to make this place
seem unpleasant.
I think we should
let this place
just crush her spirit
by itself.
I mean, it knows
what it's doing.
That's Gerald.
Oh, wow. So cute.
Oh, that is so cute.
Aw...
He's so tiny.
Is he in a ladle?
Yeah, he's in a ladle.
That's adorable.
How on earth
- did you get him in a ladle?
- He did it himself.
Is that ladle stainless or...
Oh, stainless.
Williams Sonoma.
Excuse me, waiter,
there's a dog in my soup.
It's not that kind of ladle.
- Very cute.
- Aw, let me see.
Ah, just the battery
on these things.
I'm sorry,
I've gotta recharge this.
I get it.
Last time I had a job,
I remember I hated
the boss' wife.
Of course, she was married
to Robert.
Your employees don't seem
to be taking to me.
Andy!
Andy, could you
step in here, please?
We'll fix this.
What is going on?
Please.
Andrew, my wife...
Has brought up an issue
that requires your attention.
So, uh, if you'll excuse me,
I should step out,
get to the ATM
before that homeless man
sets up camp for the night.
Okey-dokey, artichokey.
- You hate it, don't you?
- Do you not want me here?
- Why would you say that?
- It's okay.
I understand.
I'm not sure how I would feel
about having the boss' wife
work for me either.
- It's not that...Exactly.
- But it is something.
Let's just say that
if you don't want to work here,
I am totally prepared
to respect that.
Why would you not
want me working here?
I don't know.
I think I understand
what you're going through.
My husband can be a very
difficult man to read, can't he?
Yes!
- The dude is an enigma.
- Mm-hmm.
So he is mixed up
in this, isn't he?
Got it.
What do you think you're doing?
Getting my sweat on.
I build you this temple
to the human body,
and you're lifting what,
five pounds?
I just did, like,
35 minutes on the treadmill.
I was watching you.
You want to know how long
it really was?
- No.
- Eight minutes!
Dude, I'm gonna be here
all week, right?
Five days a week.
I figure I'll start slow.
Is that the same philosophy
you apply to buffalo wings?
I want you to bring that same
buffalo wing passion
to this gym!
I'm gonna make you look
like Lebron James!
It's Lejon Brames.
That's what I said.
You know, get it right.
I know.
- Cameras...
- Ooh, still here.
Terrific.
Andy and I had
a great conversation.
And I just want to let you know
that I am not going to be
working here.
- Well, that's a shame.
- It just was one of those thi--
Is it?
Because we talked about it,
and it seems like
that might be what you want.
- Which is fine.
- Where did this come from?
Did Andy say that?
No, he did not.
But I could tell
he was struggling
to understand what was
expected of him.
What's the struggle.
He made a great call,
hired a great person.
You sure about that?
- Absolutely.
- No games?
No games.
Because Andy seemed to think
there was some information
he was not able to share
with me.
Enough of this.
I mean, real-- Enough.
It's gotten way out of hand.
Andrew, this is my wife.
Whatever privacy
you were trying to protect
between us, I thank you for.
But it is not welcome
right now.
Just be honest.
- Andy...
- Yes.
Why do you keep looking
at my husband?
Andy, just answer the question.
- No games?
- No games.
Okay.
I mean, it was
kind of funny, actually.
Robert storms in, and he says,
"in four seconds,
my wife's gonna be in here.
"I told her
she could work here.
Under no circumstances
can that be allowed to happen."
You lying son of a bitch!
Tell my wife you're lying.
I am lying.
I am a compulsive liar.
- That's not true, is it?
- No, it's not.
I tell the truth
most of the time,
and I was just telling
the truth about your husband.
- Jim knows. He was there.
- This is preposterous.
- Robert...
- Let's get Jim in here.
Where's Jim?
He just rolled out
and crawled out.
Can you call security,
tell 'em to keep
an eye out for him?
Time to settle this.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Hold on, hold on.
I just need to get through.
Just real quick.
Real quick, open--
Okay.
That's weird.
Well, he's gotta
be around here somewhere.
Oh--
Ow...Ow...Ow...
Creed, I was never here,
all right?
Okay.
What about your friend?
Oh, boy.
This is my gym, my rules.
You do exactly as I say,
no questions asked.
Yeah, I'm gonna ask questions,
and I might not do
what you say.
First thing, we're gonna
stretch the pelvic bowl.
Ready?
Get down on the floor.
Okay, I'm not doing that.
Really?
Too embarrassing for you?
Huh?
You wish that every exercise
was strutting around the gym
like the Fonz?
Well, how do you think
the Fonz got so cool?
He stretched his pelvic bowl.
I didn't know Darryl joined.
Looks that way.
Nice pelvic bowl.
Deep.
- Hello, Jim.
- No, no. No, no, no!
Don't.
Damn it, tuna!
So I think you know
what we want to know.
- Do I?
- Yes.
I know. I do.
Jim, I've had enough
of your unhelpfulness.
I really wish I could help.
I'm not really sure how I can.
For God's sake,
did Robert tell you
that he didn't want me
working here?
That's the thing.
See, I didn't want to get
in the middle of this.
Still don't.
But here's something.
I feel that maybe,
if we take a step back,
this is a simple case
of anxiety
to work with a spouse.
I think we've got ourselves
an answer.
- No...
- That makes complete sense, right?
Thank you all
for a wonderful day.
- Perfect!
- Jim...
- Yes?
- Answer the question, please.
I don't know what
you want me to tell you.
To be really honest,
my wife works here.
And I love it.
She literally makes me
work harder.
She makes me smarter.
She makes me remember
why I'm here.
And between us, she's
on maternity leave right now,
and I would love to leave
this room and see her face.
I would love it.
I don't know how this helps,
but it's just what
I'm thinking.
All right. Thanks.
Yes. All right.
- Uh...
- Yeah.
Yep.
Thank you.
Andy.
Hey, Mrs. California.
Hey. Uh, I'm sorry
about the position
you were put in today.
You know, honestly,
we all wanted you
to work there.
Except for him.
Especially me.
Yes, I thought we really
hit it off.
Yeah.
Well, different circumstances.
- Who knows?
Maybe after all this
settles down...
Totally.
It's a date.
Hmm?
You're nothing!
You're so weak!
You call yourself a man?
Huh?
This doesn't help me.
I don't respond to
that kind of strategy.
Okay, fine.
Finish your set on your own,
and never come back
to my gym again!
Dwight, come back and spot me.
All right, I'll help you.
But first, you gotta tell me
what your goal is.
- What do you want?
- To push this bar up.
No! Because if that
was the case,
the bar would be up by now.
- What is your goal?
- Help me!
- What do you want?!?!?!?!
- To look good for Val!
Val Kilmore? I don't buy it,
it doesn't make any sense.
Wow.
I figured out your goal.
I'm gonna make you the buffest guy
Val Kilmore has ever seen.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com