Good morning, Dwight.
Who are you?
Who am I?
I'm Jim.
We've been working together
for 12 years.
Weird joke, Dwight.
You're not Jim.
Jim's not Asian.
You seriously never noticed?
Hey, hats off to you
for not seeing race.
All right then, Jim.
Uh, why don't you
tell me about that sale
that you made yesterday?
Uh, Wellington Systems?
Sold them ten cases
of 24-pound letter stock.
Or were you talking
about Krieger-Murphy?
Because I didn't close
that one yet,
but I'm hoping I've got a
voicemail from Paul Krieger
waiting for me.
Please enter your password.
You have one new message.
How did you know?
No!
No, no.
That is sensitive information.
Only for employees,
not outsiders!
Dwight, cut it out.
I'm trying to work.
You don't work here!
You're not Jim!
Jim, I got us
that dinner reservation.
- Grico's, 7:30.
- Oh, great.
Can't wait.
Jim's at the dentist
this morning,
and Steve is
an actor friend of ours.
I don't know who you are,
but you are not Jim.
This is Jim!
Oh, my--
oh, d--
oh, how did--
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Hey, study buddies!
Oh-- okay.
Getting Things Done.
Awesome!
It's all about finding ways
to make yourself more efficient.
Life hacking, baby.
This morning, I brushed my teeth
in the shower.
Saved myself 90 seconds.
Which I just used
to explain this to you.
Damn it.
Since Andy promoted me
to Assistant Regional Manager,
I've been trying
to step my game up.
You know, be more productive.
In fact, you know what?
Let's knock out a few more of
these sound bites
while we're here.
Whoa.
That person has really
gotten him-- or herself--
into quite a predicament.
S'il vous plait...
Dites-moi...
Ah, French.
It's a great language.
If you're
a chain-smoking acrobat.
I'm just trying to fit in
better with Andy's family.
They all speak
more than one language.
Usually when I'm there.
You want to learn a really
impressive second language?
Try Dothraki.
Win over any man in my guild.
Dothraki is the native tongue
of the nomadic,
war-mongering horse lords
of Essos, as featured
in the superb Home Box Office
series Game of Thrones.
It has a lot of nudity.
Which I fast-forward through
to get to the chopped-off heads.
I could teach you if you want,
it's a lot easier than French.
Yeah.
Let's do it.
- Athdavrazar!
- Oh--
It means "excellent."
And we have begun.
Is everything okay?
Hmm?
Oh--
oh, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, fine.
Fine, fine, fine.
I mean, I d--
I just don't want to burden you
with my massive
stress freak-outs.
Great.
It's just that I am taking
my driver's license test
in two days,
and I need to practice
with an experienced driver
in the car.
But I've had no time
to do that,
thanks to "Demandy."
I just want
to hit the open road
and drive, man.
But...
in whose car?
Nellie!
Get your wrinkly old balls
in here.
Nellie, I could practice
with you in my car at lunchtime.
Oh, Pam, thank you.
You are my savior.
- Oh, my God--
- Ohh--
I'm sorry I'm leaving
you alone for lunch.
Don't worry about it.
I have a thing.
A thing of soup.
Which I've been wanting to try.
This is my research
into how we might produce
child-proof paper
that doesn't give you
paper cuts.
We can't.
And here is a printout
of your genealogy
from thisisyourfamilytree.com.
Executive-summary me.
Hit the highlights.
Well, it turns out
you are
a distant blood relative
of Michelle Obama.
- As in--
- Wife of Barack,
loves gardening,
wants to wipe out fat children.
Wow.
This is
super-flattering.
She's the most popular person
in America.
This is a big day
for both of us.
My fellow Americans,
I have a feeling
my approval rating
is about to go
through the roof.
Turns out, I am
related to Michelle Obama.
I was intimidated
by Andy's family before.
And now I have to see
the First Lady at holidays?
She's gonna be like,
"what's your stance
on politics?"
Or, "what is
the best war to do?"
And I will just be like,
"duh--"
All right!
We gotta get rid of
all this junk food.
Get fit, America!
Not sure if the buzz has reached
the annex yet, but, uh,
I'm related to Michelle Obama.
Yeah, we noticed early on
Andy really appreciates
enthusiasm.
So we decided the best way
to get ahead here
is to be his cheerleaders.
Ohh!
It's starting to have this
reverse effect, though,
where I really do think
the stuff he does is awesome.
Yeah, me too.
It's weird.
Hard to remember what's real
at this point.
Just clap through it, man.
You're logging sales
at ten different times.
If you log 'em all at once,
you save a lot of time.
It's called batching.
This is really good, Darryl.
Life hacking, man.
There he is!
Andy, you gotta
check this out. He just--
Right now I need
canned tuna, okay?
Darryl, guess
which talented individual
who also has
a killer singing voice
is related to the First Lady.
Tracee Ellis Ross.
Daughter of the First Lady
of Motown, Diana Ross.
It's me!
I'm related to Michelle Obama.
What?
Really?
I mean, it's distant,
but--
That's cool, man.
Right?
Darryl said,
"cool, man."
He called me a cool man.
You know, I really do think it
would be worth it to pull over
and just take
ten minutes to eat.
Mm--
the thing is, Pam,
I'm gonna be eating
while I'm driving,
so I might as well
get good at it.
Brake lights. Brake lights,
brake lights, brake lights!
Whoo!
I'm just saying, what does it
imply in this country
when a white person shares
an ancestor with a black person?
You think that Andy's family
owned slaves?
Well, somebody owned somebody.
And I don't think anybody
would buy an Andy.
I throat-rip.
Foth aggendak.
You throat-rip.
Foth aggendi.
He-she-it throat-rips.
Foth aggenda.
More of a barbaric growl.
Louder. You're shouting it
from the back of a horse.
Foth aggenda!
Pretty crazy about Andy
and Michelle Obama, huh?
Yeah.
It's almost unbelievable.
What?
Well, do you know how
Andy has been
really salting
my onions lately?
Sure.
Well, when he asked me
to look up his ancestry online,
I remembered that news story
about Michelle Obama
having white relatives,
and I just knew
he would eat that up.
So he's not related
to Michelle Obama?
Pam,
I barely know how
to turn on my computer.
Nellie's pretty fearless.
And I think she might be
maybe even almost sort of fun.
Pam!
Well, if there's another
explanation,
I don't really see
what it could possibly be.
I--
What's going on here?
I'm related
to the First Lady, okay?
Get over it.
I still need weekly
status reports from most of you.
So can we get
back to work, please?
Get back to work.
Andy--
Andy, no!
I would be very polite today.
Why, is it employees' day
or something?
I cannot keep track
of these BS holidays.
Your connection
to Michelle Obama
has certain negative
connotations.
Most likely,
your family were...
slave owners.
Does anyone else
think it's possible
that I come from slave owners?
Whoa.
That person has really
gotten him-- or herself--
into quite a predicament.
Hey, mom, it's Andy.
Give me a call
when you get a chance.
Got a quick question for you.
Uh, no big deal, just about
America's national shame.
Thanks, bye.
Where were we?
Uh-- yes,
okay.
Your... productivity thing.
Yes, yes, yes.
Great.
Ooh, spreadsheets.
Yum, yum.
I included some
time-saving ideas.
Uh-huh, uh-huh,
uh-huh.
Look, I'm not gonna lie to you.
I'm a teensy bit
distracted right now.
Look, Andy, even
if your ancestors
did own slaves,
it wouldn't be your fault.
This is only weird
if you make it weird.
Right on, brother.
Word dat.
Mm--
- Ador!
- Daras.
Qazer!
Daras.
Does anyone here have
fermented mare's milk?
Hey, Erin.
Atchomar chomakaan!
Oh-- okay.
Sorry.
Oh, still, it must be great
to have something else going on
outside of work.
Yeah--
turn signal.
It's exciting to be
painting again--
those are the wipers.
So the--
it's just--
there you go.
Yeah.
Yeah, things get so busy
with the kids--
red light-- that it's nice
to have that creative outlet--
red light, red light,
red, red--
That is brilliant, Pam.
I'd love to see
some of your work.
Well, since we're stopped
at a light...
uh, here is...
the mural I did
for Angela's baby.
That is amazing, Pam.
Oh, I love
the lion in the tuxedo.
Angela insisted that all
the animals be fully clothed.
Hey, has anyone turned in
their status reports up here?
Vos.
So no?
Do you think maybe
you could remind people?
I'm trying to downplay the whole
bossy-boss thing today.
Because of your slaves.
Not my slaves, my ancestors'.
Maybe.
Probably not.
Well, if it makes you
feel any better,
the Dothraki word
for "slave master,"
azzafrok, is a term of respect.
I'm learning
how to speak Dothraki.
Color you impressed?
- That you're learning
a made-up language
from HBO's Game of Thrones?
I have a lot going on today,
but this was
a great nerd-out.
Dwight, you didn't tell me
you were teaching me
a fake language.
People laughed at Klingon
at first,
and now you can major in it.
Hi, guys.
Hey, boss.
I am so thirsty,
can I have a scoop of water?
Yeah.
You don't have to ask me--
Ha ha.
Okay, great.
Very funny.
I get it.
Just because my ancestors
happened to be--
Very funny,
Kevin changed my ringtone.
Very funny.
I liked the original song
on my ringtone.
Which, you may remember,
was Diamonds on the Soles
of Her Shoes by Paul Simon,
featuring,
Ladysmith African-American
Mombazo.
Good. Very good.
Oh-- no.
Here, it's, uh,
a text from Andy.
"New special proj.
Need fam. Tree for evbody.
"Really dig up dirt.
ASAP."
And then in parentheses
he wrote out,
"as soon as possible."
Mm.
Ugh, looks like
it's pretendy time again.
Write back,
"looking for dirt."
Oh, can I help?
We could say someone
is related to, um,
Tonya Harding.
Pam, I'm related
to Tonya Harding.
Oh--
gee, I'm--
No, I'm just
practicing my lying.
- I love it.
- Brilliant.
What should we say about Jim?
Um, oh-- uh, say
he's related to Richard Nixon.
It's an inside joke.
He looks really Nixony
when he wakes up.
My ex behaved like Nixon.
All of the lying,
none of the sexual charisma.
I just made a joke then.
I'm sorry.
It's just, um--
I actually do have
this weird feeling
that there's something
Jim isn't telling me.
Oh, no.
Ugh, an affair.
It is always an affair.
Jim?
No.
How can you be sure?
Because he just
loves me too much.
You're a cocky little thing,
aren't you, Pam?
I have done a little
genealogy research of my own.
Turns out I'm not the only one
with a few skeletons
in the ol' family closet.
For example,
Phyllis'
great-great-grandmother
was responsible for spreading
cholera to the United States.
Ew.
Kevin is related to both
John Wayne Gacy
and John Wayne Bobbitt.
And John Wayne?
No. Not that
I see here.
Wayne Johnson?
The Rock?
You mean Dwayne, and no.
What about Jim Halpert?
Uh-oh.
Turns out, distant relative
of the reviled
Richard Nixon.
Pam always says
I look like Nixon.
That's crazy, right?
I mean, there's nothing there.
Tru--
Oh, no.
Dwight's grandfather--
Was a member of the Bund,
which is not technically
the same thing
as the Nazi party.
So--
I was gonna say
he was a tax evader.
Oh.
I was joking about
that whole Bund thing.
Oh-ho, the look
on your faces.
And Meredith
is a blood relative
of Lizzie Borden.
Cool.
Stop it! Stop it,
you're frightening me.
Andy, did you call this meeting
just to talk junk
about our families?
Yeah, that-- you're being
really mean.
No, I'm proving a point, okay?
We all have ancestors
who may have
done horrible things
in the past.
But it's in the past,
and it's not our fault.
So we don't have
to talk about it.
The difference is, Andy,
that you're the only one here
still benefitting
from the terrible things
your ancestors did.
Might have done,
and how do you figure?
Your family's rich.
I have to believe
that a big part
of the Bernard fortune was
earned on the backs of slaves.
You know, there's nothing wrong
with being successful
in America, Oscar.
I'm not gonna apologize
for my family's wealth.
That wealth could one day
benefit society,
if capital gains are ever
taxed at the same rate
as earned income.
Okay, Kevin did that.
I do not wish I was in Dixie.
Hey, mom.
How are you?
Did any Bernards ever own
a plantation in the South?
She said no.
Take that!
Follow-up question,
did any Bernards
ever make money
in an unsavory way?
I just
asked you--
why didn't you
used to say that?
Okay, stop, stop.
Stop talking.
That's-- no.
I don't want to know that.
Okay, you're interrupting
a meeting.
I have to go.
Love you.
Bye.
Well, turns out the Bernards
of yore did not own slaves.
Really.
We merely transported them.
Which, at worst,
makes us amoral middlemen.
Yo, D-Dog.
I need your help.
I'm trying to think of things
I can say that make it
sound like I had a sore
difficult childhood
than I actually had.
- You gonna po' mouth.
- Exactly.
Help me po' mouth, Darryl.
Actually, Andy,
you promised me five minutes
to talk about productivity
suggestions--
What if I said
that my dad beat me,
and I just left out
the croquet of it all?
Or, I could just go all the way
and say I grew up
in an apartment.
Or is that too crazy?
That could work.
You know, Darryl, this is
textbook assistant regional
manager stuff here,
and I feel like I'm doing
all the heavy lifting.
I'm coming up
with all the ideas here.
I'm going for a walk.
Okay.
Good...
Good, and--
You doing all right, man?
I'm done.
I gotta get out of here.
Yeah.
Not the easiest day to be
Assistant Regional Manager.
It's not just today,
it's every day.
Seems like
the better title I have,
the stupider my job gets.
Aw, come on, it can always
get better, right?
Hmm.
Yeah, right.
No, I'm serious.
There's always
something better.
Like what?
Like, hypothetically,
if I said that
there was another job
that you and I could both have.
What kind of job?
Something cool,
like sports marketing, or--
does that sound like
something you'd be into?
- Hell yeah.
- Right?
That sounds awesome.
Okay, but wait.
What if I told you
that it was in Philly?
- So you'd have to--
- I love Philly.
Right?
- It's not even a thought--
- Not even a thought.
It's not even that far away,
I could still commute-- exactly.
Exactly.
All right.
What?
Wait, wait, wait.
So what, is this happening?
Oh, it's happening.
Let's just keep it
between you and me
- for right now, all right?
- Okay. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
For sure, for sure, for sure.
Man.
And Pam's into it?
We gotta have a talk about it,
but I think
that she's--
I think she understands...
- Aw, come on, man.
- ...what this is.
I thought you had
something real.
What?
No, no, no.
Come on.
This is real.
It's not real
until your wife is on board.
So what did you
want to show me?
That is quite an ugly wall,
isn't it?
Yeah.
It's really ugly.
Needs something, doesn't it?
I'm thinking,
a mural.
You mean me?
Yes, you.
You are so talented.
It's going to be my next
special project.
Hiring Scranton's most
dangerous young muralist
to paint the warehouse wall.
Oh, my God, I love it!
Uh-- I--
Nellie,
this is brilliant!
- Hey!
- Hey.
Can I talk to you for a second?
Anything you have
to say to her,
you can say to me.
She never loved you.
What? No, I--
I got this.
Okay.
This is his fault.
It is not your fault.
I am gonna find you
someone better, and rich.
And Filipino.
But we'll break that
to her later.
You know what
this is all about?
Yeah.
You too, huh?
Go on, spill it.
Tell her all the gory details,
you snake.
Hey.
He deserves this.
And he said I could
get in on it too.
Yeah.
Oh, Pam, no.
Oh, I can't bear to watch this.
I don't know what I was
so worried about.
I have the best wife
in the world.
I still can't believe
he didn't tell me.
I was helping
Nellie drive--
Do not care.
Fonas chek!
Dothras chek!
I like that guy.
We should hook him up
with Meredith.
Hmm--
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com