Can you guys come
with me for a minute?
I know you saw me
with the Senator.
I think I'm in love,
possibly for the first time.
So, yes, Senator Lipton
and I are having an affair.
I hope that I can count
on your sensitivity,
maturity, and discretion.
Why?
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
All right, good.
Yeah, just sell it
and get the best price
you can, okay?
Or we can hope
for a holiday rally?
Mike, I'm not a day trader.
I'm just a first responder
in a disaster.
Andy's family had
a total meltdown.
His dad blew through
all their money
and took off to Argentina
with a younger woman.
And his brother,
Walt Jr.,
locked himself
in the wine cellar.
The weirdest part is Andy.
The aftermath got
dumped on him,
and the way he's been
handling it is just so--
- Competent.
- Right?
Are the nards hurtin'?
Yeah, you bet.
Got kicked pretty hard.
Family shattered, super sad.
But I'm kinda crushin' it
in the damage control
department.
So, that's cool.
I wish my dad could see me now.
Of course, he caused
this whole mess, so...
fuck him.
Kevin, listen to me.
I'm in love with the Senator.
And I need time
to sort this out
in a responsible manner.
So I need your help
in keeping it a secret,
because this means
the world to me.
Okay?
That's beautiful.
No, I-I totally get that.
Can you do this, Kevin?
I really want to.
Whatever happens,
always remember that.
I don't know what that means.
Hey, hey.
Oh, great.
Yeah, um, I'll get
right back to you.
Hey, guys, has anyone ever heard
of Iris Black on the radio?
Yeah, she hosts
the Dr. Laura show.
Nope, that's Dr. Laura.
Well, her show Bizwhiz
wants someone
from Dunder Mifflin
to come on the air today.
Does anybody feel
particularly passionate
about local business issues?
I do. I do. I do.
I do. I do.
The media can make you famous.
And do you have any idea
how easy it is
to sell something
when you're famous?
"Uh, yeah, wow.
10 reams of 40-pound bond
at only $6.90 after discount?
Uh, whatever you say,
Brad Pitt."
It's that easy.
Hey, so that good-looking
single brother of yours?
Heard he was
in a downward spiral with booze.
Yeah.
He's in rehab, actually.
Which place?
The one right near Philly?
I could be there in an hour.
No, it's in New Mexico.
Oh.
So, how are you holding up?
We're done, Meredith.
Greta the tittle-tattle
prattled on
about the little metal bottle.
- Oh, my God.
- She spat a bit of spittle--
- Dwight.
In a bitter battle--
Hey, hey.
Stop questioning
my methods, okay?
I was chosen for this task
for a very good reason.
No.
You chose yourself.
Tricky Siskel spat a bit
of wicked biscuit--
All right, guys, there's a lot
of assets here
that my dad couldn't steal.
Now, first of all,
there is the family boat,
a 43-foot Tartan sloop.
My lawyer has lined up
a buyer in the Bahamas.
The sale would cover
the cost of a condo
and living expenses for my mom.
- Sounds great.
- Perfect.
Totally, except
it is a no-go.
This boat was the heart
and soul of our family.
So what else we got?
Non-boat ideas.
- What happened?
- Jammed.
- Excuse me a second.
- Could this day get worse?
Yeah, I think this day
could get worse.
- What does that mean?
- Kevin.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
She could get, like,
60 packages of ramen noodles
for 5 bucks.
- Oh, hey, sorry.
- She could eat for a month.
All right,
what's the grand total?
Did we make our nut?
If we sell everything
but the boat,
your mom should be set
for about six months.
Guys, you don't understand.
This boat's been in our family
since before I was born.
Yeah, don't you guys
have that place
where you used
to spend your summers
and have all those memories?
- I worked at a Jiffy Lube.
- See?
I bet you wouldn't
sell that Jiffy Lube
for all the money in the world,
would you, Darryl?
I would if I owned it
and I went broke.
All right.
Uh, all right.
I'm gonna tell the lawyer
to pull the trigger on the boat.
Yes, the boat means everything
to my family,
but we need the money.
Got the memories,
don't need the boat.
Can't cry about it.
What are you gonna do?
Cry about it?
Excuse me.
Oh, okay.
No problem.
Thanks.
Hey, guys, WPTU called.
The interview's off.
They're opening
a new cupcake store
at the steamtown mall, and
Iris wants to cover that, so...
Well, why don't I go
and tell Dwight,
so he can stop being
such a complete nipple?
He's gonna be disappointed.
Yes, he is.
And you know what?
We cannot let that happen.
Fax?
Oh, yeah.
Just-- just a minute.
Watermelon teeth.
This isn't how I would
cheer up just anyone,
but it's a girlfriend's job
to know her man,
and I know Andy.
He is seriously juvenile.
Cool.
He's, like, 40, though, right?
Oh, no.
He couldn't be
more than late 30s, tops.
Awesome.
Have fun.
Dunder Mifflin.
Good, sounds--
This is Dwight Schrute.
Please hold for Ms. Black.
And welcome back to Bizwhiz.
I'm Iris Black.
On the line,
we have Dunder Mifflin
senior sales associate
Dwight Schrute.
Iris, thank you so much
for having me.
Help! My teeth are all
messed up in my mouth.
Did you need something?
Oh, I just need
your signature on this.
Okay.
Thanks.
Kevin, we're out of 1138 forms.
Did you order more?
I did not.
Well, I don't know
why I'm surprised.
Literally nothing you could do
could surprise me anymore.
Oh, really, Angela?
That's interesting.
'Cause I do think
that I could surprise you.
I think that I could
surprise you all the--
Ah!
I have to go to the bathroom.
That doesn't surprise me.
That actually wasn't
the worst cover.
I'd say at least once a week,
Kevin runs out of the room,
shouting that he has to go
to the bathroom.
Oh! I have to go
to the bathroom!
I have to go to the bathroom!
Okay, who wants to go
for a super fun lunch
with a super fun girlfriend?
Look, it's not
that I don't want--
Okay, come on, I got someone
to cover the phones,
I heard on the radio
about a new cupcake place
we could go for dessert,
perfect.
All I ever wanted to do
was sail the damn thing.
But dad wouldn't let me.
He said, "you can't be a skipper
until you're a man."
You know,
I'd reach for the wheel,
and he'd just
smack my hand away.
Well, guess what.
Now I'm the man of the family,
and we're selling
the damn thing.
So I'm never gonna have
the chance.
Well, when does
the boat leave, exactly?
Tonight.
Then screw lunch.
Let's go for a sunset sail.
Yeah, right.
It's in Stamford, Connecticut.
We'd have to leave,
like, right now.
Okay, well, then let's leave,
Yeah, okay.
Let's go.
Seriously?
Of course seriously.
Get your coat on.
- All right.
- Let's do it.
Iris, let me tell you,
David Wallace is the CEO,
but he's not hands-on.
So the day-to-day operations
are entirely under your command?
Entirely is the perfect way
to describe it, Iris.
Uh, excuse me, I'm being told
by my sound engineer Steve
that, uh, there is
a clinking sound
coming from your end.
Does your shirt have buttons?
Yes.
I'm so sorry, we are going
to have to ask you
to remove the shirt altogether.
Now then.
We were saying,
when my workers gather--
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I am told we are still
having problems, Mr. Schrute.
Your voice, it's sounding
a little feminine.
That's impossible.
Are you, by any chance,
wearing pants
with a metallic zipper?
The Senator is exhausted.
This campaign
is wearing him out.
It's a tough one.
That man he's up against
is so dirty,
and the Senator's just
pushing back as hard as he can.
Please stop.
What?
Anyways, last night,
he was so tired,
he just wanted
a little Mexican brought in.
I can't.
It's-- it's too much.
I'm in big trouble.
Yeah, Oscar's in big trouble.
Okay, how is my voice now?
I'm getting the all clear
from Steve.
So, Mr. Schrute,
what is your response
to the Consumer Product
Safety Commission
that says Dunder Mifflin paper
is toxic?
This is gotcha journalism.
But you know what?
They're not gonna "gotch" me.
It's clearly not
an accounting mistake.
- Oh, Kevin.
- So...
His gambling problem
must have resurfaced.
I'm gonna have to send him home
until I can do
an investigation.
Well, you gotta do
what you gotta do, so...
This is slander, Ms. Black.
Slander, I say.
I dare you to produce
one credible source about this.
Well, as it happens,
we have with us
the foreman of your
upstate New York paper mill,
Sondra Mc--
Sondra Mick.
Good afternoon, Iris.
It's a pleasure.
I'll get straight to the point.
Is your paper toxic?
No, the paper's not toxic...
Thank you, Sondra!
Unless it's exposed to oxygen.
Then it becomes
extremely toxic.
Do not listen to her!
This employee
is obviously disgruntled.
What the heck is going on?
The stock price is plummeting.
Are you gonna get control
of the message,
or do I have to send in someone
who understands the media?
- Get out of here, moron!
- Okay.
Uh, excuse me, Mr. Dwight,
who are you talking to?
Uh, no one.
Did you just call Ms. Mick
a moron?
No, everything's fine.
Are you insulting my guests?
Okay.
I will be right there.
Hey, Oscar.
What if I'm getting
a promotion?
I hope that's it, Kevin.
Me too.
'Cause then,
I would get my own office,
and I wouldn't screw up
your secret with Angela.
I've been really
worried about that.
Hi, Kevin.
Look, I need to talk to you--
- Hi.
- Guys, excuse me.
Um, a quick word?
Please, just--
- Oscar, we're in the middle
of talking.
I know.
I'm so sorry.
Snack machine, on me.
Oh, that is nice.
Classy move.
That's what I'm saying!
No, of course not!
- Wha--
- What are you doing?
Those figures I gave you,
they're false.
No.
I was mad at Kevin.
We had a fight,
and I acted vindictively.
So you set him up.
Yes, he's innocent.
Oh... I knew it.
I knew it from the beginning,
this was a possibility.
What are you talking about?
I just did this now.
Oh, no, a few years ago,
when I was on the jury,
the Scranton strangler.
Sure.
I always thought
he might have been set up,
but I felt pressured
to convict.
That's gotta be tough.
Tough?
I put an innocent man
on death row.
The fallout from
this morning's revelation
continues to mount.
Since Mr. Dwight Schrute
began speaking,
Dunder Mifflin share prices
fell 73%.
Mr. Schrute, shareholders
demand accountability
from corporate leadership.
Can we announce your resignation
at this time?
My resignation?
What are you talking about?
No, I'm just following orders!
Listen, the person responsible
for this catastrophe
is the ceo and chairman,
David Wallace.
That's yours?
That's the family boat
right there.
Oh, my gosh, Andy.
This is enormous.
Right?
I thought it was gonna be tiny.
Oh, my gosh.
It's beautiful.
So this is how your family
came to America.
- Move.
- Sorry?
I'm trying to rig a boat here.
I don't know how to do that
when you're standing in the way.
Sure, I-I'm not--
I didn't know.
I'm not a ghost, so I can't
walk through people.
- Okay.
- He was salty.
- Yes, a little bit.
How you doing, old buddy?
Missed you.
What does that one do?
This raises the mainsail.
That was my job
when we went sailing.
I wish I had seen you do it.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Up she goes.
Don't do that.
- Don't do that.
- Oh, it's okay.
My girlfriend and I
were actually gonna
take her for a little spin
and a picnic
before you guys
head out tonight.
You know what?
Get some dinner on me.
Nope.
Can't do that.
Got it.
You know what,
then we'll just take it
for a quick little spin
around the harbor.
We've already started boarding.
No one is insured to rig
or operate now, except us.
You know what?
Chill, okay?
I own the boat.
Not gonna sue myself.
All right?
So just--
Wow.
I can smack you all day
if you keep touching
what you're not
supposed to touch.
- Okay, fine, fine.
- Okay?
- Yeah, fine.
- Good stuff.
Good stuff.
Great stuff.
Fuck! Damn it!
Screw you, dad!
Ugh!
Well, we're doing it.
We're finally having a picnic
on the boat.
I've had a thousand picnics
on this boat.
The point was
for me to sail it.
Andy, you never had
to sail the boat to be a man.
Fine, but I could have.
As long as we're on this boat,
as far as I'm concerned,
you're the captain.
I am the captain.
- Yeah.
- Right?
Yeah.
I'm the captain.
Hey, charm school.
What?
- I'm taking over from here.
- Nice.
Okay, I hate to ruin
this, uh, moment,
or breakdown, but you already
signed the papers.
So, if you want your boat back,
you can pick it up
there in the Bahamas
in ten days.
Yeah, I know,
'cause I'm sailing it there.
Okay, no.
I already said you're not
getting back your deposit.
Fine, keep it.
Just leave the supplies.
I already paid for those.
And how much
for that cool fisherman sweater?
For those just joining us,
terror in Greenwich,
where police have
surrounded the house
of Dunder Mifflin CEO
David Wallace.
Wallace is said
to be despondent
over the company's
stock plummet,
and has taken
a mailman hostage.
On the line, we have
Chief of Greenwich Police,
Mr. Bill Jackson.
Good afternoon.
Please, sir, spare him.
Please.
Uh, this Wallace guy's
looking at hard time,
and we only know this because
of what Dwight snoot said
on record.
Okay, everyone.
Everyone, hold on.
I've got a solution.
I know Wallace's phone number.
Everyone hold,
I'll conference him in.
Oh, no, Mr. Schrute,
there's really no need to,
um, involve Mr. Wallace.
Do you even know
what you're doing?
Yeah.
Yeah, I know how to hoist
the mainsail,
I know how to--
These buttons control
bilge pumps and stuff.
I also know
where the booze stash is.
Hello.
Walt?
Oh, God!
Thank goodness you're here.
I was having a little trouble,
uh, with this door,
uh, yesterday.
I, um--
I think it was yesterday.
I thought you were in rehab.
Yeah, I just, uh--
I figured I'd get
that first relapse
out of the way.
God, what's happened
to our family?
Everything is so messed up.
How did you even know
I was in here?
I didn't.
I just came to say
good-bye to the boat,
but I've decided to sail it
to Bermuda.
- Bahamas, Andy.
- Same thing.
I need a crew.
You should be my crew.
Three weeks, open ocean,
no booze.
You need this.
I need it.
We need this.
Serious bro time.
Come on.
- Hello?
- David, is that you?
Dwight?
Oh, thank God.
Are you okay?
Is everyone okay?
Yeah.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I just want you to know
that I believe in you.
I really do.
And I believe in your ability
to make the right choices.
I always have, David.
Well, thanks, Dwight.
You're welcome, sir.
But, David,
listen to me carefully.
I'm going to need you
to let the mailman go, okay?
Dwight?
- Walk out of the house...
- What?
With your hands
on top of your head.
Everything is going to be fine.
Dunder Mifflin will be
in good hands
while you're away in prison.
Okay, Dwight?
Gonna ask you to not call me
on my cell anymore.
Gotta go.
Wait a minute.
You guys?
You heard?
Schrute! Schrute!
Schrute!
Schrute! Schrute! Schrute!
Schrute! Schrute!
Overall, I'd say
my first radio interview
went pretty much
the way I expected.
Well, Oscar, I did not
get the promotion.
He just wanted to update
my personal information.
Well, I'm sorry, Kevin.
Why on Earth would you think
you were getting a promotion?
You know what, Angela, I--
Oh, my God.
Honey, what are you doing here?
Oh, I just had an intuition
that someone I love
needed a little
of my attention today.
Oscar, looking very healthy.
Getting lots
of vigorous exercise?
No.
Oscar, what is going on?
What was that?
- Wha--
- What was that?
I-I'm sorry.
I didn't mean any offense.
I was just trying
to be friendly.
You know what?
I'm sorry.
I overreacted,
because I'm stressed out.
Why am I stressed out?
Who's not stressed out?
Come on, Oscar.
We're not just gonna sit here
and ignore the obvious.
Senator Lipton
has a big election next week.
We all need
to give him our support.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you very much.
Oh, thanks, everybody.
'Cause it's really cool.
- USA! USA!
- USA. U--
I have to say,
I'm impressed with Kevin.
Uh, he showed a lot
of self-control.
I totally forgot
about the affair for a minute.
Oscar is having sex
with the Senator,
and Angela doesn't even know.
Her life is a complete sham.
All right, guys.
Cast us off.
Walt, all aboard.
Erin, this is because of you.
Do you realize that?
You're the best ever.
Oh, you know,
just being a good girlfriend.
"Good"?
Come on.
Above and beyond.
World's greatest.
You did this.
Damn it, I'm happy!
Yes, I am very pleased
I could help Andy.
Would I have gone with him
if he'd asked me?
On his sailboat cruise
to the Caribbean?
Yes, I think that would have
been really fun and romantic.
- I'll see you in three weeks!
- Okay!
Hey, bro,
it was here all along.
- No way!
- Way!
Erin, I gotta go!
Them's my chords!
Hey.
She's back.
Thanks for covering the phones.
Yeah, no problem.
How was it?
Fine.
Hey, some buddies and I
are going to poor Richard's
for beers and pool.
You want to come?
I can't promise you too much,
but you might get
to meet my friend Flipper.
Does he have a flipper?
Oh, nope.
It's not that.
He, uh, he flipped a table
one time when he was drunk.
He sounds like an idiot.
Yeah, he is.
- Okay.
Thanks.
Yeah.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com