Dunder Mifflin, this is Pam.
Sure, can I ask who's calling?
Just a second.
Jim Halpert. What?
How did you get this number?
Stalker.
Katy and Jim
met in the office.
And now, I guess they're, like,
going out or dating or something.
And...
I don't know, you know.
They're just...
She calls him, and they...
You know.
I'm sorry, I feel like I'm talking
really loud. Am I talking really loud?
So we're still on for lunch?
You're meeting me here?
Okay. Great. Bye.
Hey, you can just
give her your extension.
Okay.
HowardlRyan.
Ryan Howard is sitting
in my office.
And he has been a temp here
for a couple of months,
and he's kind of gotten the
lay of the land a little bit.
Had a few laughs
along the way.
And now he wants
to know what I think.
The temp agency wants to know
what you think.
Shall we? Let us proceed.
First up, "Proficiency
in necessary skills.
"Excellent. "
Michael's in there right
now evaluating the temp.
He hasn't evaluated me
in years.
Five years from now,
what do you wanna do?
Where do you wanna be?
Well, I'm interested
in business.
Oh. Good. Ambitious.
Excellent.
Wanna be a manager?
No, actually, what I want
is to own my own company.
That is ridiculous.
Ryan's about to attend the
Michael Scott School of Business.
I'm like Mr. Miyagi and Yoda
rolled into one.
"Much advice you seek. "
Do you know who that is?
Fozzie Bear?
Hmm.
No. That was Yoda.
There are 10 rules of business
that you need to learn.
Number one:
You need to play to win,
but you also have to
win to play.
Got it.
And I will give you
the rest of the 10 at lunch.
Hey.
Michael and I have
a very special connection.
He's like Batman,
I'm like Robin.
He's like the Lone Ranger
and I'm like Tonto.
And it's not like there was the
Lone Ranger and Tonto and Bonto.
People!
Okay, everybody!
This is not a test.
Move to the exits.
Devon, head towards
the exit. Do not panic!
Get up off your desks. No, I
don't wanna hear it. All right?
Let's go, people!
No panic is warranted.
Do not panic!
Go in a single-file line.
This is not a drill!
Arms at your side!
Please, move quickly! This
is a paper company, people.
Step lively. This whole place is
a tinderbox. It is ready to blow.
This is not a test.
Can you leave?
Oh, you say that every time.
Do you wanna die?
Oh, God.
Do you wanna die? Out!
All right, let's go,
let's go, let's go.
Stanley, have you ever seen a
burn victim? Move to the exits.
Come on, your safety partners.
Your safety partners. Let's go!
Real smoke!
We've got smoke! Smoke!
God!
Oh, Kelly! Are you okay?
I got you!
I'm okay!
Cover your nose and mouth.
Hey, let go of me!
Breathe through your nose.
Let go of me!
Remove your stockings, okay?
They'll melt right into your
flesh. Stay below the smoke line.
Let's go! Clear out, stat!
Stat means now!
Yes,
I was the first one out.
And, yes, I've heard women
and children first,
but we do not employ children.
We are not a sweatshop,
thankfully.
And women are equal
in the workplace by law.
So, I let them out first,
I've a lawsuit on my hands.
Another rule of business is being
able to adapt to different situations.
Yeah?
Mmm-hmm.
Adapt. React. Readapt.
Apt. All right?
That's rule number two.
Okay, guys, listen up.
We need a head count.
Okay, we need to count off.
Michael's number one.
Where is he? Where's he?
So, what was rule two?
Adapt, react, readapt, apt.
Okay, well, let's just kind
of take it a little slower.
Hey, Michael, Ryan needs
a number for the count off.
Okay, well, "1" is taken.
Okay, "2"?
No!
Oh, sorry.
Okay.
He can have "14."
Marjorie's not here today.
Well, he needs
a permanent number, right?
No, I don't.
Oh, you know what else? I thought
of a nickname for the three of us.
Three Musketeers.
Yeah, okay. Yeah. No, no, no.
I got one, I got one.
The Three Stooges.
That's funny, too. But if
we're the Three Musketeers...
I don't wanna be, like,
a guy here, you know?
Like, Stanley
is the crossword-puzzle guy
and Angela has cats.
I don't wanna
have a thing here.
You know, I don't wanna be
the "something guy. "
Okay, you know what?
I think I'm gonna be
setting the agenda here, okay?
Can everybody gather up,
please?
Important announcement.
Very important announcement.
I think this is a perfect opportunity
for all of us to participate
in some really intense,
psychologically revealing conversations.
So, we're gonna be playing
"desert island,"
um...
"Who would you do" and...
"Would you rather. "
"Would you rather"
is our third game.
Yeah!
Hey, guys.
Great response time.
Listen up. I got some
theories. Okay, there's a...
Okay, so three books
on a desert island, Angela.
The Bible.
That's one book.
You've got two others.
A Purpose Driven Life.
Nice.
Third book.
No.
Okay, Phyllis.
The Da Vinci Code.
I would take
The Da Vinci Code,
so I could burn
The Da Vinci Code.
Okay, great. That's gonna keep
you warm for, like, seven seconds.
Question, is there
firewood on the island?
I guess.
Then I would bring an axe,
no books.
No, it has
to be a book, Dwight.
Fine.
Physician's Desk Reference.
Nice. Smart.
Hollowed out. Inside, water
proof matches, iodine tablets,
beet seeds, protein bars,
NASA blanket,
and, in case I get bored,
Harry Potter
and the Sorcerer's Stone.
No, Harry Potter
and the Prisoner of Azkaban.
Question, did my shoes
come off in the plane crash?
Rule number four: In
business image is everything.
Andre Agassi.
This car is an investment,
right?
If I have to take out a client or
I'm seen around Scranton in it...
I love it. I love this car.
Do you like it?
Yeah.
Okay, thought
people read more books.
DVDs. Five movies, what
would you bring to the island?
Yes, Meredith.
Legends of the Fall, My Big Fat
Greek Wedding, Legally Blonde,
Bridges of Madison County.
Wow.
Legends of the Fall.
Bridges of Madison County.
Legally Blonde.
These movies are just...
Well, I kind of like
Legally...
Wait, wait, wait.
Pam, no. Do you understand?
The game is "desert island movies,"
not "guilty pleasure movies. "
Desert island movies are the movies you're
gonna watch for the rest of your life.
Forever. Unforgivable.
I take it back.
Unforgivable.
Good.
And, Ghost.
But just that one scene.
Is this your car, Ryan?
Well, sir, I don't... Some
pretty big books back there.
Good shocks.
Hello, Mr. Egghead.
Oh, Stanley Kaplan.
I know him.
"M" is for Murder,
"P" is for...
That's actually a test-prep
book.... for Phone. What?
That's a test-prep
for business school.
Oh, thinking about
business school?
I just got in.
I applied. I go at night.
Really? So, you think you
know a lot about business?
No, not yet. Just started.
Uh-huh. Yeah.
Quiz me.
I wouldn't even
know where to start.
Oh, come on. Come on,
egghead, let's do it.
Do it.
Quiz me up.
All right.
Why have people been rethinking the
Microsoft model in the past few years?
When I was Ryan's age,
I worked in a fast food restaurant
to save up money for school.
And then I lost it
in a pyramid scheme,
but I learned more about
business right then and there
than business school would ever
teach me or Ryan would ever teach me.
Is it cheaper to sign a new customer
or to keep an existing customer?
Keep an existing cust...
Shut it.
Can I just do it, please?
It's equal.
It is 10 times more expensive
to sign a new customer.
Okay. Yes,
it was a trick question, okay.
Look, I mean, he didn't need
business school, okay?
Michael comes from the school
of hard knocks.
All right. Okay, Dwight...
Self-taught.
You didn't even go to college.
You know what? You don't
need to help me here, okay?
You know, maybe you should go
to business school like Ryan.
Then you'd know
what you're talking about.
Come on.
So...
I'm studying with the master.
Reference. Why don't
you go to business...
You should learn from him,
right? Right? Right?
Stop it, Dwight. You know what,
Dwight? You're acting like a dork.
Would you cool it,
please? Okay.
Hey, he's not your
five-year-old brother, Dwight.
He's a valued member
of this company.
And you know what? He knows more
about business than you ever will.
Stupid.
I did not
go to business school.
You know who else didn't go
to business school?
Lebron James, Tracy McGrady,
Kobe Bryant.
They went right from high
school to the NBA, so...
So, it's not the same thing
at all.
Look at this stuff. "Market fragments.
" What is that supposed to be?
It's a way of looking at consumers
as subsets of a larger client base.
You are so smart.
You are so effing smart.
You should be teaching me.
Pam, get us back into it.
Okay.
Five movies. Go ahead.
Fargo, Edward Scissorhands,
Dazed and Confused.
Oh, definitely in my top five.
Yes, in my top three,
so suck it.
Breakfast Club.
What?
The Princess Bride and...
Okay, that's five.
No, my all-time favorite!
Pam, play by the rules.
All-time favorite!
Play by the rules.
Dwight,
all-time favorite movie.
The Crow.
I became a salesman
because of people.
I love making friends.
But then I was promoted
to manager, very young age.
I still try to be
a friend first,
but, you know,
when you're very successful,
your co-workers
look at you differently.
What do you think?
Maybe we should get some air.
No, I'm okay.
I'm really uncomfortable.
All right. Let's move on.
Let's move on to the main
event, "Who would you do?"
Present company excluded?
Not necessarily.
Pam.
Um...
Okay. You know what? Maybe I'll
finish explaining the rules.
Let me explain it first
and then...
Yeah, so we'll get right... You
know what? I'll be right back.
Stanley, you're taking over for
me, buddy. I'll be right back.
Okay.
Dwight.
Dwight!
Come one, Dwight, use words.
Why didn't I
go to business school?
Who goes to business school?
The temp.
He does?
Yeah, it's all him and Michael
talk about anymore.
You know, I bet
Ryan thinks to himself,
"I wish I were a volunteer
sheriff on the weekend. "
He doesn't even know
that I do that.
You should tell him.
Oh, yeah, Pam, right. That's gonna
help things. Just talk it out.
I hope the war goes on forever
and Ryan gets drafted.
Dwight.
What?
I'm sorry I said that.
I didn't...
Just part of me meant it.
Besides, he'd end up
being a hero anyway.
You know what you should do?
You should quit.
And then, that would stick it
to both of them.
No, Jim. I'm not gonna quit.
Then Ryan wins.
Yeah, you're right.
Thanks, you guys.
I just need some alone time.
Okay.
All right, buddy.
Hey. Guys, what's going on?
Nothing.
Hey.
What's up?
Can I hang out
with you guys for a bit?
The warehouse guys are a
bunch of jackasses sometimes.
Come on, people, you know
the rules of the game, now.
Hey, gang.
What game are we playing here?
Okay, it's called,
"Who would you do?"
Oh, I play this at home
all the time
while I'm falling asleep.
What... Where are we?
Where are we here?
Roy.
Roy?
Roy? Who would you do, Roy?
Oh, I got it.
What's the name of that
tight-ass Christian chick.
The blonde?
My name is Angela.
Hey, Angela.
Roy, nice to meet you.
All right, who's next?
Who's next? Who's next?
Who's... Jim? You're next.
Who would you do?
Kevin, hands down.
Yeah, I mean he's really got
that teddy bear thing going on
and afterwards we could
just watch bowling.
Well, I would
definitely have sex with Ryan,
'cause he is gonna
own his own business.
You're all gay.
Who's next? Who we got?
Who...
Hey. No, I can talk.
I can talk. I can talk.
Yeah, it's a great time.
Well, I wish I had my cell
phone, but I left it inside, so...
Would that make you happy?
What's that? If you had your cell
phone, it would make you happy?
Yeah.
I'm on it.
Dwight. Hey, Dwight!
You can't go back in yet.
He is an idiot. The man is an
idiot, ladies and gentlemen.
What if he dies in the fire,
and that's the last thing
you ever said to him?
I didn't say it to him.
I said it about him.
Jim?
Definitely Jim.
Definitely, definitely Jim.
Come on, Pam. Come on.
What about you, Pam?
Oscar's kind of cute.
Yeah, I like Oscar.
Ooh, Toby.
How long does it take
to find a cell phone?
I don't know either.
Is there anybody else?
Hey, where are you?
Oh, good.
Yeah, we're just here.
We're playing "desert island. "
It's when you pick
your five favorite DVDs.
Seriously,
where the hell is Dwight?
Hey, call my cell phone.
It'll make it
easier for him to find.
What's your number?
I gave it to you in the car.
I saw you program it in.
You gotta give it to me again.
Okay. All right.
Now I have it.
Uh...
I better tell somebody.
Excuse me, sir?
Dwight! Dwight!
Oh, God, man!
Why did you go in there?
What? Everybody was scared out
of their wits, man.
Everyone, okay,
I have an announcement.
Apparently,
in business school,
they don't teach you
how to operate a toaster oven,
because some smart, sexy temp
left his cheese pita
on "oven" instead of timing it
for the toaster thing.
Oh, wow, okay.
Well, I guess they don't teach how to
operate a toaster oven in business school.
That's exactly what I said.
Hey, did you miss
that day, there, Ryan?
Were you absent?
Toaster Oven 101.
You failed?
I'm so sorry.
Oh, man.
"Hey, I know what'll impress
everybody. I'll start a fire. "
Oh, man.
Bad idea. Bad idea jeans.
I have a song, attention
everyone, that I wanna sing,
that I wrote especially for this occasion
when I was up there among the flames.
Ready?
Ryan started the fire!
It was always burning since
the world's been turning!
Ryan started the fire!
It was always burning
since the world was turning!
Everybody!
I can't believe
I started the fire.
Marilyn Monroe!
Ryan started the fire!
It was always burning
Eat it. Yeah, eat it.
You have to eat it.
Hey.
How are you?
Good. How are you?
I'm good.
It's good to see you.
Good to see you, too.
I'm hungry.
Yeah, I am, too.
Oh, I have been thinking
the whole way over,
and I have my answers.
What answers?
For the "desert island. "
Oh, right! Right, right,
right. Come on, come on.
Ladies and gentlemen, gather
around. We have one more participant.
Come on, be polite. Be polite.
Hi. Desert island, five movies, go.
Okay, first,
Legally Blonde.
I forgot what
a super-nice girl Katy is.
And just good for Jim.
They are so cute together.
And what an adorable car.
Okay, I think the game's over.
People are, like, leaving.
There was a bigger crowd
last time.
Do you wanna just go to lunch?
Okay.
Yeah?
All right.
You wanna drive?
Sure.
All right.
They are so cute.
I'm really sorry, Dwight.
Answer me this, though.
What?
Was it worth it?
Was it worth it, temp?
No.
Was it worth it?
Really?
I'm really sorry, Dwight.
The fire guy. The fire guy!
Joe McCarthy, Richard Nixon
Studebaker, Television
North Korea, South Korea,
Marilyn Monroe!
Ryan started the fire!
Okay, rule five: Safety first,
i. e. Don't burn
the building down.
Okay?
That should be a no-brainer.
Oh, look, Ryan is book smart,
and I am street smart
and book smart.
I'll give you
the rest of the 10 tomorrow.