Angela.
What?
That was a voicemail
that corporate left last night.
They did not get our tax forms.
Did you send them?
They arrived this morning.
Are you sure?
It is a big deal if...
Is it a big deal?
Is it, Kevin?
Do you really not know?
Because it is a big deal.
AND Y: Five of us transferred from Stamford.
There's two of us left. Me and Karen.
It's like we're touring
Willy Wonka's Chocolate Factory
and dropping off one by one.
Well, guess what?
I'm not falling in a chocolate river.
Everything okay?
It's fine. You are in the clear.
Thank you.
I don't want those.
Dwight, care to join us? Finally.
Thank you.
Hey, Dwight, pass the tardy sauce.
Get it, Michael?
Yes.
Okay.
Here is the dream team.
My sales dream team.
Today we are going to team up
for sales calls.
Andy, since this was your idea,
you get to pick first.
Well, let me think about this for a minute.
Oh, I don't know. Michael Scott?
PhD. Doctor of sales.
MICHAEL: Well, I appreciate that.
That's very gracious of you.
Well, it is very gracious of you to accept.
Well, thank you, sir.
Okay, now going by seniority.
Phyllis, our resident senior.
We're the same age.
And I'll pick Karen.
Oh, thanks.
MICHAEL: Good.
Next up, the Super Fly himself, Stanley.
Pass.
You can't pass. You gotta pick somebody.
I'll take the kid.
I'm very flattered.
I was his second choice after pass.
So that just leaves Dwight and Jim.
Okay, wait. Does anyone want to trade?
Yeah, I'll trade.
Dwight and I used to go on sales calls
all the time.
In fact, I have a picture
to remember that time.
Oh, young Jim.
There's just so much I need
to warn you about
and yet, tragically, I cannot.
Sebring by Chrysler.
A heck of a motor carriage.
Dwight!
DWIGHT: Yeah?
Here you go.
Yeah!
You want shirts on hangers?
Please.
He does your laundry?
Long story.
All right, everybody, circle up!
MICHAEL: Here we go.
You know what this is?
This is The Amazing Race.
And you guys are retired Marines,
and you guys are the mother-daughter,
and you guys are the gay couple,
and we are the firefighter heroes.
Are we ready to go?
KAREN: Wait.
Amazing Race, like, the biggest sale wins?
No. We're just gonna rush out,
do the sales thing and come back.
Is there a prize?
Just bragging rights.
Then how is this Amazing Race?
It's just...
(EXCLAIMS)
It's Amazing Race, Phyllis, okay?
We're in teams of two
and we're on a mission.
All right. So, on your mark. Get set. Go.
Let's do it.
Come on!
Michael...
(LAUGHS)
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
Do you have a pole?
Let's go get a broom.
Seriously, are you gonna sit in the back?
Yeah. It's the safest part of a car.
In the event of a crash,
the driver always protects his side first.
Here we go.
AND Y: In order to take down Dwight,
I have to chip away at his ally.
In this case, Michael.
And here's the good news.
Every success I've ever had in my job
or with the lady folk
has come from my ability
to slowly and painfully wear someone down.
What's the deal
with Dwight doing your laundry?
That is a long story.
A couple of months ago,
Dwight tried to go behind my back with Jan
and get my job.
And I am now having him
do my laundry as punishment.
Wow. That is a long story,
but quite well told, Michael.
I find it very interesting.
Especially the part about Dwight
going behind your back
and basically being, like, a terrible person.
You know,
if you want your laundry done right,
I used to work at Abercrombie, so...
Pretty good folder.
Hey, Pam.
Would you like to go with me
to grab a coffee?
Really?
Yeah.
I thought you could use some fresh air
and it might be fun.
Okay. Sure.
Okay.
Why are we turning in here?
This is a beauty salon.
Hey, do you mind if I take
the lead on this one
and then you can critique me after?
You want the lead?
Yeah, if you don't mind.
Mind?
Nothing would delight me more.
Leave the keys.
You still do that thing?
(MUSIC PLAYING ON STEREO)
I think that you have assembled
an amazing team at Scranton.
It's really a pleasure to be a part of it.
It's like everyone has their own special skill,
you know.
Just like the Super Friends.
Except for Dwight,
who's kind of more of a Super Dud.
I mean, he'd be a Super Friend
if there was a Super Friend
whose super power was always being late.
You know?
Hawkman.
My plan is taking longer than I thought,
but I don't give up easily.
(TOILET FLUSHING)
I have walked two marathons, so...
Let's go.
The men's room was disgusting.
After you, sir.
No, thank you.
I never let anyone walk behind me.
Seven out of 10 attacks are from the rear.
Okay. Well, that still leaves a 30% chance
that I'll attack you from the front.
Yeah, but it'll be easier to stop.
I can always block the blow.
Or I can counter it...
Angela, you seem so happy.
I bet you wish you were like this all the time.
This friend of mine... Let's call her "Noel."
She missed this deadline turning something
into corporate in New York.
But then this gallant gentleman,
we'll call him "Kurt."
He drove all the way to New York
and handed it in for her.
That's... I don't know.
I guess he just really likes her a lot.
Well, that's great.
Yes, it is.
Hello?
Hey.
Did you catch that up
at Lake Wallenpaupack?
Yeah.
You know, I used to go up there
all the time with my step-dad
and I never caught anything that big.
I caught an 80-pound shark off Montauk.
That's in the Hamptons.
My dad's got a 42-foot Bayliner.
Sniped it with a rifle from the crow's- nest.
Also shot a deer once.
You know what? Let's get right down to it.
Dunder Mifflin may be just two rooms
and a warehouse,
but what we lack in flash,
we will make up for with hard work
and decency.
Okay, this is the classic undersell.
Because you should know
we don't work out of a log cabin.
We trade on the New York Stock Exchange.
Ever heard of it? It's in New York.
I have to say I'm a little wary
of getting involved with a big company.
We've had some problems in the past.
And I think what Andy is
trying to express is that
while we have the resources
of a large company,
we will give you the care and attention
of a small company.
Man, that is like poetry.
I swear.
No.
This guy could sell paper to a tree stump.
I'm so sorry, man.
I really screwed that up.
I really...
No. Don't worry about it.
I really Schruted it.
What?
I Schruted it.
It's just this thing people say
around your office all the time.
Like when you screw something up in
a really irreversible way,
you Schruted it.
I don't know where it comes from, though.
You think it comes from Dwight Schrute?
I don't know. Who knows
how words are formed.
Dunder Mifflin, this is Pam.
This is Pam.
I did?
Yeah, I did a watercolor
of Francis Willard Elementary School
for a contest they were having.
They were calling with the results.
And I won.
I won. My painting won!
So I'd like to thank my mom
for always encouraging me.
And I'd like to thank my dad
for buying me my first set of art pencils.
And I'd like to thank the sixth-grade class
that picked me.
It's a big order.
Thanks, Ken.
Yeah, thank you.
Hey, how's Annie?
She's great.
This is us last year in Bermuda.
Lovely place. You ever been to Bermuda?
JULIUS: Stanley Hudson.
Julius, how's it going?
Great, great, great.
Stanley, so good to see you.
You, too.
I'd like you fellows to meet Ryan Howard.
Hi.
Yeah. I'm gonna let Ryan do a little pitch
for you while I do my crossword puzzle.
Ryan.
Hi. Hi. Hi.
Hello, Ryan.
Hi.
What do you have for us?
We can offer our biggest discounts
on 30% recycled and ultra premium laser.
Okay. Okay.
Can I use your phone?
Yeah, sure. Go ahead.
Thanks.
Let me talk to you about a few
of the other things we can offer.
Namely, we know that tax season's
coming up,
so by April 1st
we can have you fully stocked.
We have discount prices on ink cartridges.
DWIGHT: One.
Three.
And also any forms
that you're gonna need...
Seven.
...we can custom make them.
Hey, Kev, guess what?
I won an art contest today.
How much did you win?
$100.
I won 400 bucks
on the Celtics game last night.
Cool. Congratulations.
Thanks.
It was so sweet.
(LAUGHING)
And you just said, "Hi! Hi! Hi!"
You sounded like my niece.
And she's six months old!
Well, I appreciate what you guys are saying,
but it makes more fiscal sense
to go with one of the big guys.
Sure.
That's true.
We can't compete with their prices.
But let me ask you something.
How important to you is customer service?
Very.
ELECTRONIC VOICE: Please keep holding.
Your call is very important to us.
That's one of the big guys.
Been on hold this whole time.
And this is Dunder Mifflin.
KELLY: Dunder Mifflin customer service.
This is Kelly.
Hey, Kelly, it's Jim.
Oh, my God! Jim! How are you?
I wanted to tell you...
Here's my card.
It's got my cell number, my pager number,
my home number
and my other pager number.
I never take vacations. I never get sick.
And I don't celebrate any major holidays.
All right. I get it.
We got a deal.
All right.
Hey, Angela, I got good news today, too.
I won an art contest.
That's great, Pam.
I like having these little moments with you.
You know what?
Sprinkles recently had kittens.
I would like to offer you the dominant male.
His name is Ash.
I don't think so. But thanks.
My building manager is...
You understand.
Well then, have a nice day.
Thanks. That was fun.
Yeah. I really enjoy spending time with you.
You're a very nice person.
Thank you.
I'm so glad you're with Jim.
He was hung-up on Pam
for such a long time.
I didn't think he'd ever get over her.
That's nice.
You can pay me back later for the makeover.
AND Y: Hey, boss. Got a minute?
MICHAEL: Yes, Andy.
AND Y: I forget. Why did Dwight say
he was late this morning?
MICHAEL: He didn't say.
That's weird.
Because I was just walking past his desk
and I saw this,
which is a toll booth receipt
from New York City,
stamped really early this morning.
So...
Why would Dwight go to New York
without telling anyone?
You think he went to see Jan?
That's not like him, is it?
Someone told me a story about this...
With like laundry and betrayal.
Did you betray Dwight
and try to steal his job or something?
No.
You are remembering it wrong.
Dwight betrayed me once before.
So this is his strike two.
You know what they say?
"Fool me once, strike one.
"But fool me twice,
"strike three."
JAN: Dwight's name is on
the security sign-in sheet,
but I don't know who he met with.
And where it asks to state your business,
he wrote,
"Beeswax Not Yours Incorporated."
I knew it.
Oh, doggie.
Hey, you wanna grab a coffee?
Sure.
Look at you.
Yeah.
Beesly, coffee?
No, thanks, I had some already.
All right.
But, hey, Jim.
Yeah?
I won an art contest today.
No way!
Yeah.
All right, Pam. Congratulations.
Thanks.
Which one was it?
I sent them one of my watercolors.
Cool.
It was a new one I did.
Are you ready, Jim?
Yeah. Can I see it when I get back?
Yeah.
Congratulations.
Thanks.
Big deal.
Hey! We nailed the sale.
Where were you this morning?
I overslept. Damn rooster didn't crow.
Why do you lie, liar?
I'm not a liar.
You are lying right now.
Sure seems like he's lying.
Stay out of this, you!
I know that you went
to corporate this morning.
And I know that you lied about it.
And given our history,
I need you to tell me right now
exactly what you were doing this morning.
Michael, I cannot tell you
what I was doing there.
But you have to trust me.
I would never do anything
to hurt you or this company.
Okay, you know what?
I want you to think about your future
at this company.
I want you to think about it long and hard.
That's what she said.
Don't...
Don't you dare.
I want to know what you were doing
this morning by the end of the day.
It's gonna be okay.
How's it gonna be okay, Dwight?
Everyone will know our business.
Well, that's not the worst thing in the world.
I'll just stand up in front of the office
and reveal our true love.
It won't be that bad. Look at Kelly and Ryan.
I hate those two people
more than anything in the entire world.
Well, I don't have a lot of choices.
KAREN: So, let me ask you a question.
Okay.
Did you ever have a thing for Pam?
Pam? Did I ever have a thing for her? No.
Why? Did she say something?
I moved here from Connecticut.
Yeah.
Okay, here's the...
I had a crush on her before I left.
And I told her about it
and she didn't feel the same way.
So it didn't amount to anything and I left.
I'm really glad you're here.
Okay?
Okay.
(CLEARING THROAT)
May I have your attention, please?
This will only take a moment of your time.
"Although I love this company
more than almost anything in the world,
"I have decided to step down from my post
and spend more time with my family.
"I do not fear the unknown.
"I will meet my new challenges head on
and I will succeed.
"And I will laugh in the faces
of those who doubt me.
"It's been a pleasure working
with some of you
"and I will not forget those of you soon.
"But remember, while today it is me,
"we all shall fall."
In other words, I'm quitting, so...
(SINGING) Oompa, Loompa,
doom-pa-dee-dawesome
Dwight is now gone,
which is totally awesome
Why was he gone?
He was such a nice guy
No, he was not
He was a total douche
Doompa-dee-doom
I would like to give the rest
of my belongings to Michael Scott.
Just take it.
Except this.
Good luck.
And this one.
Dwight will be missed.
Not by me so much, but he will be missed.
Dwight from sales
was one of the most honorable
and efficient employees
this company has ever had.
DWIGHT: One of my life goals was
to die right here in my desk chair.
And today, that dream was shattered.
Hey, man.
What happened on your sales call?
Am I happy about
the way things turned out?
Oh, "Happy's" such an ugly word,
but I saw what needed to be done
and I did it and now I'm thrilled.
So, it's pretty...
Hello?
Pretty good.