Yeah, everything!
It's all good! Phyllis.
- Dancing babies!
- Dancing babies. I love it!
We are making a commercial
for Dunder Mifflin today.
Our first ad ever.
Corporate purchased
some airtime in local markets
to spread the word
about Dunder Mifflin Infinity,
and they are even sending up
a professional ad company
to help us make it later, so...
it's not too shabby.
Best ad ever?
¶ Gimme a break ¶
¶ Break me off a piece of that... ¶
I am totally blanking.
What is the thing?
- Nobody tell him!
- What? No... Why?
You got it.
You're so close.
¶ Break me off a piece of that ¶
¶ Bre... apple sauce ¶
Break me off a piece
of that apple sauce. I don't think...
¶ piece of that chrysler car ¶
- Nope.
- ¶ football cream ¶
Okay.
Football cream.
It's football cream.
All right, so anybody else?
I'm taking a computer animation class,
so I could try to do a logo.
Look at that.
Even the receptionist is getting in
on the creativity.
Very good.
Hello, hello.
- How you doing?
- Michael Scott, regional manager.
- Nice to meet you. Us too, man.
- Excited to talk ideas.
You know what?
I want this to be cutting edge.
I want it to be fast,
quick cuts, you know?
Youthful,
sort of a MTV on crack kind of thing.
- That sounds great.
- All right.
This is what we have to work with.
I would like you to meet Andrew Bernard.
The 'nard dog.
Who let the 'nard dog out?
He gives
the best back rubs in the office.
That's true. I give a mean back rub.
I also do good aromatherapy.
Not!
You just got 'nard dogged!
Now this gentleman right here
is the key to our...
- urban vibe.
- Urban?
I grew up in a small town.
What about me seems urban to you?
Stanley's hilarious.
Phyllis is like our Mrs. Butterworth.
Kind of a less urban aunt Jemima.
These are our accountants.
And as you can see,
they are very different sizes.
What you might wanna do
is kind of a papa bear,
mama bear, baby bear thing.
- That might be kind of fun.
- Mama bear.
Who else?
I think it's great
that the company's making a commercial.
Because
not very many people have heard of us.
When I tell people
that I work at Dunder Mifflin,
they think that we sell mufflers,
or muffins, or mittens, or...
And frankly, all of those sound better
than paper, so I let it slide.
T
Tr
Tra
Tran
Trans
Transc
Transcr
Transcri
Transcrip
Transcript
Transcript:
Transcript: S
Transcript: Sw
Transcript: SwS
Transcript: SwSu
Transcript: SwSub
S
Sy
Transcript: SwSub
Syn
Sync
Transcript: SwSub
Synch
Synchr
Transcript: SwSub
Synchro
Synchro:
Transcript: SwSub
Synchro: D
Synchro: Da
Transcript: SwSub
Synchro: Dar
Synchro: DarK
Transcript: SwSub
Synchro: DarKs
Synchro: DarKsh
Resync:
nadielostzilla.
Episode 4x05
"LOCAL AD"
- You playing that game again?
- Second life is not a game.
It is a multi-user virtual environment.
It doesn't have points or scores.
It doesn't have winners or losers.
Oh, it has losers.
I signed up for Second Life
about a year ago.
Back then my life was so great
that I literally wanted a second one.
In my second life,
I was also a paper salesman,
and I was also named Dwight.
Absolutely everything was the same,
except I could fly.
Little girl
in a field holding a flower.
We zoom back
to find that she's in the desert,
and the field is an oasis.
We zoom back further.
The desert is a sandbox
in the world's largest resort hotel.
Zoom back further.
The hotel
is actually the playground...
of the world's largest prison.
- Zoom back further...
- Okay. I can tell your time's valuable.
Actually I don't get paid
by the hour anymore, but thank you.
I get paid by the year, so...
That all sounds really ambitious.
Yeah, I know.
Why don't we show you
what we did with the national branch.
Okay.
That's what national came up with?
That sucks!
That's what we came up with.
We can do better than that.
The main part of the ad
must stay the same, actually.
Yeah, it's the last five seconds
where we've some leeway.
The waving?
Well no. You won't be waving.
That was just what they did.
You guys can be clapping, sitting.
Standing outside, inside, whatever.
I mean, this is where you really get
to be creative.
I need some advice.
Been spending a lot of time
making out with Angela lately.
We've been necking,
but only necking, right?
Not actually kissing...
our mouths.
Just a neck on neck.
It's just like rubbing/nuzzling
our necks together.
It's hot, I'm not gonna lie to you.
But it's a little weird.
But you seem like a guy with answers.
So how do I fast-track this,
get to first base?
We cannot talk about this,
because...
someone might hear us.
We'll use code names.
Angela can stay the same,
but we'll change Andy to Dwight.
That's not different enough.
Dwike?
You have a call from Eddie Murphy.
Hello?
Shrek!
Shrek, I'm a donkey!
I'm a donkey, Shrek!
I'm just kidding.
It's me.
Hello, Ry.
- What?
- Okay,
calm down.
I just have a small problem.
I told you not to call
about small problems.
Well when I call about big problems,
you don't like that either,
so make up your mind, kiddo.
Here is the deal.
The ad guys that you sent
are locking me in a creative box
and sort of ignoring my ideas.
That's good.
They're creative, you're not.
I'm creative, Ryan.
It's not part of your job.
It's like, maybe you can cook,
but that doesn't mean
you should start a restaurant.
Well, actually I can't cook,
and I'm starting a restaurant.
"Mike's Cereal Shack."
I'm thinking we'll have as many
varieties as you can buy in the store.
I'm not really interested
in that right now.
I'm delegating creativity
to creative professionals.
It's a different skill set.
Look, I wasn't good at sales, right?
But I'm good
- at managing people who do sales.
- Are you?
I don't think you're doing
such a great job here,
suppressing ideas and creativity.
All right, let me ask you this.
Tell me if you think this is creative.
When I was five,
I imagined that there was such a thing
as a unicorn.
And this is before I had even
heard of one or seen one.
I just drew a picture of a horse
that could fly over rainbows
and had a huge spike in its head.
I was five.
Five years old.
Couldn't even talk yet.
Hey, guys.
You know what?
We cannot shoot this ad today.
- Okay, when should we come back?
- How about never hundred hours, sir?
- Wait, we were sent here to he...
- I'm not gonna argue with this guy.
Let's go.
Good luck, dude.
- Hey thanks. Thank you.
- Thank you.
Michael, David Wallace.
What is this
about dismissing the ad people?
Yeah, I'm glad you called.
Ryan is being a little bitch again.
- I'm on, Michael.
- What's up, my brother?
Listen, David.
I would like to do this ad in house.
I want to use only
the creativity
that we have right here in the office.
And I will send it to you
tomorrow morning. Take a look at it.
If you don't think it's ready to air,
send the ad agency back down here
and we'll do it on my dime.
This is weird.
I'm willing to stake
my entire reputation on it.
Okay.
I'll see it tomorrow.
- Okay.
And thus...
Michael Scott sealed his own destiny...
in a good way.
Has anyone ever come up to you and said,
"You're not creative."
Yes.
Well, they're wrong.
You are creative.
You are damn creative.
Each and every one of you.
You are so much more creative
than all of the other dry, boring morons
that you work with.
Who you talking to specifically?
I kind of know
what it's like to be in commercials.
My nickname in high school
used to be kool-aid man.
Younger, I always wanted
to be an actor in commercials,
then I realized I had a brain.
I'm excited about doing the ad,
but I'm not really used to doing videos
with so many people around.
We have three scenes to film,
big scenes.
We have a song to write,
so let's get cracking.
Kelly, I want you to do make-up.
Oscar, I would like you
to do costume design obviously.
I'd like you to look around town
and see if we have any celebrities
in our local area.
Sue Grafton is at the steamtown mall!
She's doing a book signing right now.
Phyllis, this is what I want you to do.
I want you to go down to the mall.
I want you to get in line.
I want you to get her
to be in this commercial.
This would be a huge coupe,
people, all right?
- Do not take no for an answer.
- Okay.
Does anyone actually know
what Sue Grafton looks like?
- I mean, is she hot or...
- She's crazy hot.
Well then maybe we should just use
Angela and say she's Sue Grafton.
- Would anyone notice?
- That's not happening.
I find the mystery genre disgusting.
I hate being titillated.
- Light it up!
- Get her, Phyl.
¶ Out of paper
Out of stock ¶
¶ There's friendly faces
around the block ¶
¶ Break loose from the chains
that are causing your pain ¶
¶ Call Michael or Stanley ¶
¶ Jim, Dwight, or Creed ¶
¶ Call indian Kelly
for your business paper needs ¶
¶ Dunder Mifflin
the people person's paper people ¶
Time out, time out.
I thought...
I was under the impression
that this was going to be a rap.
What's rap?
Okay, Darryl...
You need to learn about
your own culture. I'll make you a mix.
Great.
News flash.
I got some juicy updates
on operation fallen angel.
Remind me to tell you later.
Hey.
Eh, no talk.
I'm animating.
Why don't we take
a quick ten second break from that
so I can show you what's going on here.
Okay, this is Dwight's second life.
He's on it all the time.
So much so that his little guy here
has created his own world.
It's called Second Second Life,
for those people who want to be removed
even further from reality.
- Are you serious?
- Yeah.
Oh, my god.
He's really in pain.
Who's that?
Oh, it's just my avatar guy, whatever.
He looks a lot like you!
How much time did you spend on that?
Not much.
- It's just for tracking Dwight.
- Right.
You're a sportswriter in Philadelphia?
Nice build too.
Yep.
You have a guitar slung on your back.
I did not know you played guitar.
I...
Why don't we go back to the animation?
No, no!
I want to see more of Philly Jim.
I want Philly Jim.
Ah, show me how this works.
Oh, boy.
¶ Out of paper ¶
¶ Out of stock ¶
¶ There's friendly faces
around the block ¶
¶ Break loose from the chains ¶
¶ that are causing you pain ¶
¶ Call Mike and Stanley
Jim, Dwight, and creed ¶
¶ Call indian Kelly
for your business paper needs ¶
¶ Call Dunder Mifflin ¶
¶ people person's paper people ¶
¶ Dunder Mifflin ¶
¶ people person's pape... ¶
Stop, stop, stop, stop.
This is not me.
This is not... This is not my music.
You're right.
It's better than you.
It's us.
¶ Dunder Mifflin
people person's paper... ¶
No, no, no... I hate it!
I hate it.
I don't hate it.
I just don't like it at all.
And it's terrible.
- You're on your own, Mike.
- Okay, you know what?
Hold on, Darryl.
- You just said you hated it.
- No, I said I...
I hate the style.
¶ Break me off a piece
of that lumber tar ¶
- ¶ Snickers bar ¶
- Okay.
This looks terrible.
¶ break me off a piece... ¶
Andy, Andy!
It's a pivotal scene in the ad.
And if we don't get this,
if we don't nail it,
we're gonna lose
the whole triumph of the moment.
The triumph of the will.
Now?
God, what?
What, Phyllis?
Well,
I got in line to buy Sue Grafton's book.
On my turn, I asked her
if she wanted to be in the ad,
and she said "No, thanks," but I wasn't
supposed to take "no" for an answer.
- That a girl.
- So I kept on asking,
and they finally threw me out
of the store in front of all my friends.
Did you or did you not get Sue Grafton?
No.
Can somebody give her a tissue, please?
Hope you're not killing yourself on it.
'Cause I'm sure it's good enough
for Michael's ad
that will probably be seen by no one.
Maybe,
but it's not good enough for me yet.
Okay.
Do you want me to stay?
No, no, you can go home.
I'm good.
Pam is staying late tonight
to achieve her dreams.
So I'm pretty proud of her.
- Unfortunately, she was my ride home.
- You comin'?
I...
Piss or get off the pot.
- Dunder Mifflin, this is Pam.
- Good morning.
Yeah, sorry. I looked away for a second,
and Creed snatched your hash browns.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
I worked until about 2:45 AM.
And then I had to decide
if I wanted to spend the night
with Michael editing in his office,
and Dwight
watching Michael edit in his office,
or drive home
and probably fall asleep at the wheel
and die in a fiery car wreck.
I passed out on my keyboard
trying to decide.
Let me pour you some bubbly,
because somebody got
to a whole new level last night.
Andy, I can't hear this right now.
No, no, this is good.
You know how we haven't gotten anywhere
that I want to get to physically yet?
Well, last night that changed.
We're making out.
I'm kissing her neck,
and her cheek, and her earlobe.
And she's not really kissing me back,
but she closes her eyes
and she's, like,
"Oh, D.
Oh, D."
She called you D?
Yeah.
D for Andy.
Oh, D.
I'm about to send the ad to corporate.
And it is sent.
They'll probably watch it right away.
I would.
Okay.
- Yes?
- Pam, please clear my phone lines.
Certainly.
Okay, clear.
They could call any second now.
Oh, god.
I better call.
Well, it's been tough.
The geniuses at corporate
rejected my commercial.
And tonight
they are airing the brain-dead version.
So welcome one and all
to the world premiere
of corporate crapfest!
- Hey, seemed like a big hit.
- No, people are stupid.
People like waving.
Waving sells.
It's not art.
Yet we made our ad.
The real one was full of humor,
and full of depth,
and full of heart.
And it was real.
Hey, could you do me a favor?
Could you put that in the dvd player?
Hey, everybody. Just want
to welcome you all to the premiere
of the real Dunder Mifflin commercial.
The Michael Scott director's cut.
Hope you like it.
It all starts with an idea.
But you can never tell
where an idea will end up.
Because ideas spread.
They change, grow.
They connect us with the world.
And in a fast moving world,
where good news
moves at the speed of time...
and bad news
isn't always what it seems.
Because when push comes to shove,
we all deserve a second chance...
to score.
Dunder Mifflin.
Limitless paper in a paperless world.
Really good.
Animation?
All her, by the way.
- Really? The animation was cool.
- Thanks.
You ever been on a motorcycle?
Michael, that was fun.
That was fun.
Next round of drinks is on me, people.
¶ Claude Van Damme ¶
¶ Hair for men ¶
¶ Poison gas ¶
¶ Nutrasweet ¶
It's gotta rhyme with "piece".
Fancy feast!
¶ Break me off a piece
of that fancy feast ¶
It's a cat food.
Nailed it.