PAM: (ON PHONE)
Well, I should go.
All right.
I'll tell everybody here
that you say hi.
No, don't.
I'm mad at them.
(CHUCKLES) Why?
What happened?
Not one of them called
to congratulate me
on our engagement.
Ah!
That, they might be
off the hook for,
because I didn't tell them.
What? Why not?
(SOFTLY) I just didn't,
you know, want to deal.
Come on.
It won't be that bad.
Okay. You know what?
Here we go.
Everybody,
I just want to make
an announcement.
Pam and I are engaged.
(ON SPEAKER)
Hi, everyone!
I thought you were
already engaged.
Nope.
That was Roy.
She was engaged to Roy.
Thank you, Angela.
I got a gift for Pam and Roy.
Do I have to get another one?
Yes.
A little close to
my engagement there, Tuna.
What's your game here?
To get married.
She's not a virgin,
you know.
Wow!
What's going on?
No. Nothing.
Nothing, Michael.
Just saying hi.
The tall guy got engaged.
To be married?
Yep.
(GRUNTS)
Sorry.
Pencils down!
Just kidding.
Take your time.
HOLLY: Today is Ethics Day.
After they finish the quiz,
I'm going to run
my first meeting here.
It's going to be insane.
No, it's not. I have
to read from the binder.
I got it. I got it.
(POP MUSIC PLAYING)
(BO TH SINGING)
Let's get ethical, ethical
I want to get ethical
Let's get into ethics, yeah
Let me hear
Dunder Mifflin talk
Your body talk
Let me hear your body talk
(WHOOPS) All right!
"Why are you helping her?
You're not even dating."
She's my friend.
And ultimately my strategy is
to sort of merge this
into a relationship
without her even knowing.
Okay! Let's give it up
for Miss Holly Flax!
HOLLY: Thanks, Michael.
(EXHALING)
Today we're going to have
a business ethics seminar
because recently,
without mentioning any names,
there has been some
misconduct at corporate
and we have a very strict
ethics policy and that
employee has been fired.
Come on. He's right there.
He was hired.
Check it out, hired guy.
Nice.
Okay, elephant in the room.
Let's talk about it.
Do I regret what I did?
Of course I do.
Even though it was
an amazing ride
and I'll give an example.
Anyone see Survivor,
Season Six? Anyone know
JoAnna on that show?
In New York City,
I hooked up with a girl
who looked exactly like that.
Indistinguishable. So...
Okay. Well done.
Good speech, Ryan.
You're a good guy.
Let's start discussing
those questionnaires that
you filled in this morning.
It is wrong to make
personal calls
during work hours.
Now, some of you marked
that you very strongly agree.
But ideally,
you would have selected
"totally agree."
I thought "very strongly
agree" sounded stronger
than "totally agree."
Corporate would like
to emphasize that ideally
you would all totally agree
with that statement.
Well, I think we can
all totally agree that
Holly is totally fantastic.
(MICHAEL CLAPPING)
Thank you.
Okay. Okay.
In fact, spending a half hour
at the water cooler
during work hours
is a form of stealing.
What?
HOLLY: Yes.
It's called "time theft"
and it's the same as taking
money from the company.
Can anyone think of examples
of things that are
over-the-line time wasters?
This meeting.
(MEN CHEERING)
Can't set them up like that.
Why is it okay for smokers
to take breaks all the time?
If I want to go outside and
hang out once an hour, then
I'll just take up smoking.
I'll do it. I don't care.
MEREDITH:
I'll smoke with you.
I got a bag of cigars
in my purse.
Stealing office supplies
is another big ethical area
that there seems to be
some confusion about.
Okay. Could we have
a moment?
(WHISPERING)
Can I talk to you
for a second?
(WHISPERS) Yeah.
A lot of good stuff.
And you look...
You look fantastic.
Michael.
Yeah?
What should we be working on
while you guys are talking?
Do some...
Do some work.
(WHISPERING)
People expect a lot
from these meetings.
Laughter, sudden twists,
surprise endings,
you need to be Robin Williams
and M. Night Shyamalan.
You need to be
Robin Shyamalan.
(WHISPERING) Well,
I just have to get
through the binder.
You're... It's just,
you're kind of losing them.
I am?
Yeah.
Don't think about the stakes.
It'll freak you out.
Okay. Well,
Michael makes
a really good point.
So, let's just open
this up a little bit.
Say my name is Lauren
and here I am shopping
in a supermarket
and I steal a pencil.
That's not right.
(COUGHING) Lauren!
Enough with the pencils!
No. I have to
go over pencils
and office supplies.
It's part of
the ethics thing.
That isn't ethics.
Ethics is a real discussion
of competing conceptions
of the good.
This is just the corporate
anti-shoplifting rules.
I'll drop an ethics bomb
on you. Would you steal
bread to feed your family?
Boom!
Exactly, Andy.
Yeah. I took Intro
to Philosophy twice.
No big deal.
It's a trick question.
The bread is poisoned.
Also, it's not
your real family.
You've been cuckolded
by a stronger, smarter male.
No, that's not
how it works.
I would not steal the bread.
And I would not let
my family go hungry.
HOLLY: Okay.
But we should get
back to business.
Have any of you
ever faced any ethical
dilemmas in the workplace?
MICHAEL: Anybody?
This is a chance
for you to say something
without any repercussions.
Stanley?
Oscar, come on.
I'll pass.
I will go first.
When I discovered YouTube,
I didn't work for five days.
I did nothing.
I viewed Cookie Monster
Sings Chocolate Rain
about 1,000 times.
What was the dilemma?
To tell you or not.
And I'm glad I did.
I feel very, very good.
Cathartic.
I promise you that
you are not going
to get into trouble.
You can say anything
you want with total
and complete immunity.
Oh, no, no, no.
Yeah. Come on.
Anybody. Let it fly.
Okay. Once in a while,
I'll take a long lunch.
A siesta.
Time thief.
Time thief. Fire him!
Dwight, you've really never
stolen any company time?
Never.
You are a thief of joy.
Anybody else? Yeah?
Sometimes I download
pirated music onto
my work computer.
Who hasn't? Good.
Good. What else?
No, I'd like to hear
more about that.
I once reported Oscar to
the INS. Turns out he's clean,
but I'm glad I did it.
Well, let's keep
this party moving on.
I'll go.
Have you guys ever met
Bruce Myers, the Scranton
rep for Hammermill?
Bruce.
Well, for the past six years
I have been sleeping with him
in exchange for discounts
on our supplies and Outback
Steakhouse gift certificates.
Jackpot.
(LAUGHS)
(CLEARS THROAT)
Meredith, that is serious.
I mean, not only is that
a conflict of interest,
but there's also
an exchange of goods.
Exchange of steak.
Have you ever had
sirloin steak, honey?
That's crazy.
That's crazy talk.
Meredith, "the Merenator,"
sleeping with suppliers.
(LAUGHS)
Wow!
What time we got?
You know what?
That's a good place
to end it.
Right there.
This, I think, was
a great ethics seminar.
She has given us
a lot of wonderful
things to think about.
Right. What is wrong?
Who's to say, really,
in the end?
I mean, because it is
unknowable. But let's
give her a round of applause.
Holly, everybody! Holly!
Get back to work.
Great job.
I am truly impressed.
That... You really
pulled that one out.
Classic. Classic meeting.
We should celebrate.
Michael, there's
some serious issues
with Meredith.
I mean, all of you
have done things
I wouldn't have done myself,
but Meredith's actions
are really over the line.
Yeah. What are you
going to do?
So regarding this supplier,
approximately how many
liaisons have there been?
Liaisons? You mean
meet-ups? I don't know.
Once a month for six years.
Something like that.
Meredith, why don't you
tell Holly it's not
what she thinks,
nothing unethical happened
and that you just like
to sleep around?
Am I in trouble here
or something?
No. No. This is just
a stupid formality.
No, it's not a formality.
Now, were these
"meet-ups" just personal,
unrelated to business?
No. I wouldn't have
done it if it wasrt
for the discount paper.
There's not
a lot of fruit
in those looms.
(EXCLAIMS) For the love
of God, we're trying to
help you, you stupid bag.
What I don't understand is,
why the steak coupons?
I mean, if you were
already getting
the discounted paper...
Well, it's funny,
maybe it's a girl thing,
but after we did it,
when he would give me
those coupons, I just
felt good about myself.
Hey, what's going on here?
I thought I had immunity.
Well, unfortunately,
immunity or something
being off the record
does not really exist
in the workplace.
I mean, I've never heard
of anyone who kept their job
after something like this.
Well, I'm not quitting.
(STOP WATCH BEEPS)
(EXHALING)
Yawn, four seconds.
What are you doing?
You had said that you don't
do anything personal
during work time,
so I'm just making sure.
Wait a minute. So you're
going to time me every time
I yawn? That's absurd.
Really?
Hey, look, monkey knows
how to use a stop watch,
everybody.
He's...
(STOP WATCH BEEPS)
Personal conversation.
17 seconds.
(STOP WATCH BEEPS)
There is no way
that that was...
(STOP WATCH BEEPS)
One second.
Well, well, Holly-lujah!
It's a miracle
you're at your desk.
It's Mike-raculous.
(LAUGHS) Reaching.
You'll get there.
Anyway, I was giving it
some thought, and there's
no reason that two attractive,
good looking,
intelligent, funny,
attractive people can't,
you know, just sit down
and work this whole
Meredith thing out.
Sounds good.
Good.
Would you care to
bang it out over lunch?
I already bought this.
No, no, no.
Your food is no good
here, my lady.
Sorry.
You know what?
Let's go out.
Dunder Mifflirs treat.
Actually,
you're not a client,
so we'll just split it?
Ethical.
So, I've gone over
corporate policy.
What do you think?
What do you think
of this place?
It's very nice.
Isn't it?
Yeah. It's kind of
business romantic.
So you're from Des Moines.
Mmm.
That sounds so warm.
In summer.
Here, too.
You know what
my favorite season is?
Maybe we should talk
about Meredith first.
Yes. Get the boring stuff
out of the way.
Autumn was what I was
going to say. When the
leaves change, it's just...
I think it's the most
contemplative of seasons.
Okay, so I've gone over this
and I've thought about it
and I just don't think
there's any way I can write
a report that doesn't end
with her being terminated.
Terminate her. Terminator.
(MIMICS ARNOLD SCHWARZENEGGER)
"I'm from the future."
Yeah.
Hey, Andy.
Yo.
By any chance, did you
see Battlestar Galactica
last night?
No, I did not.
Was that any good?
Actually not.
It was really so-so.
Okay.
I mean, I like
all the crazy monsters
and stuff, you know,
like Klingons and Wookiees
and all that, but...
Sorry, was there something
you wanted to add, Dwight?
Is that anything
like the original
Battlestar Galactica?
You know what's weird?
It's practically
a shot-for-shot remake.
Really?
That's cool.
The story's kind of bland.
It's about this guy named
Dumbledore Calrissian...
Okay.
...who needs to return
the ring back to Mordor.
(HUFFING)
Really.
That doesn't sound right.
I just don't want my employees
thinking that their jobs
depend on performance.
I mean, what sort of place
is that to call home?
And Meredith needs
this job. This is
her main source of money.
Well, that's
very sweet, but we have
to follow the protocol.
Those are the rules.
Okay, new idea.
We don't report it at all.
We just punish her.
We punish her?
Tell her,
"Can't have sex
for six months."
I don't think
we could enforce that.
I don't know.
I saw this thing.
Like a belt with a key.
A chastity belt.
No, it's more of an underwear
garment that has little
spikes, like, made of...
Like sometimes they're
made of metal. You know
what I'm talking about?
You unlock
a little door that...
Down where you...
Where you put...
Where you put the...
He has not stopped
working for a second.
At 12:45, he sneezed
while keeping his eyes open,
which I always thought
was impossible.
At 1:32, he peed.
And I know that because
he did it in an open
soda bottle under the desk
while filling out
expense reports.
And on the flip side,
I've been so busy
watching him that
I haven't even started work.
It's exhausting,
being this vigilant.
I'll probably have
to go home early today.
I am just saying that
I don't think that you
understand what I am saying.
No, you are saying
that we should sweep
it under the carpet,
accept the discount
on supplies, not fire Meredith
and pretend like the whole
thing never happened.
Yes.
What am I saying?
Well...
(LAUGHS) Busted. I don't...
I'm saying that
her behavior is unethical,
and a little icky.
And I don't think I want
to work in an environment
where that sort
of conduct is tolerated.
Well, you have
to tolerate a lot when
you're part of a family.
It's not a family.
It's a workplace.
I will be honest with you.
That car ride did not go well.
And that was not my fault.
The only reason
I am standing
out here right now
is because
I don't want to take
the elevator with her.
And I am holding
on to her leftovers.
(STOP WATCH BEEPS)
Nineteen minutes
and 48 seconds.
What were we doing
for 19 minutes
and 48 seconds?
None of your business.
So I guess I can assume
that was personal.
Fine.
So maybe you're not
completely ethical after all.
Yes. Maybe I'm not.
It's been a little tense.
People are suspicious of me
and my best friend in the
office won't even talk to me.
Turns out being
the morality police
does not make you popular.
I should know,
because in middle school
I was the hall monitor
and the kids used to stuff
egg salad in my locker.
Yeah, I was just hoping
middle school was over.
Kendall from corporate HR
is on line one and
Holly's on her way in, too.
What's the only thing
worse than one HR rep?
Two HR reps.
You get me.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Can I sit?
I don't know, can you?
Kendall, my main man.
KENDALL: (ON PHONE)
Listen, Holly, Michael,
I just got the report
that your branch submitted.
And there's a lot of
stuff about a relationship
Meredith's having with a...
Yes, that came out during
the ethics seminar...
And let the record show
that it was during the
immunity part of the seminar.
Well, I'm not sure
these circumstances
warrant any action.
I think
it's pretty clear
it was unethical.
Well, from what I can gather,
it seems like a gray area.
Look, to be honest,
the company's getting
a discount at a tough time
in our balance sheet and
I don't know that the right
thing to do for the company
is to turn our
noses up at that.
Kendall, I understand
that the discount is
good for the company,
but I'm just not happy about
the way we're getting it.
(SIGHS) You see, I thought
I was clear with you, Holly.
Your task was
to get signatures
from the employees
showing that they
completed the training.
No, I understand.
Because every other branch
has managed to get this to us,
so if it's not something
you can handle, then
that's a different discussion.
No. No, I can do it.
Good.
(DIAL TONE BEEPS)
How do you tell somebody
that you care about deeply,
"I told you so"?
Gently, with a rose?
In a funny way?
Like it's a hilarious joke?
Or do you just let it go?
Because saying it would
just make things worse.
Probably the funny way.
Can I have
everyone's attention?
Excuse me.
May I have everyone's
attention, please?
We need to finish
the ethics seminar.
No way, lady.
It's a trap.
Everyone, please,
I just need
your signatures
to show corporate
that I gave you
the training.
Don't sign anything.
Okay, everybody,
listen up,
if you're not in
that conference room
in two minutes,
I am going to kill you.
It's a quarter to 5:00
and I have started
to gather my things.
Get in there right now
or I'm going to lose it!
(WHISPERING)
Am I getting fired?
Now is really not
the time, Meredith.
In this next section
we examine the difference
between sick days
and personal days.
Sick days are only
to be used when
an illness precludes you
from doing your job
or can spread
to your co-workers.
Personal days,
on the other hand,
are much more flexible.
Thank you, Meredith,
this was delicious.
Hey, where's the steak sauce?
I think we're out.
I got some
in my minivan somewhere.
Wait a second,
how does this steak
factor in again?
I think she got it as a tip,
but I don't know why
she didn't just take cash.
I don't care what
she's doing, I hope
she just keeps doing it.
(CHUCKLING)
Amen. Just keep
the ribs coming.