I had no idea,
when I got into that car
to go to New York,
that I was going
to be quitting.
I got on the ramp,
and I was, like,
"Two hours.
"Two hours to go.
Feeling good.
Crank some tunes.
"Should've peed
before I left."
Michael,
get to the good part.
Okay, so,
get up to the building.
Revolving door, broken.
(KEVIN EXCLAIMS)
So I have to take
the normal door.
Oh, my God.
At least he's in the building.
No! No.
I was so nervous,
it was the wrong building.
I had walked into
the wrong building.
He finally has a story
we really wanna hear.
And he knows it.
Okay, focus, focus.
You're in the right building,
you're with the right people,
what happened?
I looked at Wallace
and I said,
"I quit."
And as I turned to leave,
I looked back,
and I said,
"You have no idea
how high I can fly."
You didn't tell him
how sick of him you were?
Why would I do that?
Well, wouldn't it
feel good to tell him
that he's incompetent or...
That he's wasted
15 years
of your life?
Maybe spit in his face?
You guys have
thought about this
a lot more than I have.
I just winged it.
I love a good
quitting story.
It makes me feel
like I have control
over my own life.
Gives me hope.
Maybe I'll have
one of my own someday.
But I dream.
So...
(LAUGHING)
About a week ago,
Michael gave his
two-weeks' notice.
And surprisingly,
there is a very
big difference
between Michael trying
and Michael not trying.
Michael, is that Scotch?
Scotch and Splenda.
Tastes like Splenda,
gets drunk like Scotch.
(SLURPING)
(GLASS CLINKING)
Clinky.
Clinky-clink.
Come on.
Come on. Come on.
What am I gonna do?
I'll tell you
what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna do
a little bit of this
and a little bit of that.
I'm gonna stay up all day.
I'm gonna
sleep up all night.
I'm gonna give it a...
Ho! Hey Ho!
And I'm gonna
stop worrying
about calories.
Maybe you should
go into your office,
close the door
and make some
calls about jobs.
I have a job.
For four more days.
Do you have any
leads on a job?
Pam, what you don't
understand, at my level,
you don't just look in
the want ads for a job.
You're headhunted.
Have you called
any headhunters?
Any good headhunter knows
that I'm available.
Any really good headhunter
will storm your village
at sunset
with overwhelming force
and cut off your head
with a ceremonial knife.
Right, 'cause that's
what we're talking about.
I need you to go over
these client lists
and indicate any
wrong or false data.
Your
"I need you to"
is my command.
Okay.
Hey, Michael.
Hey.
Can I talk to you
for a minute?
You can talk to me
for as long
as you want,
because I have
all the time
in the world.
Oh, God.
Phyllis.
I just wanted to
tell you that...
(EXCLAIMING)
What's that?
Oh! Hey!
What is this about?
You know,
'cause you're leaving
and everything.
It's a farewell...
Right.
So I hope I get
to work with you
someday again.
Me, too. Me, too.
Is this wine?
Busted. Yes.
I already have wine.
Hello.
Hi.
Isaac Sylvie here
for the interview.
Yes, please have a seat.
It'll be a few minutes.
Thank you.
Are you interviewing, too?
Um. Hmm?
Interviewing?
For?
Regional manager.
Yes, I am.
For regional manager,
I've decided to go
with an outside hire.
For obvious reasons.
Where you from?
Philly.
That's a drive.
Yeah, well, this is
one of the few places
that's hiring.
It's brutal out there.
(SIGHING)
Pam?
When will the new
copier be ready?
I'm working on it, Kev.
You said it would
be ready by today.
And it is today.
It'll be ready soon.
Soon could mean anything.
Soon could be three weeks.
Is that what
soon means to you?
Sometimes.
Then come back soon.
During the course of business
a copier goes through
something called
normal wear and tear.
I think it's 75 cents.
That's a lot.
Bandit, no! No, no, no!
Yesterday,
they delivered the new one.
But they didn't set it up.
So my day just got
a little more interesting.
(MONSTERS RO ARING)
It's monster. Com. Singular.
Thank you.
You work in
paper long enough,
you get to know the players.
MAN: (WHIMPERING) Hi,
you've reached Prince Paper.
We are sad to inform you
that after 40 years
of serving the community,
we are no longer in business.
Thank you for your support
and may God bless you.
GIRL: Bye!
What am I gonna do?
(CHUCKLES HELPLESSLY)
(CLATTERING)
(MICHAEL CALLING)
Yep? Do you want me
to come into your office?
Okay.
All right.
Close your eyes.
I'd prefer not to.
Just close your eyes.
(CHUCKLING)
I'm going to start
my own paper company.
(MICHAEL CHUCKLING)
You're starting
your own paper company.
Yeah!
Why?
Can you believe...
'Cause I know paper.
I know everything
there is to know about paper.
Do you that
the industry's
in decline?
Yeah. Oh, God,
I practically
invented decline.
Right.
I know paper,
I know how to manage.
I have a name.
Close your eyes.
No, I did that before.
It added nothing.
Close them.
Okay.
All right.
Michael Scott Paper Company.
You want in?
Do you want to be
a part of this?
I am not going to do this.
Obviously.
And you are not
going to, either.
Agreed. Except...
Here's the thing.
What I wish for you
is that you land
a job at a company
that A, exists,
and B, has a salary,
because they're set up
to do that kind of thing.
What's up, Chuck?
Jim, what are you doing?
Nothing. Just talking.
Okay. Michael handed in
his two-week notice.
Did you also hand
in your two-week...
I didn't.
CHARLES: No? Okay.
(CHARLES SIGHING)
After you.
No, I'm staying.
Okay.
Do you want me to translate
the German instructions
for you?
No, I'm sure
they're pretty much the same
as the English instructions.
(SCOFFS)
Typical American arrogance
that got us involved
in a war we never
should have been in.
That's a really...
World War II.
Well, fine, did
the German instructions say
what this is supposed to do?
(SPEAKS IN GERMAN)
Let me see here.
That is either
an incense dispenser
or a ceremonial
sarcophagus.
Hmm.
My German is preindustrial
and mostly religious.
Pam, listen.
This order form,
instead of saying
Dunder Mifflin at the top,
is there any way
I could get it to
say something else?
Like Michael Scott
Paper Company?
You...
Somebody's been
talking in bed.
Pillow talk.
Yeah. Listen, Michael.
Have you really
thought this through?
'Cause it's
a pretty big risk.
This is a dream
that I have had since lunch
and I am not
giving up on it now.
Yeah. You could give
it up, though, right?
And almost no one would know.
Before you got here,
I'm the one who landed
all of these clients.
Half of them. At least.
I can do it again.
I know the market.
I know the price points.
I'm on it. Don't worry.
So, how do I do that?
Well,
you can scan it,
and then you can
upload the image,
copy a new image...
Could I take a piece of paper
and just tape it
with transparent tape?
Yeah. Good.
Thank you very much.
So that is why
I have to leave at 5:00
on Tuesdays.
It's to pick up
my little sisters
from school.
We're really tight.
We're like the Kardashians.
You know,
you can run this stuff
by Toby.
Yeah, I don't like talking...
Come in.
I'm sorry.
I didn't realize
you were with anyone.
But I just wanted to
bring you the brochure
on that accounting seminar
that I was telling
you about earlier.
Okay, we're in the middle
of something, Angela, so...
Actually, you know,
it was so much fun last year.
There was a sundae bar.
I mean,
I didn't have any.
You know,
to stay trim.
Did Michael just let
anybody in his office?
Yes. He loved to
facilitate communication.
He loved it.
He invited us in
all the time.
He was, like, "Come in."
Yeah.
I am aware of the effect
I have on women.
So you should be
heading back
to your desk.
Okay. Bye, Charles.
Well, you'll let me know.
Goodbye.
She's such
a special person.
She's turning 50 this year.
I'm starting
my own paper company.
No way!
Yeah.
In this climate?
In all climates.
It's going to be worldwide.
And I'm looking for
some talented salesmen
to join me.
That's where you come in.
(MUMBLING)
(IN BRITISH ACCENT) Well,
it's a very intriguing
concept, isn't it?
(SMACKING LIPS)
Michael is starting
his own paper company.
What do you think
about that?
Your own paper company?
Can you believe it?
Well, we'll see.
We'll see.
Wow.
It's just a...
It's a nugget of
an idea right now.
Right.
Potential.
Lots of potential. Yes.
What a courageous venture.
It's very courageous
and very exciting.
Location is hard for me
with the farm...
That's what
I was thinking.
...and the
responsibilities, so...
That's what I was thinking.
With the farm.
You getting to wherever...
It's so crucial...
...l'm gonna put my thing.
Okay.
So, think about it.
Yeah.
Let's put a pin in it for now.
You know, I would love
to put a pin in that.
Everyone, can I have
your attention?
This is the moment
you've all been
waiting for.
Right?
(IMITATING DRUM ROLL)
Little Miss Thing
wants attention.
Thanks, Meredith.
(EXHALES)
(BEEPS)
(WHIRRING)
(BEEPING)
Oh!
So...
G-44.
It's not ready, Kevin!
I am at a crucial point
where I have sunk
four hours
into that copier.
And I am not gonna
let it beat me like that
wireless router did.
You put a note in my food?
I made it sterile.
Just saying sterile
doesn't make it so.
I am offering you
the opportunity
of a lifetime, Oscar,
to come work for me.
Do you have
a business plan?
A funding request,
market research,
financials...
No, no, no!
You need those things...
Most new businesses,
they don't make a profit
till at least two years.
And then your margins
will be razor-thin.
Best-case scenario,
you don't
cut yourself a salary
for at least five years.
Can you go five years
without a salary,
Michael?
Okay.
Five years?
You already have the job.
You don't have
to convince me.
It's just not prudent,
Michael.
MICHAEL: (WHISPERING)
Stanley.
STANLEY:
Can't you see
I'm urinating?
MICHAEL: Listen.
Listen, Stanley, you don't
need to answer me now.
STANLEY: No.
Just... I want you
to think about it.
I am starting
my own company.
STANLEY: No.
Okay, you're not
letting me finish.
And you just lost out
on a million dollars.
STANLEY: No, I didn't.
You know what?
I had a great time at prom.
And no one said yes
to that, either.
How's it working?
Let's see.
Yeah, it's fine.
Good.
I did it.
I learned everything
about this machine.
I know all the buttons.
Even the inside ones.
I know all
the error messages.
I could do a bound book
in plastic
with offset colors,
which feels...
CHARLES: Hey, Hank.
You ready?
Yeah.
Okay.
Michael?
I can't pretend
I haven't seen that.
So I'm gonna ask you
to stand up, walk out
and you can't
take anything.
Okay.
I have immunity.
It's my two weeks.
Not if you're starting
a competing paper
company, Michael.
Hank.
Okay, Michael.
Hank?
You really think Hank is
going to be loyal to you?
Hank, please escort Charles
from the building.
(SNICKERING)
Come on, man, let's go.
I always thought
Michael got a bad rap.
He's a good guy.
And he's super funny.
Yeah,
maybe I should tell him
before he goes.
He's all the way over there.
(SIGHING)
Well, here we are.
I would just like to...
No. No, no, no.
You're done, Michael.
All right then,
everybody,
I'm out of here!
(INAUDIBLE)
What is he doing?
It looks like
he's saying something.
I think he's singing.
I can't believe this
is really happening.
And I feel free!
And just like that,
as mysteriously
as he arrived,
he was gone.
ANDY: The whole office
feels darker.
You know?
It's just a sad, dark day.
Andy, he's gone.
I know.
You don't have to
kiss his ass anymore.
Michael's like
a movie on a plane.
You know, it's not great,
but it's something to watch.
And then when it's over,
you're, like,
how much time is left
on this flight?
You know. Now what?
(RUSTLING)
Michael?
(SHUSHING)
(WHISPERING)
Don't look down.
Look straight up.
Come on. Please.
These are for employees only.
Angela, Kevin,
help me out.
I just need a few things,
and then I'll be gone.
Michael, why is it that
you asked everyone
except me, Angela,
Creed and Meredith?
I was going to.
I wanted to.
But I had to
start somewhere.
And you didn't want
to start with us?
No.
Of course not.
But now I want everybody.
Jim.
Buddy.
Buddy. Jimbo.
Did you have time to
think about my offer?
I did have a chance
to think about it,
but then I thought
about something else.
So, which way
are you leaning?
Well, it is tempting,
but I am 100%
leaning towards passing.
That's...
Did anyone see
the client list
that Michael was supposed
to be working on?
DWIGHT: No.
Okay, let me know
if you find it.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Okay.
(PANTING) Okay,
we don't have much time.
Just act normal.
Don't look at me.
People, stop.
Don't look down.
He's gonna see me.
Not all the way up.
Keep them at
a normal height.
Okay?
This is not Michael Scott
talking right now.
This is your future. Hello.
I am your future.
You are older and
you are very happy now,
because you went with
Michael Scott, right?
So, everybody,
come on down.
And let's just crawl
out of here together,
all right?
Come on!
Are you doing
your best here?
Are you being the best
that you can be?
All right, everybody
who's gonna go with me,
I want you
to stomp your foot.
Okay.
All right. Come on.
Come on.
You're coming with me.
Come on, Phyllis.
Here we go.
(DOOR OPENING)
Michael, get up.
Oh, God, okay.
All right, all right.
Time to go.
Jim, let's go.
Come on.
Come on!
Michael!
What are you doing?
I think maybe Hank
should be here.
Hank? You know,
I don't need Hank.
You're gonna mess with me?
Is that what you're gonna do?
I'll tell you something,
Charles.
I don't even care,
because I've got
nothing to lose.
Okay.
Oh, my God. No, God! No!
No. All right.
It's not won'th it.
Oh, no.
What?
I'm going with him.
What? Pam.
PAM: I'm going!
Pam, you can't be serious.
Michael, wait!
I'm coming with you.
You are?
Yeah.
(LAUGHING)
Okay. It's gonna be great.
Great. Except I don't want to
be a receptionist anymore.
Right.
Executive assistant.
Salesman.
MICHAEL: All right. Okay.
Deal.
Okay, well, Jim?
Still no.
Okay.
Yeah.
Well, let's go.
All my stuff is
still upstairs.
Are people watching?
Probably.
Michael, it's not how
you leave an office.
It's how you...
Jim, Jim, Jim.
We're having
a company meeting here.
I will bring all
your stuff home.
Okay.
All right.
I'll see you later.
Bye.
See you later.
So, we had
a personnel change today.
Shouldrt affect
our day-to-day,
but until we get
a new receptionist,
I want Kevin on the phones.
Phones?
CHARLES: Also, there's been
way too much wasting time.
So, Stanley?
Yes?
Yeah, I want you
on top of that.
Okay, I want you to be
my productivity czar.
Okay? Good.
Okay, that's it on my list.
So, no excuses, guys.
Let's get going, okay?