- Could you sign my expense report?
- No way, no how.
Expense reports are a day-to-day item.
That is Jim's now.
I am exclusively big picture, epic.
Sign this.
Where's the "please"?
We're not animals.
Sign it.
Not without a "please."
Idiot.
- I have a complaint about Jim.
- That is not big picture.
I would like to file a huge,
enormous, massive complaint
about the tallest guy in our office.
Jim won't sign my expense report.
That is not... Okay...
- That is day-to-day.
- No, that his huge.
You're trying to trick me.
Get out, get out, get out...
- I'd like to lodge a complaint.
- I'm sorry to hear about that.
- Who is this about?
- You!
Just want to let you know
I take complaints very seriously.
- When did this happen?
- One minute ago.
- And how do you feel?
- Angry.
- All right. Did he hit you?
- No.
- Did you cry?
- Did you feel like crying?
- No.
I'm gonna write, "held back tears."
Wait, stop writing that.
That is not true.
If you stop crying,
I'll stop writing it.
I deserved that promotion, not Jim.
Makes me want to put him
in a triangle choke hold
and force him down to the ground
and just keep pressing and pressing.
And then flip him over
and then put him in a hammer lock.
And he's gasping, he's panting.
Every last breath.
And the crowd is going crazy.
I emerge victorious!
$18,000 and a chance at the title.
Jim wants you to keep it down.
Everyone, now would be
a good time to freshen up,
because I'd like everyone to meet
in the conference room in five minutes.
I suggest that you bring a snack,
we may be in there for a while.
Can I talk to you in my office?
Sure, but could I first
talk to you in my office?
Can I also be a boss?
It doesn't take a genius to know
that any organization thrives
when it has two leaders.
Go ahead, name a country
that doesn't have two presidents.
A boat that sets sail
without two captains.
Where would catholicism be
without the popes?
I have noticed that...
Welcome.
I've noticed we've been having
a lot of conference room meetings.
And I'm wondering
if perhaps those are a bit...
Disruptive.
I don't think they are.
I think
the meetings are very important.
Maybe we should talk specifics.
Let's do.
Yesterday, we had a meeting
about planets.
Well, to be fair, Jim...
James...
Jimothy...
To be fair, Jimothy, the...
That sounds weird.
Are you okay with being called Jim?
I am.
Jim, to be fair,
the conversation wasn't about planets.
At first, we were talking about
introducing a line of toilet paper.
And what part of the human body
does one use toilet paper upon?
So you draw a line from there
to the other planets,
and I think by the end, we all learned
a little bit about how small we are.
- Yes, I agree...
- Because it's a big universe,
and we're all just little,
tiny specks of dust.
I just think that maybe
they're eating large amounts of the day.
You know what eats
a large amount of the day are naps.
You go to sleep, it's light out,
you wake up, it's dark.
That's the whole day.
Where did that day go?
I have no idea.
You mean on a weekend.
I think our goal should be
we don't have meetings
unless they're absolutely essential.
- No more meetings this week.
- Really?
- You just agree to that?
- I can be very surprising.
What's going on?
I need to fit into my wedding dress.
However, I'm also pregnant.
It's a myth that women have to gain
more than nine pounds in a pregnancy?
Look at these actresses.
Some of them lose weight.
Did you guys register
for wedding gifts?
We did,
but mostly because people expect us to.
We're also accepting other gifts...
not on the registry...
However much.
It's awkward asking people for money,
but we could really use it.
Why doesn't Crate & Barrel
let you register
for a toaster full of cash?
Perfect. I hate registries.
Good.
My cousin makes the most amazing,
romantic birdhouse mailboxes.
I know I shouldn't tell you,
but you'll still be surprised.
You're not registered
for a birdhouse?
No, we're not.
Good.
Okay,
I thought I saw people missing.
Just focus-grouping
a product expansion idea to these folks.
- Got one of each.
- Really?
Stanley, what was the last thing
Michael said before I came?
You don't need to answer that.
"If you don't smell this,
you're fired."
I thought we agreed to not take up
people's time with meetings like these.
What do you mean by "these people"?
This is a conference room meeting.
Everybody,
I think that Jim has gone insane,
because he thinks
that my office is a conference room.
That's not what I meant.
No offense,
but when push comes to shove,
what I want is more important
than what you want.
- I disagree.
- What do you guys think?
Can I go back to my desk now?
Great. Guys, can I just have
a moment with Michael?
You don't need to go anywhere.
Anything that Jim has to say to me,
he can say
in front of these types of people.
That is not what I said,
and, also, I am co-manager,
meaning you are not the only manager.
I am also a co-manager.
- That's not what Wallace told.
- That's exactly what he told.
That is not the way I heard it.
I love rivalries...
Michael or Jim,
Paris or Nicole, Heidi or L.C.
It's so much fun.
But I guess
if I'm really thinking about it
and answering
your question honestly,
I'd have to go with L.C.
Heidi's a bad friend,
and her skin is terrible.
It is one thing,
me giving you the co-manager title.
It is another thing,
you bossing me around.
I'm not. I'm trying to do my job,
which is sharing your job,
so maybe we should just call David.
No, we will not call David Wallace.
I will call David Wallace.
David Wallace
is on line two for you guys.
Or Davidwill call us on line two.
Why don't we just...
Hey, David.
You got Jim here.
This is Michael, senior co-manager.
Hey, guys,
I'm calling, because, unfortunately,
we will not be able
to give out cost of living raises
this year,
and I know people expect it.
However, there just is only
a small amount of money for each branch,
so we're leaving it up to the managers
to decide how to distribute it.
Got it, Dave.
Sounds like
your classic big-picture decision.
Which will clearly affect
the day-to-day well-being of employees.
- It's probably a little of both.
- Which is it more of?
Excuse me?
I know that I'm very new at this,
but I have a very good perspective.
Wait, I'm sorry.
Michael, are you...
Are you texting me?
I thought maybe
we could talk after this is over.
Look, I need you both
to take care of this.
This is not going to be
a problem, is it?
- Nope, not at all.
- No, it will not be.
I am on top of it.
- Thanks a lot.
- Talk to you later.
You didn't let me say good-bye.
All right,
I am looking forward to this.
- You don't have to lie.
- I hate that we have to do this.
I think
we work much better separately.
When I am irritated and I look at you,
I don't see you anymore.
All I can see
is how big and gross
the pores on your nose are.
All right.
Let's get started.
Hey, why haven't we ever...
We have.
There's no easy way to do this.
I say...
we add 1.5% to their paychecks
and don't say anything about it.
Like break in
in the middle of the night
- and change the numbers on payroll?
- We can do it during the day.
It doesn't have to be that dramatic.
You know what would help is
a pros and cons list
for our options.
Don't take this the wrong way.
Are you gonna take this the wrong way?
- It's hard to tell so far.
- You use your brain too much.
Are you advocating
that I use it less?
Sometimes the smartest people
don't think at all.
- You just came up with that.
- As I was saying it.
Okay, so for the 1.5% increase, pro:
everyone gets a little bit.
Con: you look like a nerd.
Con: no one gets
as much as they did last year.
Pro: you get to share your list
with the other nerds.
Pro: no favoritism.
Con: you unzip your pants,
and you find
that there's a calculator down there.
I've been studying Michael
for years,
and I've condensed
what I've learned into this chart.
How Michael spends his time.
As you can see, we have
procrastinating and distracting others,
and this tiny sliver here
is critical thinking.
I made it bigger,
so that you could see it.
I heard that you were registered,
but I didn't hear where.
I don't think
we registered anywhere.
We just want cash.
Like money?
You want my money?
Will you take a check?
Cool.
In the memo line, I'm gonna write,
"To love's eternal glory. "
Wait till Monday.
Is this what I've become?
Materialistic?
Shallow?
I feel horrible.
Look!
"Mrs. Pam Halpert!"
That's the first time
I've seen it in writing.
You know, the more I think about it,
the more I think,
we should give it to the salesmen.
- That will not go over well.
- I know. I just think it seems smart
to keep the salesmen happy.
Of course I know
that this might come off as biased,
so you know what?
Let us...
Are you gonna make
another pro and con list?
- I'm gonna kill myself.
- I'm not gonna stop thinking.
I could not do that, Jim.
I can see it
in your crusty little eyes
that you are going to make
everything perfect.
If I can just think this through,
if I could just think it
exactly right,
I can make this perfect.
Then I can go down every avenue,
every avenue off of that avenue,
and then another avenue.
- And then another...
- You've a lot of strengths.
I do? Tell me what they are.
I think that you are able
to take constructive criticism
very well.
That...
I am not known for that.
There is a reason why I'm here.
You went over my head to Wallace.
It's because you also have
a lot of weaknesses.
Why don't you tell me what those are?
Why don't you enliven me?
You're not good
at making tough decisions.
At thinking out the options,
and then stating that decision
very clearly,
especially when
it's an unpopular decision.
Here's a tough decision for you.
You suck. You suck.
Is that clear enough for you?
Maybe,
I'm here for a reason,
because I might have
some good ideas, too.
I've been sitting out there,
learning a lot,
and maybe I can just bring something
different to the table.
OK, Skippy, here we go.
Why don't you run yourself
out there and tell them?
You call it.
This had better be terrible.
Could I have everyone's attention?
I have some tough news,
so I'm gonna give it
to you straight.
Truth is, we only have
so much money for raises this year,
so the simple fact is some people
will get raises and some people won't.
Now, what we've decided is,
we are gonna give those raises
to the sales staff.
Wait. Seriously?
You guys are smart,
so I'm just leveling with you.
- I'm trying to treat you like adults.
- Thank you, Jim, for...
thinking that we're smart people.
But I do not understand.
If we're such smart adults,
then why don't we get raises?
Excellent question, genius.
'Cause Jim wants to give the raises
to his friends
and the people he sleeps with.
Easy. That's not it at all.
Really what it is is about the money
the sales staff brings into the office.
- What's going on?
- Jim is only giving raises
to the salesmen.
- Why are you being such a jerk?
- Hold on, kelly.
Would it help you to know
that Jim thinks you're smart?
How is that gonna repair Ryan's car?
This is ridiculous!
How could he do this to us?
You know what?
You'd be getting the raise...
What about all these people?
How is it fair to them?
We work as hard as the sales people.
We deserve raises.
They don't get 'em
if we don't get 'em.
My kid needs shoes!
You want to tell him
he doesn't get shoes?
Her kid needs shoes, Jim!
What the hell?
I'm just gonna
rewind
and back off a bit.
That was good.
Okay, all right.
Well, we all know
it's hard to be a boss, right?
You know what?
Look around you.
These are your best friends.
These are the people
who will open their hearts to you.
They all have
heart-ons for you,
and that is a gift.
So in terms of gifts,
we should be giving
each other gifts.
Angela, yes,
lend Oscar a cup of sugar.
What are you talking about?
We just need to hear
your plan for our raise.
My plan...
A man... Panama.
- That's not how that goes.
- You're not saying anything.
At least, Jim was direct
when he was telling us
his dumbass plan.
What's happening?
Are we getting a raise, yes or no?
Let me get this clear.
Does everybody want a raise?
All right, everyone wants a raise.
What we're going to do
is go into here,
and we will not come out
until we do.
That gives us no information.
This isn't a game, you know?
It's our livelihood!
What about a raise based on merit?
Rank each person individually.
Piece of cake.
- Ryan, obviously the best.
- Well, obviously.
Too bad he's a temp, he doesn't count.
Let's get started.
Are you making a...
I'm numbering the paper.
- Just...
- I don't understand
how they can even consider
giving money to some people
and not the rest of us.
We're not gonna see the checks.
- We're in accounting.
- I am so pissed at this company.
And Jim.
Who said that?
I think it was Creed.
It's going really well, actually.
Each Boston Baked Bean
represents half a percent raise,
we each got 24 beans,
so the idea is you place the bean
on the picture of
who you think deserv...
Who's that?
- He's not a part of this.
- Just wanted to draw a picture of him.
- Your move.
- All right, who to pick?
- Who to pick?
- Here we go.
I...
will skip a turn.
You're gonna still have
to play that bean.
I need more time.
Wallace sent an e-mail about a meeting.
He wants you both to respond.
People are starting
to notice how terrible Jim is.
It's great.
Eventually,
they'll rise up and revolt.
My only hope is that
they do it sooner rather than later.
If the people here
were our founding fathers,
the Revolutionary War
would have been delayed ten years,
because Stanley Washington
was napping,
Phyllis Hancock
was still signing the declaration,
Kevin Jefferson
was distracted by a butterfly.
Come on in.
That's right.
Come in, feast your eyes.
They determine our worth
by putting beans upon our faces.
Things were not this bad
when just Michael was manager.
- What are you doing?
- What does a bean mean?
Why aren't there any beans
on this very old,
frizzy-haired picture of me?
What does a bean mean?
- I was trying to be unbiased.
- What does a bean mean?
- Please explain it to Kevin.
- Why can't you?
- My time is valuable as yours.
- Not according to the beans.
This is how you make
this important decision?
There's no way
that Stanley gets more beans than me.
That is ridiculous.
This is how it works.
It's not so much
that I might not get a raise.
It's just demeaning.
Thank you.
That is exactly...
By the way,
I would also like a raise.
I would, too.
Are we idiots?
What right
does Jim have to claim authority?
Is he as good a salesman as I?
Is he as
matronly as Phyllis?
There are moments
where we can affect change.
For a few seconds, every decade,
we exist,
and these are those seconds.
Let us storm his castle.
Come on... Tick.
Let's get him... Tock.
Let's get Jim!
Tick.
And drag Jim out of his office...
Tock.
Take his keys away from him.
Tick... That's a clock.
The time is getting very close.
It's now or never.
What say you?
I say no.
No, I mean,
what do you say to my plan?
What does a bean mean?
How you doing?
On a scale of one to ten,
I'd say I'm about a four.
What are you usually?
Six.
You?
Usually a ten,
but I'm feeling like a zero.
A performance-based raise
sounded like a good idea, right?
I know, I know.
We tried to find the fairest way.
Yes, we did.
What?
Nothing. I just...
I used to have to do
this part alone,
and it was the worst.
I've something
I would like to give you.
Michael's my only friend left
in the office.
Except Pam...
I think.
Is she still upset?
You cannot
just keep avoiding us like this!
You're welcome.
What's in here?
Just pretend we're not here.
You're looking for cash
for the wedding?
I mean,
if it's all the same for you.
Question for you.
Would you guys rather have $100 now
or $5,000 a year from now?
$100 now for sure.
'Cause you just give me $50
to cover the broker fee,
I put in 100 of my own money
as the gift...
The hundred.
I'll just take the hundred.
Instead of $5,000 a year from now?
How sure is this?
The guy has an algorithm
to determine the winner
of any given college basketball game.
Don't tell Jim.