Go! Gotcha you! Broken arm!
Boom! Boom boom! Broken nose!
Boom boom boom! Broken nose! Boom!
TOPTOPTHIS YEAR IN MARTIAL ARTS:
Once a year, Dwight holds a seminar updating us,
a newest dewelopment of Karate!
as we all know,the one thing
that thousand-year-old martial
arts do all the time is change.
How can i pose this to
you in a relatable way?
You are all members of the yakuza,
and you happen to be visiting
the lackawanna trolley museum,
and you are attacked by triads.
How can you hold them off
until your clan arrives?
You cannot go wrong with a throat punch.
Okay,so there's no defense
for that? Good to know.
No,there is a defense for that.
Let me demonstrate.
Someone attack me. Kevin,go!
No way. Last time,you
pulled my pants down,
and then you tried to
choke me with my shoelace.
False. I did choke you with
your shoelace. Now come at me!
Okay,with all due
respect to everyone here,
i think the most worthy
opponent of you is you.
That is correct,unless there
happen to be measles present.
So let's just say that dwight has
come at you with the throat punch.
Now,how would you,dwight,
defend against it?
Easy. Allow me to demonstrate.
I am attacking myself
with a throat punch.
Here it comes. Block.
Grasp wrist as such.
And what if he comes at
you with the other hand?
Because he does have two.
Good point. Second throat punch.
Absorb the blow.
Groin punch.
Hit,block,elbow to the gut!
Up to the nose! No,you're not!
Oh,my god,he's making
you look like such a fool.
He really is,but not for long.
God! Instep!
Boh! Not again!
You let go! You let go!
Oh,you're right! I can't hold on!
You two are so evenly matched,i don't know
how one of you's gonna get the upper hand.
The important thing to remember,jim,
we always have what is called
the element of surprise.
But i would say my favorite art form
is a tie between sculpting
and stand-up comedy.
I did stand-up comedy once.
- You did?
- Yeah,i killed.
- That sounds like it was hilarious.
- It was hilarious.
- Michael?
- Yes?
What is the meaning of this
email that everyone got?
You'll have to be more specific,dwight.
I get like eight emails a day.
This one. "from: david
wallace,to: all dunder mifflin.
" whoo-hoo.
Shout-out.
"hello,everyone,i'm sure you've
seen "the item in the journal.
"just want to stress
it's all conjecture.
"if there's any concrete
news,you will know a. S. A. P.
" erin,do we have the journal?
Your feelings journal? You told
me to put it in the time capsule.
- Did you?
- Michael,he means the wall street journal online.
Oh,the wall.
I found the article.
"on a day marked by panicked
corporate board meetings,
"one that is relatively
unsurprising "is dunder mifflin's.
It is rumored that they
will recommend de--"
and the article cuts off.
It's $1. 99 to finish the article.
I wonder what it was gonna say.
Are you serious?
I got it,i got it.
Tuna beat me to it.
"it is rumored that they will
recommend declaring bankruptcy"?
No,no. That doesn't make any sense.
Oh,lord,we're all gonna lose our jobs.
Not necessarily. Bankruptcy
could mean a lot of things.
Maybe they're just
restructuring to get out of debt.
Oh,that sounds awful.
Or it could mean the
end of dunder mifflin.
Oh,god! Well,that's
an interesting theory.
You know what? You can all
have jobs at schrute farms...
As human scarecrows.
It doesn't pay much
and you can't unionize.
I'm sorry,michael. David's in a meeting.
Ah,well,maybe you should spy on him.
Oh,my god! Wouldn't that be hilarious?
um,i'll just have him call you back.
Okay,okay. Good.
I'll catch you on the
flippity-flip. Bye!
He's busy. Call me back when he's free.
michael,are you okay?
Did you throw up in there?
No,just poopin'. You know how i be.
But it smells like throw-up in here.
Crazy world,lotta smells.
You guys,what if this
is our last day at work?
What if we never see
each other ever again?
I like erin. There,i said it.
I was kinda hoping she would ask me out,
but things have not panned
out on that front,so...
It is time for the nard-dog to
take matters into his own paws.
We have to do something,
because people are losin' it out there,
wondering what's gonna happen.
Okay,we need some sort of
distraction for everybody.
Is there anything new in youtube?
- Michael-- - doesn't
even need to be good.
Oh,god! I can't think.
I need more mullins.
listen,wallace said these
were just rumors,right?
So we have no reason to think that
the company's anything but fine.
So if we just go on with our work,
you and me,they'll follow along.
- Monkey see,monkey do.
- That's it.
Monkey pee all over you.
That... Rhymes.
So what have we on the docket today?
We have a...
A monthly staff meeting.
All right! Let's conference room it up!
Here's the deal,guys. There is
no new information as of yet,
so i suggest we all just keep working.
Sure,i'm a little nervous,but doing
our work will make us feel better.
I only slack off when things are good.
Customers have to use the
coupon code from the website.
and as of now,there is no differentiation
between the letter "o" and the zero,
but we are working on that.
Stay tuned for that.
He needs me. Seat-save infinity.
- Okay,great.
- Oh,god!
What?
Oh,my god.
- What?
- What is it?
Is there news?
There has been a murder!
- What? - A
mur-- -what?
There's been a murder... In savannah.
Games have the power to distract
people from stressful situations.
"battleship" got me
through my parents' divorce.
"operation" got me through my
vasectomy,i. E. My operation.
I don't think i would have been able to
endure my break-up with holly
had it not been for "toss across.
"belles,bourbon,and bullets,
a murder mystery dinner party game.
it is so much fun.
Everybody plays a character,we
go around the room,
we try to figure out who did it.
Hey,i'm wondering if this
is a,um,terrible idea.
This is my call,jim. Big
picture stuff. It's about murder.
I thought we agreed that we
wouldn't do things like this.
Tube city. You owe me one.
Co-managing is a give and take.
You have to pick your battles.
One of the battles that i picked
was to stop michael from
running plastic tubes
all over the office and
placing hamsters inside of them.
He was gonna call it tube city.
So,yes,i do owe him one.
august 5,1955.
it's a sad day down here in savannah.
Local magnate bill bourbon
was killed last night,
and all y'all have
congregated tonight for a meal
to celebrate bill as he
passes on to his great reward.
But you're not just here
to pay your respects.
You have to figure out which of y'all
is the no-account
scoundrel who killed him.
This is ridiculous.
There will be food. You
leave,you do not get food.
- What kind of food?
- Sandwich platters.
- I'm in.
- Baby carrots.
Okay,here are your character cards.
Take one,pass it down.
Here is your prop box.
Some of your characters will have props.
Now,on your character card,
it tells you who you are
and what your alibi is.
Everything else is up
to your imagination.
So if you talk slowly in real
life,your character could,
say,have been kicked
in the head by a horse.
Cool. I'll try it.
Okay. Use your imaginations.
Who did you get?
"naughty nellie nutmeg,
a vivacious young socialite
with a penchant for scandal.
- ooh! Saucy.
- How about you?
"nathaniel nutmeg,the
local bartender and...
Nellie's brother.
michael,i don't like
this game. It's scary.
It's not scary.
I don't like my character.
Who are you?
"voodoo mama juju,the witch
doctor of the savannah swamps.
" i'm not comfortable with this.
Well,how do you think i feel?
I mean,i have to play caleb
crawdad,handsome playboy.
Every night,a different woman,
being oogled,having to
hug and kiss and spoon.
Oh! I make them feel beautiful.
Well,well,well!
What is this contraption,i do declare?
It's my blackberry,michael. I'm
trying to get updates on the company.
Who's michael? I'm caleb
crawdad,i do declare.
You don't have to keep
saying,"i do declare.
" anytime you say something
it means you're declaring.
That is the way southern people talk.
And what designing woman
are you basing that on?
Delta burke,i do declare.
Now,shall we get to the mystery?
I'll go.
"my name is deborah
utante,deb for short.
that's clever. Debutante.
"bill bourbon was my uncle.
"i would have never hurt him any
more than i'd hurt a june bug.
nice accent. You sound
like forrest gump.
- I do not.
- Well,you do,actually.
You got this kind of like
florida panhandle thing goin',
whereas what you really want
is more of a savannah accent,
which is more like molasses,just
sort of spillin' out of your mouth.
Oh,now do the swedish chef.
Uh,i'm not familiar.
What province is he from?
He lives on sesame street,dumbass.
You know,i think i'm supposed to say
something to pam-- i mean,deb. Okay.
Um... "i overheard you askin' the
butler where the pistol was kept.
wait a minute! Wait a minute!
I'm the butler. You were listening
in on that? Oh,you rich people.
You think you can do whatever
you want to the servant class!
No,no,no. Don't turn this
into a political thing.
I will poison your food.
I reckon i got somethin' to say
to miss beatrix bourbon
if'n she don't mind.
Ooh,doggy! We got a party now!
I do believe that the game is a big hit.
People are really divin'
into their characters.
Y'all...
i made a mistake.
Sorry i'm late,boss. What's goin' on?
Sir,there has been a
murder,and you are a suspect.
Okay. Hang on just a second.
Let me settle in,and i'll be right back.
Very good! Very good!
Now,no one was there in the wine cellar.
- hey,there,young lady.
- Hello.
I would be remiss if i did
not ask the pretty young lady
out on a date for this weekend.
Sounds like a plan,sugar.
All right!
A plan it is.
voodoo mama juju,explain your
dalliance with the dark arts.
It's not my fault. I was
exposed to harry potter.
I know you did it!
I know she didn't do it.
It's never the person you most suspect.
It's also never the
person you least suspect,
since anyone with half a brain
would suspect them the most.
Therefore,i know the
killer to be phyllis,
a.K.A.Beatrix bourbon,
the person i most medium suspect.
Do you want to go out on a date with me?
We can make out by the horses.
Well,you know old nellie is
always up for a romp in the hay.
How 'bout a threesome?
Yeah. My boudoir's always open.
Nice.
I'm a little worried i might have
asked out naughty nellie and not erin.
Which would be a whole
lot less appealing,
because naughty nellie
says yes to everyone,
and she might be a murderer.
Follow before...
i just got an email from corporate,
specifically for accounting to
stop all payments to our vendors.
What does that mean?
Well,maybe nothing,but
it could be a prob--
What's this strange yankee accent
comin' out of your mouth,son?
This here is savannah.
Phyllis,uh...
Uh... This...
Uh,plan--planta--
this plantation,
we're runnin' low on,uh,greenbacks,
and we're havin'
problems payin' the people
who give us the seeds and the dirt.
We can't pay 'em.
Michael,i
can't-- basically,
it could mean a lot of things,
but it is unprecedented,
so it's cause for concern.
Okay,i'm going back to work.
No. No,no. No. No.
No,no,i'm gonna skip forward to
a really big clue. Here we go.
Narrator on cd: well,by now,you figured
out that old beatrix
bourbon was the killer.
What?
Michael,i was doing so well.
Are you goin' to believe that?
That is a mis--
that's a misdirection.
We still don't know who the murderer is.
Nellie nutmeg,come back in heyah!
I can't do this mahself.
Voodoo mama juju!
What am i gonna do?
Okay,so corporate is
still in their meeting.
That could be a good sign.
Hey,everyone,kevin's gonna give
us his take on the situation.
Let's listen up.
All right,guys,it's a workday,
and you guys work here,so
let's go do some work.
Now,jim telling us all to work,
i think that is a very good sign.
Don't just say things.
oh,good,michael.
Listen,i wrote up
those sales targets-- -
i do believe you have me mistaken.
My name is caleb crawdad.
Y'all skedaddled way too soon.
We need to re-open this case.
No,you're not re-opening
the case. The case is closed.
No,it ain't.
Frankly,i'm not surprised.
A lot of the evidence
seemed to be based on puns.
i was just thinking
about weekend at bernie's.
So funny. The guy's dead the whole time.
I haven't seen it.
Speaking of weekends,you excited
about our date this weekend?
Of course,nathaniel.
Okay.
Where are you takin' me?
Well...
The finest steakhouse in all savannah.
Savannah?
That's a far way from scranton.
Did you mean a real date?
No.
- Did you?
- Totally not.
I thought it was for real...
So i was excited,but it was
just-- it was part of the game.
You're sure it was water?
It couldn't have been acid?
I already declared you
it was too dark to tell!
Stop playing games with me,crawdad!
This is not a game! This is my life!
- You are out of order,sir!
- Answer me!
- You are out of order!
- You are out-- - i think
michael may have snapped.
Or maybe he's just stuck in character.
Well,which is worse? Snapped or stuck?
Both. They're both worse.
It's gonna be all right.
We're a good company.
We'll figure this out.
We're not going under.
Jim,what if we both lose our jobs?
I'm trying to think of a way that this
all ends up fine,and
i can't think of one.
Deb,what in the world?
Do you have the vapors?
Michael! Not now.
Can't wait. We have to get you
to our witch doctor right now.
Come on. come on!
I should just go.
Where to now,caleb?
To mama juju boo-boo.
Michael,can
i--
okay,i'm just gonna skip right
past the what and go with why?
Because this is the
re-creation of a crime scene.
I'm the dead body,and
these are my brain chunks.
Hey,shut up. You're dead.
Michael,can i talk
to you in your office?
- No michael here.
- Caleb!
- Today,of all days--
- no! You shut up!
They need this game,jim.
Let us have this stupid
little game,all right?
You startled me!
My stars,my heart nearly
leapt out of my chest.
What can i do you for?
Wallace is on the phone.
He's returning your call.
- Detective wallace?
- I don't think so.
I think it's david wallace
from dunder mifflin.
Aw,shucks. Tell him i'm not heyah.
You're not gonna answer the phone?
No,i only answer to detective wallace,
'cause i got a warm
body in the other room.
I'll take it.
- Hey,david.
- Hey.
Sorry to be gettin'
back to you guys so late.
Things are still a bit unclear.
We didn't officially
decide anything yet.
Oh,okay.
But if i can be candid
with you here,jim...
It's not good. We fully
expect to be out of money
by the end of the
year-- insolvent.
So... Well,you know what?
I'm sorry. I have to run.
- But we will talk soon,okay?
- Sure. Okay.
Oh,you know,while i have you,
- today i was working on this pitch for a supermarket chain...
- great.
And it would actually be a big account.
Okay,look,you know what?
I can't really get my
head around anything
like that right now,but that's great.
Keep after it,but i gotta run.
- Okay. -
Thanks,jim. - See ya.
What's the news?
Nothing yet.
Well,i guess that's not...
well,there is some bad news.
There has been another murder.
A murder,you say?
I do declare.
Conference room,everyone.
Do we have to play?
- No.
- Super.
Oh,this could be a juicy one.
Get in there! Get in there!
I think today was a good
day to have two managers,
because if you're a
family stuck on a lifeboat
in the middle of the ocean,
one parent might want
to just keep rowing.
But if the other parent
wants to play a game,
it's not because they're crazy.
It's because they're
doing it for the kids.
And i get that now.
There has been a lot of
murder and a lot of intrigue.
My little heart can
barely take it no more.
Today is the hardest i have
worked in a long,long time.
- I didn't do it!
- Okay.
- ever'body just calm down.
- I am calm.
Count of three,we're all
gonna put down our guns.
I have crossbows.
- We'll put down our weaponry on the count of three.
- Okay.
- You ready?
- I'm ready.
One... Two... two.
Three. Three.
andy revealed himself
to be a double agent,
at which point,dwight
felt comfortable revealing
that he also was a double agent,
and then,michael announced
to everybody that,
get this,he was a double agent.
Oh,and it is 6:00.
really?
It wasn't me!
I'm not goin' down for this!
Hey,i want to go home.
Get the keys out of
my purse,start the car.