You wanted to see me?
Yeah. Have a seat.
Is it serious?
- Andy's a wittle scawed.
- Okay,right there.
Right there is the problem.
There have been reports
around the office
that you have been talking baby talk.
Why would people say that?
Well,I have it on good authority
that you said the following.
Can you read that back to me?
"Andy have a boo-boo tummy.
Would you rather me say
"hey,guys,my irritable bowel
syndrome is flaring up"?
- Okay.
- "Crazy diarrhea happening right now."
'cause things can get
real adult,real fast.
You are also on record
as saying "wittle-ittle,"
"footy-wutties," "num nums,"
"jammies," "make
boom-boom," "widicuwous,"
and "wode iwand."
Do I sometimes replace rs with ws?
Do I sometimes repeat a
word to get my point across?
Well,if I do,andy's sowwy.
You can't be a baby in the office.
It makes me look like I hire babies.
Well,if we're complaining,
a lot of people think your
elvis voice is annoying
- okay,who said that?
- I don't... Just people.
For the record,I think
it's pretty fantastic.
Well,thank you. Thank you a lot.
And for what it's worth,I
think your baby voice is tops.
- Tank you,Mr. Elwis.
Tuna,md,I have some terrible news.
Wait,are you the patient or the doctor?
The entire office has come down with
a pernicious case of the mondays.
What do you put our chances at?
0%.
Unless we perform an immediate
emergency morale transplant,stat!
- Sounds risky.
- Don't worry. There is a surefire cure.
Employee of the month.
Every awesome place I've worked had one.
Bear stearns. Lehman brothers. Aig.
My summer at enron.
Wow,that's not such a bad idea.
Great! Anything else? Nope.
Frankie's dirty joke of the day?
- There's a bunch of those.
- Keep.
There's a bunch of sent emails
that just say "delivered.
" Should I delete all those?
I want to keep those so
I can see what I sent.
- That's why you have a "sent mail" folder.
- Keep.
- There's about 30 news alerts for "nip slip.
- " For what?
- "Nip slip.
- " Oh,okay.
I don't know how those get there.
- Well...
- Must be hackers.
What's up?
What if I told you I had
done the worst thing ever,
would you still want to be my friend?
Did you murder someone?
- Worse than that.
- Oh,my god.
Lurk much?
I Miss pam.
I think she's okay.
Is that what we're
going for now? "okay"?
We used to go for "pretty good.
" Great. Hey,how do you feel about
starting an employee
of the month program?
Yeah.
You know what,that actually
might make me feel better.
I'm not in this for the trophies,but...
You're not in it at all 'cause you can't
be employee of the month,you're a manager.
Well,technically,I am a co-manager.
And I barely have any responsibilities.
But I work hard,I love this
company,and for those reasons,
I think I would make a
good employee of the month.
It would look bad. Sorry.
It would look good on my mantle.
jim's talking to michael right now ?
they totally went for our idea.
Yeah!
Your idea. My idea.
I just need andy to think it's his idea
so it won't get traced back to me.
In approximately six hours,
jim will get a phone
call from david wallace.
He will be fired.
Hey,pam,do you have a sec
to check over this itinerary?
- Looks great.
- Oh,did you really look it over?
Felt like maybe you didn't.
Okay.
The michael scott foundation
is still in existence.
There you are. I don't think
we have finished with my inbox.
What's "scott's tots"?
Has it really been ten years?
"local businessman pledges
college tuition to third graders.
" Michael,why did you promise that?
To change lives.
No,michael,why would you promise that?
Yeah,okay,I... Call the school. Cancel.
I can't go through with this.
We've already rescheduled seven times.
Michael,this is a
terrible,terrible thing you've done.
- Well... It's terrible.
- No.
Just terrible.
And the longer you put it
off,the worse it's gonna get.
I just... I fell in
love with these kids.
And I didn't want to see them
fall victim to the system.
So I made them a promise.
I told them that if they
graduated from high school,
I would pay for their college education.
I've made some empty
promises in my life,
but hands down,that
was the most generous.
Just tell me it is going
to be okay,all right?
- No!
- I'm not a bad news person. I bring good news.
Like when I promised those
kids i'd pay for college.
Okay. All right.
You have to tell them.
Would you come with me? You
know,like old times instead of...
I can print out a new
itinerary with pam's name on it.
It's fine. Erin,you're going to go.
And you're going to make
sure michael tells the truth.
Agh,god,you know what,could
this day get any worse?
Hey,jimmy,what's up?
- Not much.
- Cool. Very cool.
I bet if you tried,you uld grow the
best beard of anyone in this office.
Thanks,dwight.
- That laugh is so infectious.
- You're creeping me out. I'm gonna go.
I didn't mean any of
those things I just said.
And you can expect the same thing
from everyone in this office
if you don't nip this whole employee
of the month situation in the bud.
Make it about the work.
Let me guess,you think
you should get it.
This encompasses all available data.
Hours. Tardiness. Unconfirmed
sick days. Participation.
Everyone has been
assigned a random number
for total fairness and transparency.
Also,this should be
accompanied by a monetary prize.
Well,in an ideal world...
In an ideal world,I would have
all ten fgers on my left hand
so my right hand could
just be a fist for punching.
Okay,if it's all the same to you,
i'm just gonna take away "survival
skills" and "self-defense.
" I'm gonna run this
by toby in accounting
and have him assemble the data.
That's okay. I'll do it.
Mr. Scott.
Hey,mikela lasker.
- How are you?
- I'm good.
Good to see you. Where's your saxophone?
It's in the music room,Mr. Scott.
Eighth grade graduation,she
gave a rendition of
when the saints go marn
that would blow your freaking mind.
Well,you didn't even hear it.
- Everyone's so excited that you're here today.
- Oh,good.
Now,I know you probably
want to see everyone,
but I was wondering if I could
ask you some questions first.
- Sure.
- You're famous.
the ***
- I'm sure you remember this place.
- Oh,ye.
- Do you want to go in?
- No,not at all. Nope. Come on.
Oh,you know what,you know
what,I shouldn't go in there.
I'm pretty busy. I should...
We just want to say thanks.
Mr. Scott,I know you're a busy man
and your schedule moves around a lot,
but through all your generosity
through the years,your tots,
who are ready to graduate,
thought it was time to
give you a proper thank you.
hey,Mr. Scott ?
what you gonna do?
Make our dreams come true ?
hey,Mr. Scott,what you gonna do?
what you gonna do?
Make our dreams come true ?
you came into our lives
and made a promise ?
that made us honest,made us realize ?
we don't need to compromise
'cause we can have it all ?
'cause you made it possible ?
for us to achieve the improbable ?
hey,Mr. Scott,what you gonna do?
what you gonna do?
Make our dreams come true ?
hey,so jim thought it would be
ideal if we all pitched in...
So jim thought it would be ideal
if we all pitched in a twenty
for this whole employee
of the month thing.
Jim said that?
He thought you were doing
an incredible job last month.
Jim said that?
You seem surprised.
No,no. That makes total sense.
- Hey,buddy.
- Sure.
So every...
Five minutes ahead of schedule.
Right on schedule.
Politicians are always
coming around telling us
they're going to fix our schools.
Promising this and that.
But you,Mr. Scott...
You are actually doing it.
You have taught these kids,
with hard work that
anything is possible.
You are a dream maker.
And I thank you.
I thank you.
So much.
There were a lot of times over the years
where I was pressured to
get into the drug game.
But I always thought back
to my guardian angel...
And the gift that you gave me.
So I just want to thank you
for giving me the
opportunity to go to college,
educate myself,and become
the next president obama.
Oh,god. Oh,god.
Okay,ladies and gentlemen,welcome.
I know you're all very excited.
But no matter who gets this,
I just wanted to say that you guys are
all employees of the month in my eyes.
And the winner is employee number nine.
And that is?
Number nine,number nine.
Jim halpert.
What?
- Are you kidding me?
- Oh,no.
Okay,wait,I was not...
I did not...
I did not.
That was not.
How come not?
Guys,listen,this was
anonymous,all right?
There's no way I could've
given it to myself
because I didn't even
know who was on here.
I just gave it to the employee
with the highest overall score.
To my tally,you just won
back your own parking spot,
a vacation day,and a nice,tidy
quarter of $1,000 from all of us.
Will everybody just stop for a second,
'cause obviously I'm
not taking any of it.
A mistake has been made
and we'll figure it out.
Second of all,there was no cash prize.
- Yes.
- Dwight?
Yeah,you said "in an ideal world,
there would be a cash prize.
" Isn't that what you said?
No,dwight,I meant
"yes,in a perfect world,
someone would get money,but not...
" yeah,but in your perfect
world,only you get money.
Let's put your hands together
and give a warm welcome
for the man of the
hour,Mr. Michael scott.
All right.
Um,I am never going to forget today.
Not a chance.
I don't think I could
ever give back to you
what you have given me today.
Who here has done something
stupid in their lives,
like skipped out on study
hall or mix up the difference
between "a" gym and "b"
gym,that sort of thing?
Show of hands. Anybody.
Yes. Bunch of you. Okay. Well,me too.
I've done something stupid,whh
I would like to share.
Um...
Should we go?
Oh,no. We're okay. It's
a... It's a double period.
All right.
I came here today because
I promised you tuition.
And tuition is very valuable.
But you know what's
invaluable is intuition.
You know what that is?
That is the ability to know when
something is about to happen.
Does anybody out there have intuition?
Know what's gonna happen next?
Nobody? Okay.
You're gonna make me say it.
All right,I am so proud of all of you.
Derrick,and lefervre,and...
And ben,and ayana,and
mikela,and nikki,and jason,and...
I'm... Sorry,okay.
Sorry. Spacing. Your name.
I'm zion. I'm mikela's younger brother.
Well,zion,I am not going to
be paying for your tuition.
Which brings me to my
main point and that is
that I will not be able to
pay for anybody's tuition.
I'm so,so sorry.
- You're kidding.
- Excuse me?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
You lied to us.
I lied to myself too.
I'm not a millionaire.
I thought I would be by the time
I was 30,but I wasn't even close.
And then I thought maybe
by the time I was 40.
But by 40,I had less
money than when I was 30.
Maybe by my 50s,I don't know.
I wanted to pay for your education.
I really did.
It was my dream.
Some people have evil dreams.
Some people have selfish
dreams or wet dreams.
My dream was in the right place.
You owe this to us.
Okay,hold on. Hold on.
Now I can't pay for your college.
But you don't have to go
to class to be in class.
Online courses are a viable option
to a traditional college experience.
And the best way to access those courses
is with your own personal laptop.
Which is rendered
useless without batteries.
And I have one for each of you.
Hey,hold... Hold on. Hold
on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on.
They're lithium.
Look,there was a big
mistake,obviously,so I will fix it. Okay?
This was your idea anyway.
Correction. It was my idea.
- Okay.
- My idea.
Guys,I'm starting to think
pam's not even pregnant.
Okay. For the record,I am pregnant.
And,obviously,there's been
some kind of a mistake.
So why doesn't jim just pick the
next highest score on the list
and we'll move on.
- Yeah. Okay. -
That's fair. - Fine.
- Excellent idea,pam.
- Thank you.
That would be employee
number three,which is...
Son of a bitch!
Pam halpert.
How is that possible? No offense,pam.
But how the hell is tt possible?
There must be some reasonable
explanation for this.
No,wait,come on. I
- I didn't Miss a day.
I came in early. I stayed late.
And I doubled my sales last month.
Oh,really,from what,two to four?
yep.
Guys,this isn't some
elaborate scam,okay?
Hi,I have an order here for
a custom cake,jim halpert.
Okay.
That is me,but I didn't order the cake.
- Look who it is.
- "It could only be you.
- " Way to go.
- He knew all along.
David wallace's office.
This is kevin malone. Is david there?
No,he's in his weekly staff
meeting. Can I take a message?
Tellim I'm mad at jim,
'cause he's asking us
to give money to pam.
This is stanley hudson.
Jim halpert is a menace.
It's toby flenderson.
Listen,things are getting
really bad down here.
Hey,Mr. Scott.
Erin,can you give us a second?
That was messed up what you did.
Yeah. Yeah. I know. I
know. I know. I'm sorry.
Who does something like that?
Who promises that to a bunch of kids
and then just doesn't
come through like that?
What can I do?
You can pay for my college.
I can give you an extra laptop battery.
Not everyone took one.
How about this...
If you can find a way
to pay for your tuition,
let me buy your books,okay?
They're expensive.
Yeah,well,I owe you that at least,right?
It's about $1,000.
Really. That's...
That's over $200 a year.
No,$1,000 each year. For...
Okay. Okay.
Here's what I'm gonna do, i'm gonna
write four checks for $1,000 each.
I'm going to date them one year apart.
Now,you are to use one check a year.
- And please call me before you cash the check.
- Yeah. Yeah.
'Cause I've got monies
to move around,okay?
Make it out to my mom,ros
that's a lot of zeroes.
- This is jim.
- Jim,what the hell is happening there?
- Hey,uh,david.
- Yes.
So there was a little bit of
a miscommunication here today.
It's been a little
wild. Uh,but I am on it.
Just so I understand,you
started employee of the month,
give it to yourself,then
people complain,
so you give it to your wife?
- No.
- Am I missing something?
I really don't know
how it happened,david.
I know how it happened.
Jim,I bumped you up because I
thought you could make my life easier.
If you can't do that,we're
gonna have a separate discussion.
All right,it will not
happen again. I promise.
Uh,hey,I'm sorry. I'm
taking this out on you.
No. It's been crazy here.
You know I think you're
doing a great job,right?
- What?
- Yeah. Thank you.
- No.
- Okay.
Hey,we still on for dinner this weekend?
- What?
- Yes. Okay.
- Oh,you're kidding me!
- See you.
Damn it!
hey,Mr. Scott,what you gonna do?
what you gonna do?
Make our dreams come true ?
hey,Mr. Scott,what you gonna do?
please stop.
15 lives.
I destroyed 15 young lives today.
- No.
- Yes.
No. There's financial aid.
Uh,they could join the army or the navy.
You're what,like,12?
The principal told me that 90% of
scott's tots are on track to graduate
and that's 35% higher than
the rest of the school.
So I think that if you
hadn't made that promise,
a lot of them would've dropped out,
which is something to
think about,I think.
I think you're doing a great job.
Really?
What do you want from this job,
provided the company
doesn't go out of business?
I've always wondered what it
might be like to be an accountant.
- Really?
- Yes.
But I'm terrible at math so...
You know,when I hired kevin,
he was actually applying
for a job in the warehouse.
- Seriously?
- Yeah.
I just sort of had a feeling about him.
I have a feeling about you too.
hey,Mr. Scott,what you gonnao?
what you gonna do?
Make our dreams come true ?
hey,Mr. Scott,what you gonna do?
what you gonna do?
Make our dreams come true ? yeah.
see you tomorrow,dwight.
Apparently.
- How's it going? Good day?
- Not now,temp.
Um,okay. So,um,listen.
I know about your diabolical plan.
What? Diabolical plan?
****
I found a copy of it
hin the copier tray.
So what do you want?
I want the same thing you want.
I want to take jim halpert down.
I want in.