I have a reservation in your fair city
From February 12th through the 19th,
First week of the olympics.
Well, we're looking forward to having you,
So let me just pull up
your information here.
- Okeydoke.
- I don't seem to have it, sir.
What?
I'm not seeing anything
under confirmation.
- No--
- could it be under affirmation?
You have thousands of those. - No.
We're just trying to look it up right now.
i>- You did get the evite
to my barbecue!
- N--come on, dwight.
- Michael--
Um, sir, a lot of people are trying to get
Last-minute reservations at
hotels here for the olympics,
But we've been fully booked for months.
Well, I have been booked for three years.
So you should have that.
I have always heard that british columbia
Is a very nice place,
But I'm not getting that
from this conversation.
Wait! I got it! Confirmation code--
Xv2rdm!
[softly] oh.
Here it is.
- Oh...
- Yep. Uh-huh.
- Uh, thank you.
- Seven nights
In our street view economy single.
- That's it.
- Mm-hmm.
Yeah. We changed systems a while back.
I do apologize.
Together: Uh-huh. Okay...
How may I help you, mr. Scott?
All right, I would like to
cancel my reservation, please.
Well, there is a
cancellation fee for this, sir.
Okay. Put it on my card.
[cheerful music]
Today jo bennett, the ceo from sabre,
Is coming to see us here for the first time.
She bought us sight unseen,
like a mail order bride.
[chuckling] so she's gotta be kinda nervous.
I mean, are we ugly? Are we smart?
Are we cool? Are we too cool?
Do we speak english?
[woman chuckling]
Ha ha.
Why, hello!
- This is michael scott, co-regional manager
Of this branch.
Pleasure to meet you, miss bennett.
Uh, that's mrs. Bennett, sweetheart.
My husband and I are divorced,
but I kept the mrs.
Just to piss off the new wife.
Oh... All: [chuckling]
Well, let's take a
gander around this place.
These sure are pretty dogs.
- They love a good crotch.
- Yeah, they sure do.
You should take that as a compliment.
Oh, I do.
- Hello?
- Hello.
Do you always stay seated
when a lady enters the room?
I am treating you the same as a man
For whom I would also not stand.
Unless it was the president. Or judge judy.
I like that.
- Um, this is accounting.
- Uh-huh.
Hi.
- Good
-looking group.
Over here is meredith palmer,
creed bratton.
Another couple of heartbreakers.
Who's this tall drink of sun tea?
That is jim halpert.
He is the co-regional
manager of this office.
I thought this guy was the manager.
Oh, he is. He's the comanager.
That's the other comanager.
Two guys doing one job?
We gotta do something about that.
[chuckles]
Got some valentines cards for my coworkers
And my bro-workers.
No. No--
What--no candy?
Valentine's day, right around the corner.
Erin and I have been on zero dates.
So I got her a valentine's day card.
But I didn't want to seem too eager,
So I got cards for everyone
in the whole office
To kind of dilute it a little bit.
Look alive.
Ow!
Jeez, you gave me a paper cut on my throat!
Yeah, I have this thing about men cutting
Or threatening to cut my throat.
Don't try to cut my throat.
Jo, I don't know how
things work in florida--
Which, from your description, sounds like
A colorful, lawless swamp.
But here
It takes two men to do one job,
Where in florida it might
take one very strong woman
To do such a job. - Whoa...Whoa!
- Whoa, whoa!
- I'll take over.
Um, what we're doing here--
Michael handles more of
the big picture stuff,
And I handle more of the day-to-day stuff.
- Yeah...
- So together...
- I think I understand.
- All right.
Each of you is doing half a job.
- No.
- And sometimes I can
Hardly handle that.
Now, this is knucklehead talk.
I'm not gonna abide it, you know.
You can't give me gravy
and tell me it's jelly,
'cause gravy ain't sweet... Is it, jim?
[whispers] I don't think so.
- Michael?
- Forget the question.
I think one of you should return to sales
And the other one will be manager.
I humbly accept the management position.
Why would you just automatically get it?
Because...Well, jim,
Where I'm from, there're two types of folk--
Those who ain't,
And those who are kne
e-high on a grasshopper.
Which type ain't you ain't?
Y'all come back now.
Do you even know what that means?
Yes.
Well, I'm gonna let this marinate,
so you can go.
- Um...
- You can go on.
Yep.
Shoo.
I'm joleen bennett. Jo for short.
I'm a breast cancer survivor.
Close, personal friends with nancy pelosi,
And truman capote and I slept
with three of the same guys.
When I was a little girl,
I was terrified to fly,
And now I have my own pilot's license.
I am ceo of sabre international,
And I sell the best damn printers
And all-in-one machines korea can make.
Pleased to meet you.
Whoa, traffic jam.
- Uh-oh! Traffic jam on route 3.
- Beep beep!
20 people dead in a pileup.
There's blood everywhere! [both giggling]
Um, I got you a valentine's card.
- You did?
- Yep.
Oh, a bird and a dog.
Yeah, well, it's snoopy and woodstock.
- You named them?
- Uh, charles schulz did.
I thought it was relevant
'cause I got you all those
birds for christmas.
Remember? - Uh, yeah, I do remember.
Aw, they love each other.
Oh, look at that. They sure do.
I hadn't noticed.
Oh, it smells really good too.
Yeah. It's roger federer for men.
I sprayed some in there.
Andy, whoa! Thank you very much.
It's got pheromones in it.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Uh...Just choosin' seats.
Not getting married.
Chop-chop, little onion.
Jo, there's books in my chair.
That's right, darling.
Now you're the proud new
owner of a sabre handbook
And my autobiography.
Now, you all must be in a tizzy.
I can see it on your faces.
I mean, what's going on now?
I mean, who owns dunder mifflin, right?
I mean, sabre? What's that?
Some company we never heard of
From down in tallahassee?
Where is that? Near mars?
No, we know. Texas.
Now, dunder mifflin has an arm's reach
Into all these small businesses
all over the northeast.
And now we're gonna take that arm...
And we're gonna start selling...
Printers.
I could manage my way around that.
They're the easiest to
use printers in the market.
I will try to manage my excitement.
I have been saying the word "manager" a lot
So whenever jo thinks manager,
she thinks of me.
Camel cigarettes did the
same thing with joe camel
By making him look like a penis.
I can't even go near a cigarette now
Without thinking of a penis.
And vice versa.
I think that's it.
So we're all good.
Thanks, y'all. - I, um...
Oh, my god.
I guess andy likes me.
I never thought of him in that way.
But I guess in most romantic comedies,
The guy you're supposed to be with
Is the one that you never
thought of in that way.
You might have even thought he was annoying
Or possibly homosexual.
So check this out.
According to the handbook,
You could make more money as a salesman
Than as a manager.
They have all these incentive programs.
I ran your numbers from last year.
i>- This is way more than I make now.
I don't think I'm gonna miss being manager.
You know, some people say
they're not in it for the money.
Well, with all due respect to this job,
I think I'm definitely in it for the money.
And, quite honestly, the women.
[click] hey. Got a second?
- Sure.
- All right.
What, are you here to tell me
That you think I would be a better manager
And that you are sorry
for being such a jerk?
Actually...Yeah.
What?
Exactly that.
I think that you
Absolutely deserve the manager
position more than I do.
[laughs] what?
Really? - Yeah.
[laughing] wow! Wow!
* la la la la, hello, oscar *
Michael. Reading.
- What are you reading?
- The atlantic.
Oh, that is my favorite ocean--I love it!
I'm so happy right now.
No! I can't keep it a secret any longer.
Jim's stepping down to salesman.
I am going to be the
sole manager once again.
I should step into sales myself.
Why? Is there an untapped gay market?
Sabre has no caps on commissions.
He can make a lot more
money in sales.
Where did you get that information?
Manual.
Manuel who?
Mm-hmm. Well, according to the manual,
There is no cap on commissions.
I have been hustled.
[quietly] son of a bitch.
Pardon me. - Oh. Speak of the devil.
We were just talking about you. Have a seat.
- Okay.
- Now, jim here is, uh...
Thinking about taking
himself out of the running
For being manager.
- Yep.
- Really?
Oh, that is so sweet of you!
But...
I cannot accept, because I
have been thinking about it,
And I think I want to go back to sales.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah.
You can take the man out of the salesman,
But you can't take the
sales out of salesman.
Well, I think you're both
being a little too modest.
No, I really, really think michael
Is better at being manager
for so many reasons.
- Mm
-mm. No.
I think I would be bad.
I...Would sleep in my office,
And I would sexually harass people.
Why would you do that?
I'm turning myself in right now.
You know, michael,
You have more experience
in sales and management,
So I'm gonna defer to your judgment.
Thank you.
I think you will become the salesman,
And congratulations...
You're gonna be the new
manager of this branch!
Great! That's great.
Congratulations.
[quietly] have fun signing
my commission checks, boss.
Oh! Michael marked his heights.
He's...Grown.
Mm. [both chuckle]
Bobcat, this is dragon.
Listen, he's been promoted to sole manager.
We have got to step this up.
Meet me behind the dumpster in 90 seconds.
89, 88...
You're 20 minutes late.
Um...
I was at another dumpster.
Just admit you lost track of time.
Ryan and I have been meeting up
To work on our diabolical plot against jim.
Ryan is always late for our meetings.
I wish I had a lair.
i>- Did you see saw?
Course I seesaw.
Mose and I seesaw all the time.
No. Uh, the movie.
Did you see the movie saw?
Oh. Yeah. Great film.
Almost as fun as going on a seesaw.
Okay, the reason these
movies are so popular
Is the element of psychological torment.
I like where you're going with this.
Continue.
Can we lure him into an
old warehouse or something?
I have an old barn.
It's kinda smelly... - Yes!
But that might be a plus. Okay, then what?
i>- We do what they did in saw.
I mean, we don't kill him, obviously.
- I don't--
- I have a mask...
Okay. That's your idea?
Exactly like in the movie?
That is the most idiotic thing
I have ever heard in my life!
Well, suggest something
else then, don't just--
He's supposed to cut his leg off?
- Don't just criticize my idea!
- Think!
You think of something then!
Michael, I'm worried that, uh,
Not all your toys are gonna
fit on your new desk.
How is that possible?
Well, in your old office,
There were all those
ledges and extra space--
No excuses, erin. Come on!
Make it happen.
You know, I actually think
that I should get back to work.
Jim asked me to do some stuff,
and he's manager.
Oh. Yeah. Fine, fine.
- Okay.
- Leave it here.
All right.
I have to make some sales anyway.
Who should I call with
my magic sales fingers?
[telephone rings]
[ringing]
Michael scott, head of sales.
You gotta do something, man.
You can't just sit there.
The new I.T. Guy.
Nick.
- Nick.
- I think he's the key.
He's very trusting.
He's looking for friends.
He's been given an awesome amount of power
And does not know how to wield it.
Like frodo.
Why don't you just let me
handle the tolkien references,
Okay, dumb jock?
Well, I think he can be corrupted.
Like gollum.
Smeagol was corrupted
And became gollum.
I might start a diabolical
plot against him
After this one.
Who's hungry?
- What is that?
- That's ants on a log.
Michael would always have
me bring them in at 2:30
And say, "who's hungry?" - [laughs] oh.
I'm fine. Thank you, though.
Do you want me to spin you in
your chair and make you dizzy?
- Why would I want to do that?
- It's a thinking technique.
All the top executives do it.
It keeps the brain moving,
And a...Spinning brain is a working brain.
For now, I'm just gonna
go back to work here.
- Oh, sure.
- Yeah. Thank you.
Well...
It will be a pleasure
doing business with you.
Thanks. Bye-bye.
[train whistle sound]
I just got a new account.
The gentleman's club in carbondale.
It is called curves.
I went by there the other day.
Saw some of the women walking in.
Not...Really my cup of tea.
Actually, kevin, you might like it.
Nice.
You know, we really
don't announce out loud
Our sales that much.
Why not? It's part of
the sales experience.
It's not really 1992 anymore.
Well, okay.
[laughter]
"you brighten my day with
the sound of your voice.
"you bring so much laughter and love.
"you're everything to me,
And I was so blessed when
god sent you here to me."
- Jeez louise.
- I know.
Obsessed with me much?
- Well, everyone got one.
- What did yours say?
"friends are worth
sharing a doghouse with."
It's no wonder
That andy gave kelly such a romantic card.
I can't compete with her.
That girl can sing and dance
And gets all of her clothes at the mall...
And I feel like such a fool
For thinking that andy was
only going after one girl.
'cause andy bernard is a playboy,
And why shouldn't he be?
He's got it all.
Ho ho. There he is, the I.T. Guy.
See you discovered the break room.
- Uh, yep.
- I imagine
One of the best things
about being an I.T. Guy
Is you get to know everyone's
computer passwords.
You know, I actually don't.
[all laugh]
Listen. I know you have to say that,
But we got a little problem here.
There is a employee named jim halpert,
And he's doi some terrible things, okay?
He's molesting people via the internet,
And we need to stop him.
I think that you should call the cops--
No. The cops called us.
So I'm gonna need you
to give me the password
To jim halpert's computer.
I don't know what to tell you,
man, I'm sorry.
I just can't give out
his password like that.
Nick, we could make things very...
Very difficult for you.
Are you...
You threatening me?
Threatening you?
No.
What is that smell? Do you smell that?
What is that?
Like a sulfur deposit under here?
Michael...Stop.
No, I'm serious. We don't have to put up--
Is it the dogs? - [whispers] michael.
You know what?
We don't have to deal with this.
I'm going to google sulfur maps.
Michael, it's phyllis.
No, this is geological.
I sent an email out
to everyone in this area
That this might be a side effect
To my new allergy medication I'm on.
- Are you kidding me?
- No.
And you guys are okay with this?
She sent an email...
It's not 'cause of the smell.
I'm just expecting a nosebleed.
Oh, my god.
Oh...[giggling] you scared me.
I'm sorry. I thought you saw me.
I didn't see you.
And you were there all along.
Well, I warmed it up for you.
So should be good to go.
Cool. Thanks.
Bye, andy.
- That was weird.
- No, it ain't.
We all saw the valentine you gave her.
I don't even know what that card said.
Believe me, if I got that card,
We'd be in the bathroom
doing it right...Now.
Oh!
Hey.
You know, it's funny,
I used to stand in here
And wish I was out there.
Now I'm out there, and I wish I was in here.
Well, the grass is always greener.
Yeah. Except there's no grass out there.
It's just a farty dirt patch.
Well, it's what you wanted.
I really need my job back.
We made a terrible mistake here.
For the record, I fought this, all right?
And now...I'm not really sure what we do.
We make a poster that
says "happy opposite day,"
And she sees it on the way out--
That's stupid.
Oh, I wish we had one of those
Amnesia flashlights from men
in black and just--
Hey, what was that movie
Where their boss was within earshot,
And they could have just
gone and talked to her?
- Lethal weapon?
- That's it.
I think we should do it the
lethal weapon way.
You two are grown-ass men.
What do I have to do,
Fire you and get two people in here
Who don't need so much management?
Wha...? What I'm saying--
Michael's saying that he's
better at being a manager,
And I agree, because he's
a better people person,
Weird--weirdly. - And weirdly,
I'm a good dog person, right, guys?
See? They love me.
Fine. I don't care which
one of you does which job.
Just...Stop meetin' with
me to talk about it.
All right.
[cell phone rings] - oh.
I gotta take this.
Yep. Uh, finish walking my dogs for me.
And don't ride 'em.
Lotta people try to ride 'em.
'scuse me, everyone.
Please check your emails.
I just sent you the following message:
"coworkers, you may have
received a valentine from me.
"please understand this does not mean
That I like you in any way."
You don't even like us as friends?
Phyllis, you guys are
like my closest friends.
I just mean I don't like like you.
What are we, five?
"please don't read into this card.
Yours, in professionalism, nard dog."
Um, why did I just receive
a mass email from you
That said that you don't like me?
Do you realize how hard that
makes me like you, andy?
It's--
That wasn't--
I like someone else.
Who?
[snorts]
It's...Not...
Whether or not...
[mumbles]
Who? What?
Yeah, I guess andy never liked kelly.
How about that?
[inhales]
Oh, it smells good in here.
It sure does. Okay, we have your...
Space heater, your humidifier,
your dehumidifier,
Your fan, your foot fan,
and your food dehydrator.
Erin...What about my keyboard?
[soft electronic music]
Ah.
So good to be home.
* *
How 'bout a little bossa nova?
Oh...
[bossa nova plays]
* *
He looks happy.
Yep.
Well, well, well. Hmm.
Boss for...What was it?
Oh...4 1/2 hours?
New record... Low.
Previous record, henry rostin.
Boss for nine years, four months.
And he only left
Because he had family matters to attend to,
And he--what--
Michael?
I can't help but think
That something we did made this possible.