Oscar, Toby said
he left my girl scout cookies
on my chair.
Have you seen them?
Wait, I'm sitting on them.
This is awesome.
Thank you.
It didn't even take that long.
What's the difference
between a chimichanga,
a chalupa,
and a tostada?
Call me back ASAP.
It's urgent.
This isn't funny.
I don't talk like that.
Say, "Me eat cookie."
I won't say it.
Why is everyone clumped
around accounting?
Break it up, you clique.
It's Kevin as cookie monster
from Sesame Street.
Is that the program
where all those puppets
live in the barrio?
- Mm-hmm.
- I love that show.
This is Kevin. This is Kevin.
Thank you.
That is an amusing link.
I'd like it sent to me,
please. - Yes.
Me too, Oscar.
Please send it to me.
C.C. Me.
Angela, this is inappropriate.
This is my favorite day.
It's secretary's day.
And it is Erin's and my
three-week anniversary.
So perfect storm for
a romantic gesture.
Want to make sure the
whole office remembers
it's secretary's day.
I sent an email blast,
a text blast,
a good, old-fashioned talk blast.
I sent a snail mail
blast a week ago.
And a stern reminder via fax at 7:00
this morning,
so people better step up
and appreciate the
crap out of Erin.
- Here you go.
- Oh, thank you.
I do.
Thank you.
If it wasn't for secretaries,
I wouldn't have a stepmom.
- Welcome back.
- Hey, thanks.
It's my first day back
after maternity leave.
And I miss Cece, of course.
But we need the money.
What was maternity leave like?
Oh, how do I explain it?
It rocked.
It rocked my ass off.
Oh. You couldn't have watered it?
I literally did not
know that existed
until this moment.
Well, I knew it existed,
and I chose to let it die.
It's nice to see
you again, Dwight.
Hello, Pam.
I was just wondering
what you had planned
for secretary's day.
I'm going to give Erin $15.
I know that Erin
would be so psyched
if you took her out to lunch.
- A one-on-one lunch with Erin?
- Yeah.
She really looks up to you.
And there's only so much
we can do as her coworkers.
Secretary's day is really kind
of a boss-secretary thing.
She's kind of a rube.
That's my girlfriend
you're talking about.
Okay. All right. All right.
Okay. I'll take her to lunch.
She's gonna be so psyched.
Hi, Erin.
Happy secretary's day.
Well, happy boss's day.
There wouldn't be a secretary
if there was no boss.
I wanted to know what
your plans for lunch were
because I was hoping
to ask you to...
Lunch.
I got a picture of
you asking me to lunch.
I was thinking we could
go to Hayworth's.
- Ugh.
- Just the two of us.
Well, Hayworth's is
more business casual,
and they always
screw up your order.
So I'm... - Yeah, okay.
Yeah, that was a
stupid suggestion.
I was thinking someplace special,
so I thought Hayworth's, but...
Okay, well,
we'll figure something.
Oh.
Okay, let's go to Hayworth's.
- Okay.
- All right.
Have a cookie, kev.
Yeah, ha ha. Tray of cookie.
I'm not falling for that.
I brought those in.
It's my birthday.
That's some stone-cold
narcissism right there.
Man, Darryl, I'm sorry.
Happy Birthday. - Thank you.
Yum, yum, yum, yum, yum, yum.
They're making fun
of cookie monster.
I get that.
But in a strange way, it feels
like they're making fun of me.
Oscar, did you eat
some of my m&m's?
The level-- - this is
violent and offensive.
Thank you.
It really make me
self-conscious about my voice.
- It's awful.
- I'm not crying.
You have some food on your face.
Do my hands feel sweaty to you?
The beginning here has been
a little bit of a fiasco.
Either they don't respect me
or they respect me too much.
And some of them still think
that I'm the I.T. Guy.
This cookie monster
thing is an opportunity
to show people that I'm
an authority figure.
Hello, everyone.
If I might have a
moment of your time.
It's come to my attention
that people have been watching
and laughing at a
hurtful parody video.
It is now forbidden to talk,
joke about,
or email this around.
Yeah.
And that's straight
from corporate.
So, not to be scary,
but, yeah, I would listen to me.
And that's all.
Ciao.
Would you mind if I
listen to my book on tape?
I'm kind of a bookworm.
This is a novelization
of the movie
Based on the book push by sapphire.
I was thinking it would be
fun to talk on the way over.
So what decade would you
have chosen to be a teenager?
I don't know.
I would have chosen the 1490s.
'Cause America was discovered.
Right.
And then my last job was
at a taco bell express.
But then it became
a full taco bell,
and I don't know,
I couldn't keep up.
My favorite part about
being a receptionist
is that I get to have my own desk.
In my foster home,
I never had a desk.
So it's like--I don't mean that
I didn't like my foster home.
I did like it.
I just didn't have a desk there.
Did you have a favorite age?
Or month?
An age or month?
Yeah, like a favorite month.
Like, I like April
when I was seven.
I've been trying.
I've been trying
to keep it going.
Erin is just weird.
How many pillows do
you sleep on at night?
So how are things
going with Andy?
He's the best
boyfriend in the world.
Tell me about him
before I met him.
Well, let's see.
Um... Andy.
Plays the banjo.
Yeah. I love that.
Other than the fact
that he dated Angela,
I don't think he is
a snappy dresser.
What?
I don't think he
is the best dresser.
Reminds me of Easter.
Sorry. About Angela?
Did you say he dated Angela?
Mm-hmm.
You didn't know that?
Oh. - Here we go. Hot plate.
- Okay.
- And your salad, miss.
Why wouldn't he tell me that?
I don't know.
Probably didn't want you
to have a mental image
of him having sex
with somebody else.
They had sex?
They were engaged, so...
Okay. You know what, sir?
Yes.
Yeah, I asked for
pickles with my burger,
and there are only,
like, five or six.
Could I get some more pickles?
Of course. I'll get
you a bowl of pickles.
- Thank you.
- They were engaged?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
- Uh-oh.
- Well...
What are you doing?
In the foster home,
my hair was my room.
Okay. You know what?
You know what? You know what?
Everybody's looking
at you right now.
I'll have what she's having.
- Did you have a-
- did you like your lunch?
Did you have a good lunch?
Did you like that?
Did you enjoy your food?
It was good. I liked my lunch.
Ooh.
Ah-ah-ah. Ha-ha.
- What's up?
- Her milk is coming in.
She's getting uncomfortable.
Dwight, don't be gross.
No, no, he's right.
Same thing happens with my cows
if I don't tend them
frequently enough.
You gotta milk them,
or else they'll moo like crazy.
That's weird.
My breast pump is missing.
Have you seen my breast pump?
All right,
this is gonna traumatize me
a hell of a lot more than you,
believe me.
You know what, Dwight?
Let me just check
the bathroom first.
Okay? - Really? Fine.
Let your breasts explode.
Three squeezes and
I would drain you.
Mm.
Meredith!
I just like the way it feels.
What are you doing?
- Relax. Okay.
- Relax?
This is like the
Cadillac of pumps.
Give it back to me now.
Okay, I was just warming it up.
It's disgusting!
- It's not a big deal.
- It's not sterile!
We're both girls. Who cares?
So...
How was lunch?
Lunch was fine.
Was it everything that you
hoped and dreamed it might be?
I don't know.
It was lunch, Andy.
Well, I know.
Just want-- I mean...
Erin?
I think we're out
of fax cover sheets.
God, Oscar,
will you keep your pants on?
It's easy.
"My name is Kevin.
I'm an accountant."
See, I did the voice.
That's a little derivative.
But parody is always derivative.
Uh, it's not organic.
Do you know what I mean?
Jim does a really good one.
Do yours. - Oh, guys.
I really refuse to participate.
"Michael, can I have an
advance on my paycheck
because a Mrs. field cookie
just opened up at the mall."
Guys, why don't we
leave the parodies
to the pros at madtv?
"Sorry, Gabe, but that show
hasn't been on in many cookies."
Okay.
Hey, can I have your
attention, please?
First of all, thanks to everyone
for helping put this
awesome party together.
And a very special
shout-out to the chair
of the party planning committee,
miss Angela Martin.
You have outdone yourself.
You know what,
I think we can all agree
that Angela's not so great, so...
I am saying the exact opposite.
Angela is fantastic.
No. No. No.
- Specific shout-out...
- Stop talking.
Okay.
As some of you may know,
I have a very special
connection to secretary's day
in the form of that 115-pound
moonbeam over there
named Erin hannon.
To a lot of you she
may just be the person
who brings you your
fax confirmations,
but to me, she is my girlfriend...
In addition to being the person
who brings me my
fax confirmations.
So I wrote a Little ditty
that I would like to play
for all of you right now.
It's a little tune called
secretary of love.
A one, a two,
a one, two, three--
I know about Angela.
I know that you
were engaged to her
and that you were
sleeping with her.
Michael told me. - Oh, God.
Erin, can we talk
about this in private?
I don't want it
to be in private.
Is it true or is it not?
- Yes.
- Who else did you sleep with?
Did you sleep with
Phyllis or Kelly or Pam?
Maybe all together?
- No. No, never.
- Did everyone know?
Was I the only one
who didn't know?
- Yeah, pretty much.
- Pretty much.
Who are you? I don't know you.
I don't know you!
I should probably
get involved in this,
but I think my energy
is better spent
on the cookie monster issue.
Erin, you know,
if I had been engaged
to anybody before you,
I would have told you.
Thanks.
So if you need anything,
I'm right over there.
"Hey, Erin, you look delicious.
I mean, beautiful."
Okay.
Okay. There. I heard that.
So I'm sorry, Pam, but that's it.
I'm going to have to
suspend you without pay
for two days.
What? What do you mean,
suspend me?
I think you need
to go a little easy.
You can't just suspend
someone from work.
Yeah, you're right.
You know what?
Um, you're suspended too, Jim.
Okay. - Fine. You too, Dwight.
Wait, what?
I was just slow-clapping
your no-nonsense decision-making.
I don't want to hear it.
Suspended.
"C" is for suspension.
Why would that be something
that you would talk about
on secretary's day?
Andy, she's not the
easiest person in the world
to have a conversation with.
All right? And besides,
who doesn't tell their girlfriend
that they were engaged to someone
who works four feet
away from them?
That's like-- that's--
that's, like, mr. And Mrs.
smith crap.
I was gonna tell her,
just on my own time.
You know what,
I resent the implication
that I would keep that secret.
Everyone here knows that I can't
and won't keep a secret.
Who cares?
I mean, it's not like
I killed somebody.
Big deal, right?
This can blow over in two seconds.
She never asked me, so,
if you think about it...
I probably should have
told her, I guess.
Everybody does stupid things.
Psst. Hey.
Erin. - You want to talk to me,
come to my desk.
You embarrassed me earlier.
Oh, take it up with
the chief of police.
You think I want
people remembering
I had sensual relations with Andy?
It's the kind of thing you
wish you could have annulled.
I want to throw up
just thinking about it.
I want to throw up just
thinking about it.
You are throwing up
for the wrong reasons.
I don't think this
fax is going through.
Is there a different...
I can just put it
through again, you know.
Hey.
You know, I was
engaged before Jim.
Really?
Yeah. And he worked here too.
It was Andy, wasn't it?
No, no, it wasn't Andy.
It wasn't.
It doesn't matter.
It's not about who
you've been with.
It's about who you end up with.
Sometimes the heart
doesn't know what it wants
until it finds what it wants.
I hope you find what
you're looking for.
Thank you.
So I can reprimand them,
but I can't suspend them.
Oh, I can't do either.
Uh-huh. Fair enough.
Hey, Toby.
I called Tallahassee.
He can ask you not to come in,
but he can't dock your pay.
That's not legal.
Very interesting.
Yeah, I also learned
some interesting things
about how they structure--
thanks, Toby.
Hey, everyone. Hi.
Quite an afternoon, huh?
Cathartic in a way.
I'm glad that I got
to share it with you.
It makes you think about
what's really important.
It's not about showing
you're in charge
or flexing some sort of authority.
It's about forgiveness.
And, yes, I'm talking
about you three
in this desk clump right here.
I think that, if you
were to apologize to me,
then I would revoke
your suspension.
I don't think an
apology is enough.
I really think the only way
for me to learn my lesson
is to take my suspension.
And I got to take
this bad attitude,
and I got to go home,
and I got to adjust it.
And I hope the
suspension does that.
Prideful idiots.
Watch how it's done.
Gabriel, I apologize.
Great.
I kneel before you.
Guys, I would even
take a contrite look
as an apology.
Humbly taking your
hand upon which I kiss
to show my contrition.
Guys, to err is human.
Trust is the most
important thing to me.
Is your name Andy Bernard?
What's your real name?
Lionel frankenstein?
Will you stop walking
for one second?
That's it.
There's no other secrets.
Okay? I mean, yeah,
my chest is not
naturally hairless,
and my parents pay
my credit card bill.
How long were you guys together?
- A year.
- A year?
You were together for a year.
Yeah. But that's it.
Now you know everything about me.
I promise.
And if I think of anything else...
I think I have to be on
my own for a little bit.
Like that girl precious
in precious:
Based on the novel push by sapphire.
Okay?
I didn't see that movie.
That was ugly.
I'm sorry that you
had to see that.
Do they still get paid?
It's tacky to discuss finances.
It's best to pretend
that this never happened.
Sounds like they just
got to go home with pay.
- Yeah.
- Pathetic.
- Very nice.
- Can I buy everyone coffees?
"Or cookies."
- Oh.
- What was that?
Was that an impression?
All right.
Uh, guys,
I'm now going to apologize
for the mess that we're in.
Because corporate told me to.
I just want you to know I
laugh like a crazy person.
Okay.
You got to be able to-
you got to be able
to laugh at yourself.
I'm one of the gang.
"I have to go back to the zoo
to the stick insect exhibit."
"Ciao."
Right? "Ciao.
I say ciao 'cause I'm
fancy from Tallahassee."
Why don't we say "ciao"
to the impressions?
Ciao.
- Ciao. Filming.
- Ciao, stick insect.
Ciao.
God.
- Erin?
- Oh.
Sorry. I thought
everyone was gone.
No, no, I was just
watching cookie monster.
Finally downloaded.
Mind if I sit down?
- Yeah.
- What's, um...
I can't trust Andy anymore.
Oh. Yep.
I'm sorry about that.
I feel-- I'm sorry I
caused that thing.
It's Andy's fault.
Well, yeah, yes.
But I still feel sorry.
Oh.
You know what,
I wouldn't worry about Angela.
She's-- she doesn't hold a candle
to you, Erin.
She's old enough to be
your mom for one thing,
and she's, like, three feet tall.
And she wears pioneer
women clothing.
And I don't think
she's ever pooped
in her life.
And Andy, you know, come on.
Andy, his butt looks
big in those khakis.
Oh, I like his butt.
You said butt.
- You tricked me.
- Ahh!
Ahh.
You said it.
You know who'd you love?
Oh, this guy
in my neighborhood, Tom dizemore.
This is him. "Hey! Hey, Scott!"
Sometimes,
telling someone something
is hard.
Well, at least somebody made
her happy on secretary's day.
Hey, Kevin, it's Oscar.
I'm looking at the
sheet you sent me.
And I can't seem to find the
column for shipping costs
I made the most brilliant
the retaliation video.
It is so awesome.
I don't get it.
Yeah, I mean, the Count
has a very distinct voice.
Yeah. "I vant to count to ten."
But Oscar is an accountant,
and the Count counts numbers.
Your an accountant too,
so, it doesn't...
Why didn't you do Oscar the grouch
that would have been funny.
That would have been funny.
But the Count is purple,
and Oscar wears purple.
Oh! Oh! I was just watching that.
Did you do that man?
Oscar!
I am the Count...
Nailed him. Nailed him!
Good work cookie monster.
Thank you.