Back orders and you
never call them.
- Can you believe this?
- There's a dog in the car.
You can't leave a dog
in a parked car!
Snowboarder, it figures.
Dude, snowboarders
ain't animals?
I bet this guy didn't leave
his weed in the car.
Okay, we have to do something
because this is incredibly dangerous.
Oscar, is not that hard out.
A car parked in the sun
is like a toast oven.
Well, we don't know how long
the driver's been gone and
it's not in direct sun light.
So what, Andy?
You wanna just let him die,
you scumbag?
Here, I'm gonna get in my car.
When I start dying,
I will honk the horn
three times.
That means save the dog.
Okay, you know what?
I'm gonna give him
something to drink.
Come here, doggy.
Come on.
Dwight, at least aim it.
There you go.
Here, doggy.
You're not even trying.
Come here, doggy, come on.
We're losing cloud cover.
Oh, don't try to get in
on it now, Michael Vick.
Hey, hey, hey.
Vick did his time.
This guy's been gone
long enough.
He's lost his right
to a window.
Get back, buddy.
Get back.
Oscar, what are you--
What-- No, hey!
All right.
Yeah!
Nice job, Oscar.
And one for good measure.
Oh!
Yeah!
So, uh-- Who's gonna
take the dog?
Why would we take the dog?
What if he jumps out
the window and runs away?
Jim, he's not gonna start--
Shh, stay, stay.
Nein. Sit.
Good.
Oscar, what do you wanna do?
This is kinda your deal.
You want a dog?
There we go.
That should do it.
- Yeah, it's good.
- It'll work.
Nice job.
- Bye, poochie.
- Bye.
Woof, woof.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
What's that come to?
Like, what did they each win?
Oh man, it's gotta be...
Over $100,000.
Yeah, before taxes.
That's still a lot of money.
The warehouse crew won
the lottery yesterday.
$950,000.
And then they quit.
And, no one else can focus.
This is it.
This is all on my shoulders.
I'm the one who has to tell
everyone to get back to work.
I'm the one
who has to tell Darryl to hire
a new warehouse crew.
I'm the one who has to say
those things.
Hello?
Justine.
Nice surprise.
How you doing, baby?
No, no, no.
I didn't win.
When I got promoted,
I stopped--
What?
Yeah, yeah.
Glen won.
Oh, you wanna call him?
Yeah, you should call him.
Congratulate him.
That would be--
What?
Oh, this number
is in your old phone.
Oh, you know what?
I might have it right--
Whoops.
When I worked in the warehouse,
I was part of that lotto pool.
They won...
Playing my birthday.
What really interests me is
the group dynamic of six people
winning the lottery.
This will not end well, right?
Yeah.
We're looking at
at least one suicide
- and one weird sex thing.
- At least.
I don't even know what
I'd do with all that money.
I know what you'd do
with all that money.
"Hey, Pam.
Let's buy
expensive bathrobes and hug."
No, I'd probably buy
a big piece of land in Maine,
build a house, work in town.
Somewhere I could
bike to or kayak to.
And either bike to my job
at the kayak shop
or kayak to my job
at the bike shop.
And then on the weekends,
would you hackysack
back to reality and spend time
with your wife and kids?
Whoa, saucy.
I thought you liked Maine.
I think we should get
a townhouse in Soho.
Soho's mostly lofts, but okay.
And then, every morning,
I'd walk out onto my terrace,
and I would breathe
in the inspiration of the city.
You know, and just gather
ideas for my painting.
Oh, God.
And then my handsome husband--
Which, ideally, would be me.
Would bring me
a flavored coffee.
Stop. I'm a barista
in your fantasy?
Well, in your fantasy,
we're Stephen King characters.
I don't know
about Stephen King.
Get a divorce. Get a divorce.
I think I would keep working.
And for my salary,
I guess I would take, like,
a dollar a year.
Obviously, I wouldn't come
in till noon.
And I wouldn't do anything
I didn't wanna do.
I mean, I'm getting paid
a dollar a year, okay?
You can chill.
Are you kidding me?
Guys?
If I have to ask you to
get back to work one more time,
I'm gonna change my tone.
To down here, like Mr. T.
And this would get
seriously annoying.
I feel sympathy for the jerks
who have to listen
to this all day.
Darryl.
How we doing on
the new warehouse guys?
I don't know.
What--
Wh-Wh-
Do we have new guys?
No.
Are they on their way over?
I haven't hired anyone.
What?
No warehouse guys?
I have an important order
that has to go out by five.
I emailed you about it.
I'm not checking email
until lunch.
4-hour work week.
- This is kind
of time-sensitive.
I got it.
I'm doing it.
Andy, this is
a seriously big order.
I can't lose this client.
All right, well,
until we have a new crew,
let's get some volunteers
for warehouse duty.
Who's in?
As long as you guys
don't need me up here.
I think we'll be fine.
Really?
Nobody's gonna help her?
Is chivalry dead?
Are you volunteering?
Of course...I would.
But my hip--
I would kill to be at 100%.
Jim, how about you?
Uh, yeah--
I mean,
as the strongest person in this
office, I guess I should--
Okay, no, no.
That-- You are so not--
Oh, God.
False.
Andy, I will volunteer.
Great.
And Kevin.
Good old Kevin.
He'll do anything.
Well, guess what?
I will not do a good job.
- Oh, thank you.
- Sure.
Wait, wait.
What's this?
Oh, sorry.
I thought it was
a guess-your-baby's-birth
weight pool.
It says "lotto pool."
Right on top.
Yeah.
And I said sorry.
Oh, come on.
You really think I'm gonna have
a 14-pound baby?
When did I get so fat?
You look awesome.
I didn't hire anyone
if that's why you're here.
Where are we in the process?
I have a file
of applicants here.
I just gotta open it,
look at it,
interview a bunch of guys,
hire some of them.
So I say we're in the early
stages of the process.
Did you go out celebrating
with the guys last night?
They guys did invite me
out to celebrate,
but I decided to just stay home.
Eat a bunch of tacos
in my basement.
You do have
a fantastic basement.
I did.
I did have
a fantastic basement.
Now it smells like tacos.
You can't air out a basement.
And taco air is heavy.
It settles at the lowest point.
Right, um,
well, how about we take
a look at some applications?
This guy wrote his in green ink.
That's pretty cool.
Check it out.
Hey.
There you go.
There he is.
That is not Darryl.
I don't know where Darryl is.
I suspect, probably,
our Darryl is
inside of that Darryl.
Okay. 300 boxes
of 20 pound white.
That's 75 boxes per person.
So, that's not so bad.
Negative.
300 boxes for me,
0 for you chumps.
Deal with it.
Nice.
Whoa, oh, oh, oh, oh!
Oh!
Damn.
Ah!
Yup.
Welcome everybody.
My name is Andy,
and this is
my other brother, Darryl.
What? No Newhart fans?
Okay.
Darryl, how do we
usually kick things off?
You mean, what did
we do the last time
the warehouse won the lottery?
Your old crew won the lottery?
Does anyone have experience
shelving, storing,
keeping track--
What do we use?
The Dewey decimal system?
Wait, wait.
So, all the old guys quit?
- Oh, yeah.
- Well--
One of them, Glen, is starting
one of those fat camps
where he steals your kid
in the middle of the night.
Madge and a couple of the guys
might start a strip club.
But on a boat.
And Hide is investing
in an energy drink
for Asian homosexuals.
Um, could you guys
give us a minute?
But stay close.
You're all doing great.
Maybe grab a coffee,
or if there's any donuts out,
you can split one.
You know, they're for everybody
so people get fussy.
You know what?
Just have a donut.
Do you want to talk about this
- not-winning-the-lottery thing?
- I don't.
You sure? 'Cause you keep
talking about it, so--
Nope. I'm good.
I'm here.
Let's find
some warehouse workers.
Good, great.
Then, can you say things
that aren't like,
a huge bummer to everybody?
'Cause the more I talk,
the more they're gonna realize
I don't know
what I'm talking about.
Okay.
We need you, okay?
- Okay?
- Yeah.
All right.
What's the problem?
Grunting is scientifically
proven to add more power.
Ask any female tennis player,
or her husband.
I didn't feel anything.
All right, thank you
for coming back in.
Again.
Now we're going to ask you
a few questions.
Darryl, you have the floor.
Why do you want to work here?
I need a job.
It's not a good reason.
Good.
Keeping them honest.
Don't just take the first job
that comes your way.
'Cause next thing you know,
it's ten years later,
and you're still there.
You could write
your obituary tomorrow.
It's not gonna change.
Are we scaring them straight?
I hope so.
Think about this carefully.
There's better lives
than this one.
I've never been lucky.
And I'm not talking
about the lottery.
I'm talking about stuff like
developing a soy allergy at 35.
Who gets a soy allergy at 35?
And why is soy in everything?
Nice.
Right back where I like you.
Can you make
ten copies of this for me?
No.
Why not?
What are you doing?
Uh, buying
lottery tickets online.
Ah, everyone wants to be rich.
But nobody wants to work for it.
You came in at 10:30 today,
right?
Okay, just dismiss it.
- Is everyone licensed?
- Like a driver's license?
No.
Warehouse license.
Master's in warehouse sciences.
I feel that Darryl has talked
about a license of some kind.
- Is this a joke?
- No. Not joking.
This is real.
Painfully real,
what is happening, right now.
Okay, I'm not gonna make it.
I'm turning back.
There's gotta be
a better way to do this.
This is literally
how they built the pyramids.
Well, they whipped people,
which is helpful.
But you're right.
We should be able to find
a more efficient way
of moving boxes
than Madge and Hide.
Yeah.
Not that they're not
smart people.
No, no.
Very smart--
Theirs is more of
a "physical" intelligence.
I'd go with that.
Like baboons or elephants.
Not that, don't--
Guys, when I was a kid,
my sisters used to butter me up,
and slide me across
the linoleum floor
of the kitchen.
It really made them laugh.
It's a great idea, Kev.
I don't think
it applies here, though.
So, maybe we just--
Yeah, we move stuff
and have fun.
Kevin, doesn't apply.
Right, my mom--
You need to drop it.
Okay?
They hate it.
I like it a lot,
but they hate it,
so drop it.
Does anybody get distracted
easily by bubble wrap?
You'll be dealing with
lots of bubble wrap.
Obviously.
Um--
How much longer
is this going to take?
Did you hire them?
No, because they all left.
What do you mean, "they left"?
I mean, after you bailed,
I got confused,
and frankly, a little weird.
And the stuff that you said
certainly didn't help.
Then I think
you should fire me.
What are you talking about?
I'm not gonna fire you.
Yeah, just put me
out of my misery.
Okay, this is weird.
I don't-- I don't get the joke.
No? Okay.
I don't wanna be here anymore.
Fire me.
So Darryl says to me, "fire me",
but what he really means is,
"I'ma say
something really weird.
Try and figure out
what it means."
So I say,
"no, you're not fired."
But what I really mean is,
"I've no idea what
you're talking about.
"But I'm going to go ahead
and hire some people
"for the warehouse
and hope that
you eventually
start feeling better."
I really hope that's what
he and I mean.
Attention.
Does anyone know anyone
who could work in a warehouse?
We can pay.
Come on, Oscar.
Who's the most jacked guy
in all of Scranton?
Like your wildest fantasy guy?
Bulk or definition?
Definition.
Bruce Kenward.
He hangs out at planet fitness.
Are those just show muscles,
or is he really strong?
Oh, he's plenty strong.
He used to be Reggie Winters
out at gold's gym.
But he moved away.
And then it was between
Bruce and this guy, Dean.
Um, but Dean got fixated
on his calves,
and, uh,
and his triceps went to hell.
So, I've been thinking,
after we win the lottery,
we take our winnings...
Our fake winnings.
And we move
to the South of France.
See-- No, there's plenty
of bicycling for you.
I think that's where they do
the Tour De France.
It is, yeah.
I mean, I just don't know
why I'm compromising
if it's my fantasy.
Because in my fantasy,
it's Maine, and you love it.
Because I'm never gonna
act like that,
even in your fantasy.
Nope, you-- You're doing
a great job at it
in my fantasy, right now.
Hey, idiot.
What did Erin want again?
A hot chocolate tea.
Gideon, you are a PhD candidate
studying America's diminishing
blue-collar work force?
North America.
And diminishing is a little
reductive, but, uh, sure.
That's the headline version.
Great.
Well, it will bring
a fresh, new perspective
to the warehouse.
FYI,
Wednesday through Friday,
I have a pretty full
teaching schedule.
Oh.
Cool.
We'll figure that out.
Also, FYI,
ah, I don't technically
have a hearing problem.
But sometimes,
when there's a lot of noises
occurring at the same time,
I'll hear them
as one big jumble.
Uh, again, it's not
that I can't hear.
Because that's false.
I can.
Um, I just can't distinguish
between everything I'm hearing.
Got it.
Duly noted.
You.
Coolest tank top I've ever seen.
Where did you get that?
- Made it.
- So cool.
What a cross section
we have here.
It's what I love
about interviewing.
I get to meet all these people
I wouldn't ordinarily
meet, or know, or even talk to.
Message in a bottle,
the postman--
Kevin Costner.
So...
I found this grease.
And then I remembered that
you thought it was a great idea.
You did say
it was a great idea.
I heard you say it.
So it's not the dumbest idea.
It's not the greatest one--
But the fact remains,
we gotta move these boxes.
And it's clear
we're not gonna carry them.
So sadly, it's the best idea
on the table.
Exactly.
Hey, I think we're ready
to get this--
- Yup.
- Is he okay?
He'll be fine.
Surprise!
Your new crew.
Would you just fire me, man?
Hey, why?
Because you didn't win
the lottery?
How am I supposed
to make you happy?
You wanna make me happy?
Huh?
- Yeah.
- Give me your job.
- Ah, what?
- I'll do it better than you.
I earned it.
I deserve it.
I got passed over,
God knows why.
Reasons I cannot
and will not understand.
The job was mine, Andy.
Everyone said it was mine.
Make me manager or fire me.
I'm not going
to give you my job.
It's my job!
I earned it!
And here's the thing.
You weren't even next in line.
I asked about you.
I saw your file.
You have a history
of being short with people,
and you hired Glen, your buddy,
to replace
you in the warehouse.
He was underqualified.
They saw that.
Also, Darryl, FYI,
I already told this to Andy,
but, uh, you should
probably know,
I technically don't have
a hearing problem.
It's just when there's
a lot of noises--
Nate. Please.
Thank you.
You have no business education.
You were going to take
classes under DeAngelo.
What happened with that?
He died.
He didn't die.
His brain died.
And my brain is very much alive.
And I'd be happy to give you
business classes.
How come you haven't asked me
about it?
What was--
What was the last--
I'm having a--
No part of this has anything
to do with you.
I didn't have time
because of my daughter.
Oh, but you had time
for a softball clinic.
And a mediterranean
cooking class.
Hey, I'm not gonna
tell you this stuff
if you're gonna throw it
back in my face!
Hey, here's the thing.
Jo saw something in you.
She loved you.
She gave you a shot,
and then you stopped pushing.
She noticed.
Okay.
Okay, what?
Okay, don't fire me.
Okay.
My future's not gonna
be determined
by seven
little white lotto balls.
It's gonna be determined
by two big black balls.
I control my destiny.
I do.
I'll put some guys on tonight.
The best of your bunch
and my bunch.
Tell you now, though.
It's gonna be mostly my bunch.
Yeah, that makes sense.
Okay, good.
All right.
Are they here?
What is going on?
Oh, hey, guys.
Why is the forklift
in the wall?
Why is the truck empty?
Uh, it's not totally empty.
Is that grease on my floor?
Okay.
I can see why you're angry.
You're coming into this cold.
But believe me,
a lot of thought went into this.
And did your brains tell you
to ruin these boxes with grease?
Okay, Darryl.
Listen, and then
you will understand.
The boxes were ruined
during our first trial testing.
So now, it's cool.
'Cause we found
another use for them.
Okay, all right.
That's-- Look.
All we were trying to do
is we thought we could come up
with a more efficient way
to do things.
And?
- And we did.
- I don't know.
Jim, tell them
what it's called.
That's all right.
No, Jim, tell them
what the name is.
Doesn't matter
Señor Loadenstein.
That's stupid.
Tell them why
it's called that, Jim.
That's okay.
We're good.
Nope, Jim. Tell us why
it's called señor Loadenstein.
Porque es muy rápido.
Okay.
You know what?
It's been a really busy day.
What do you say
we put all this away?
Let me see it.
It's, uh, in beta testing.
Let me see it!
Get the thing, go!
Lube it up.
Kevin, start mopping.
Uno, dos, tres.
Ah!
Yeah. I lost my client.
I already won the lottery.
I was born
in the US of A, baby.
And as backup,
I have a Swiss passport.
I would spend a lot of time
launching my true crime podcast,
the Flenderson Files.
Dum-bum-ba.
Flenderson Files.
We came to an agreement.
We're going to live
in a stunning, prewar brownstone
at the top of a mountain.
Right, the city
and country combined.
Just a subway stop away
are the best museums
in the world.
And I can fish right
from the window
of Pam's pottery studio.
We can * any time we want.
Just like now.
♪ schools are terrible, but, what
are you gonna do about that?
What are you gonna do?
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com