- Erin, hey.
- Yeah.
In two minutes, I want you to
come in to this meeting and
tell me that I have a
really important phone call.
I'm not gonna take it because
I want him to know how important
the meeting is to me.
Who's calling?
Nobody. Just say that...
Just make it up that I have a phone call
and I'm gonna refuse to take it.
- You're not gonna take it?
- Just make up a phone call.
- It's not real.
- Oh.
- Make it up.
- Okay.
And you come it and tell me.
It doesn't matter what it is.
You're not gonna get it though?
I'm not gonna take it.
And then he's gonna be like,
"wow, this is a really
important meeting."
Copy that.
Okay.
Okay, so tell me exactly
what kind of deal
you are getting right now,
and I'll tell you
how we can beat it.
Uh, well,
we've been going with a--
Andy, you have
a very important call.
I'm sorry, I'm with
a very important client.
It'll have to wait.
Are you sure?
It's really, really important.
There is nothing more important
to me right now
than this meeting.
Really?
Because your mother is dead.
Oh, my God.
I don't think she's dead.
She's dead.
She was hit by a bus.
She's not dead.
This is exactly the kind
of thing my mom pulls.
This isn't one of those times.
It's the police.
They said it's the worst
they've ever seen.
Andy, I'm really sorry
about your mother.
My deepest condolences.
Oh, you must take this call.
It's...
Yeah, um, line one?
Line two.
- Hi.
- It's Darryl.
Erin told me to pretend to be
a cop and say your mom died.
Oh...
Gosh...Thank you, officer.
Look, man, this is a bad idea.
Did she have
any last words or--
Really? That is messed up, man.
Oh, make sure that your client
gets the best deal possible.
You're a bad man,
Andrew Bernard.
That is so mom.
You know, this stuff
can come back to get you.
It's called karma.
Let me tell you something.
- You do not wanna--
- All right, well,
thank you, officer.
Erin, please hold
all my other calls.
Where were we?
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
- Hey, Cathy.
- Hi.
How's it going?
Everything make sense?
I think everything
is under control.
- Great.
- You should sit down.
Oh, no, I'm fine.
No, I should go
fill out my paperwork.
Okay.
Oh, that was just me.
Pregnant Pam.
And I make sounds
much worse than this.
Oh, we know.
I'm training a temp
to be my replacement
while I'm on maternity leave.
Oh, I should have
mentioned I'm pregnant.
You probably didn't notice,
because it's impossible to tell
because I'm so small.
But, yeah, I'm pregnant.
Oh, come on.
Hey, asking for a friend.
Do you happen to know
if that new girl is single?
Hmm, doubt it.
Yeah, me too.
- You doubt it?
- What's that?
Why do you doubt
that she's single?
Honestly, I have no idea.
I just figured
we'd save her from Ryan.
Right?
What are you doing
with my lunch?
I'm delivering it
from the fridge.
It's like a porno--
Hey, did anybody order a pizza?
It's not pizza.
Yeah, and we're not
about to make love.
I just thought maybe you'd wanna
eat lunch at your desk today
so that during lunch
we could go down
to the warehouse
and bang out a few tunes.
I like the sound of that.
Is Kevin in?
Uh, you tell me.
So word on the street is
she has a boyfriend.
Well, he's probably
a drug dealer.
That's the best way
to land a hot girlfriend.
You just, uh,
you get her hooked on blow.
It's gonna be nice
to have just like
a healthy, young, fit presence
in the middle of the office.
Yeah, aesthetically
speaking, strictly.
- She adds a nice presence.
- Good energy.
Yeah, it's gonna be nice
to have someone hot
at Pam's desk, huh?
Oh, no, no, no, no, not even.
I'm kidding!
Oh, my gosh.
You guys, she's obviously
super cute, I get it.
But I'd like to point out
that there's 50 pounds
more of me to love...
If that's your thing.
Pam, you look more beautiful
- now than ever.
- Radiant.
Thank you guys, really.
Thank you, very sweet.
Yeah, you have this sexy glow.
You know, it's one of
the most common fetishes.
Really, well, thank you all.
You know, it's not
just pregnant women
who don't get their due.
You know who's gorgeous?
Helen Mirren.
Yes.
Yes, have you seen her
in a bikini?
Amazing.
You know what would be
the hottest thing ever...
- Is a pregnant Helen Mirren.
- Oh!
Now we're talking!
Okay, okay.
No, no, no.
This is disgusting.
Do you realize
what you're saying?
The hottest thing ever
would be a 66-year-old
pregnant woman.
In this case, yes.
No!
There are universal
biological standards
of beauty and attraction.
And you are purposefully
celebrating the opposite of them
to mollycoddle
a pregnant woman.
- No, we're not.
- No...
Yes you are.
And another thing.
Helen Mirren was born
Helen Mironoff.
That's right,
you're fake salivating
over a Soviet-era Russian.
- Nice scatting, man.
- Thank you.
I think I said doop
instead of boop at one point.
Not bad, fellas.
You're better than you look.
Hey, screw you!
Hey, Robert.
Are we meeting early?
Just taking a stroll.
What exactly have I
stumbled upon here?
Well, we're all musicians,
and we play together sometimes.
You're a band.
Thank you.
We're called Kevin
And The Zits.
That was never agreed upon.
I miss being in a band.
Miss no more!
What do you play?
Join us.
I have a tambourine.
Tambourine?
You know I'm the CEO, right?
CEOs don't play tambourines.
Tambourines are for girlfriends.
I play a harmonica.
I think I have one in the car.
- Great!
- Nice.
Guys, Robert is gonna be a Zit.
Again, never agreed upon.
I had totally given up
on hanging out
with Robert California,
and now he wants to be
in our band.
And when you're in a
rock n' roll band with somebody,
you're bonded for life.
Usually that life
is short and tragic.
That's okay, right?
Yeah, even cooler.
We all got to go sometime.
Hey.
Helen Mirren.
Hot?
Yeah.
Super pretty.
Huh.
What about Cathy?
The temp?
- Yeah, do you think she's hot?
- Nope.
I'm not asking
if you're into her.
Just, objectively, do you
find her attractive?
And I'm telling you I don't.
You don't find
Cathy attractive?
No, I don't.
No, I'm not going to tell
my nine-months-pregnant wife
that I find her replacement
objectively attractive.
Just like I'm not going to
tell my two-year-old daughter
that violent video games
are objectively more fun.
It's true, but it doesn't
help anybody.
Look at her.
Even I want some fries
with that shake.
Okay.
Uh, I don't.
So are we good?
That's just absurd.
Yes, because she's hot, right?
Her breasts are large,
her waist is small,
her reproductive health
in ample evidence.
And facial symmetry--
Come on.
The thing about pregnancy is
people treat you differently.
Like you're a kid almost.
They lose all sense
of boundaries.
They start acting weird,
telling you things
that clearly aren't true.
I know it sounds nuts,
but I think Dwight
is the only one
who's telling me the truth.
Dwight, am I hot right now?
Why would I or anyone else
think that you're hot right now?
I can't impregnate you,
and that's the driving force
between male-female attraction.
What about before?
Was I attractive before?
Meh...You were at your most
attractive when you were 24
with a slight, gradual decline
and a steep drodrop-offoff when you
got pregnant for the first time.
Gradual recovery and, uh,
well, now, obviously,
you're at an all-time low.
Hmm.
I think Jim's lying to me about
not being attracted to Cathy.
You think Jim's lying?
That's so cute.
I know he's lying.
5 bucks if you can
get him to admit it.
Done.
I never touch a pregnant woman.
Yep, that's the Dwight I need.
If we're gonna work together
- we need some ground rules.
- Okay.
Rule one, our only loyalty
is to the truth.
I think so. Okay.
Rule two, we stop at nothing.
Well, what does that--
Is that... Okay.
Rule three,
don't fall in love.
Yep, good.
We're gonna bust this guy.
Honesty is very
important to me.
So important.
And then we will destroy
the man himself.
Let's just see how
we feel when we get there.
Well, you came to
the right person.
You have to follow
your intuition, Pam.
You don't want to end up
like Elin Nordegren.
Actually, what am I saying,
you wish you had her life--
No offense, Pam.
None taken.
What have you got?
It is called the matchmaker
test, and it is very powerful.
Basically we have Pam ask Jim
which of his friends
he would set up with Cathy.
If Jim picks
a really hot friend,
then we know that
he thinks that Cathy's hot.
Hmm.
♪ ♪
Hey, you found us!
You guys sound great, man.
Darryl, Andy, Kevin, this is
Curtis Dorough, local musician
and the officiate at my wedding.
Local musician?
Local legend.
I used to come hear you play
every week at The Deerhead.
Dude, you're on tv.
You're the sportscaster
on channel seven.
Go eagles!
You do that on tv.
You guys mind if they join us?
- Yeah!
- Absolutely!
Guys, I've got some
instruments right here.
Hey, why don't you
and me play those?
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Okay, this is awesome.
What should we play?
Maybe we should
warm up with some scales?
- Midnight Rambler?
- Yeah.
Midnigwhat?
♪ ♪
♪ have you heard about
the midnight rambler? ♪
♪ everybody got to go ♪
Hey, come on in, baby,
come on in.
♪ ♪
Yeah.
Hey, I was talking to Cathy.
Turns out she is single.
Oh, I stand corrected.
I thought it might be fun
to set her up with someone.
Any ideas?
Oh, you know who might be good?
Mike Tibbets.
- Mike Tibbets, really?
- Mm-hmm.
Hey, who's this
Mike Tibbets guy?
- What kind of car does he drive?
- Not his mom's car.
Yeah, 'cause his mom's car's
probably not a Nissan z.
Touche?
- Eww!
- Kelly, calm down.
I mean, I guess
he'd be okay with hair.
Okay you should see if
he'll get hair plugs.
I don't think Jim
cares about his hair.
Yeah, but I do Pam, okay.
It's called being a nice person.
I don't see
what's so ugly about him.
He's got the broad
face of a brewer.
- Jim's on to me.
- Hmm?
Yeah, Jim barely talks to Mike.
We had to go through like
two levels of friends
to even find his profile.
Jim picked someone
just unattractive enough to
shut me up without tipping it.
Just ugly enough
to have deniability.
Yep.
Mike Tibbets is like the most
boring-looking guy I know.
So if that was for
the matchmaker test,
I think I'm in the clear.
If that wasn't for
the matchmaker test, then...
Cathy, he's a really nice guy.
Well, Jim may be
lying with his words,
but he can't lie with his body.
I'm gonna write
something mean on his wall.
No, Kelly, don't.
The male reveals attraction
through unconscious
and involuntary physical signs.
The puffing of the chest,
mirroring,
increased blood flow
to the crotch.
I say we start there.
With the crotch?
With the crotch.
♪ ♪
Whoo!
Psst, we're not here.
- Who said that?
- Exactly.
How'd I this long triangle?
Okay, just shut it.
Is he puffing out his chest?
I can't tell.
It's unnaturally sunken.
Busted.
He just was mirroring.
Did you see that?
No. Maybe he just said
something funny.
Jim has no discernible
sense of humor, Pam.
You should know that.
I think he's just
making her laugh.
Time for me to find out.
Why's he making
her laugh so much?
Just gonna walk over here--
Whoa, I'm slipping and falling!
Oh, stumbling, I need
something to grab on to!
- Dwight!
- Are you okay?
I'm fine, I'm totally fine.
- Dwight!
- Yes?
- Wha-- Jim.
- Sorry about that.
Aw, cramp, I'm just--
Dwight!
Why?
I'm sorry,
I fell down, Mr. balance.
Leave.
Does your husband
have very soft erections?
Because if not, I just grabbed
a very soft penis for nothing.
Why was he making her
laugh so much?
Oh, hey. I'll just be a second.
- Yeah, take your time.
- Okay.
Oh, that line from Zoolander?
- Mm-hmm?
- It was from a deleted scene.
So we were both right.
Told you.
Um, do I hand in
my expense reports
to a particular accountant or--
Oscar, Cathy has a question.
Sorry, um,
I'll just go ask Oscar.
- Yeah?
- You okay?
Why won't you just admit
that she's attractive?
It's kind of annoying
that you won't say it.
Okay, what can I do
to make you believe me?
Well, Dwight had this idea,
and I thought it was
kind of crazy.
But maybe
that's where we are now.
She called it crazy?
Aw, man, that's insulting.
All I did was propose
a makeshift lie-detector test.
Monitoring his
blood pressure, pulse,
perspiration,
and breathing rate.
Yeah, it's nuts.
But I don't know
what else to do.
And she called it nuts?
Seriously, that was hot.
Feel like you and the newsman
- had a groove going.
- Mm-hmm.
Did you know that Lisa
toured with Chaka Khan?
Are you serious?
From Star Trek?
- Hey, you caught some of that?
- I caught it.
What, you don't like the blues?
I might enjoy seeing you guys
play the blues.
Well, we are playing.
We're all playing together.
These are our jam buddies.
It's a jam session.
We go where the music takes us.
I think the music
left without you.
- Come on.
- Stop shoving me.
Stop shoving me.
Stop grabbing my penis.
Grow up.
Take off your jacket
and take a seat.
When it lies, the human body
exhibits many telltale signs.
Really?
This could all go away
if you just tell me the truth.
Uh, are you all in line?
Why don't you go check out
the sympathy cards, old man?
Now I'm gonna ask you
just a few simple questions.
Wait for this to constrict.
Here we go.
Is your name Jim Halpert?
Si.
Wait, that's it?
That's the question
you're gonna ask him?
We have to start with
a baseline question
to establish what the truth is.
You have to share
the machine with others.
Well,
that's what they taught me
in my 19th century kindergarten.
Okay, Dwight, come on.
- You can go first.
- Thank you.
Jim, are you serious?
Oh, you know what? This reminds me.
Cece needs a new toothbrush.
Oh.
♪ ♪
Maybe we could
switch instruments.
Yeah.
'Cause, uh, my body's
starting to get bruised.
Yeah, maybe everyone move
one instrument to the right.
We had to leave because
of creative differences.
Yeah they kind of had
a specific sound
that didn't really
fit in with our thing.
Guys, this mean's they're
Kevin And The Zits now.
No, man...
We are.
- Well--
- No, no, no.
Okay, you're done.
I have a new heart, you know.
Do you really, tin man?
Okay, where were we?
No, I'm not worried.
Because this lie isn't
for me, it's for Pam.
And when she gets her body back
and her confidence back...
Yes, I will tell her the truth.
That I had feelings
for a co-worker today
that...
I haven't had in years.
In my defense,
he was grabbing my crotch
fairly aggressively
at the time.
Do you find
Cathy Simms attractive?
No.
Yep, he's lying.
Ah, see, was that so hard?
I am not lying.
- Really?
- Pam, are you really gonna
listen to his
stupid homemade test?
I would listen to
my homemade test,
because your husband
is definitely lying.
In fact, he's lied
about every question.
Even his name.
Who are you really?
- Wait, what?
- Look at the numbers.
Every single time,
it's come up 150 over 100.
Your husband
is a pathological liar.
Jim, you have
high blood pressure.
Oh, he is definitely
attracted to her.
Doesn't your dad have
high blood pressure?
Yeah, but I don't smoke.
When was the last time
you went to the doctor?
I don't know.
It's important
to go every month
and get your prostate checked.
You can do it at home by
yourself with your finger.
You just stick it--
- Okay.
- Dwight, stop.
I'm not kidding, I mean,
I need you to
take care of yourself.
What would we do if
something happened to you?
Okay, easy.
Trust me, I'm around
for the long-haul.
It's not really
your choice though, is it?
Death waits for no man.
- Okay.
- Come on, let's go.
I wanna call your doctor.
Doesn't it worry you
in the slightest
that Jim is not his real name?
Just go home.
It doesn't matter.
But--
Hey, Cece's toothbrush.
Thank you.
♪ Oh, baby, I love your way ♪
♪ every day ♪
♪ wanna be with you
night and day ♪
♪ day ♪
♪ oh, baby, I love your way ♪
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com