Christmas time is here!
Wow! Thanks, guys.
That sounded amazing.
Hi, I'm * Bernard and I am the
first office Santa ever
to make holiday wishes
come true.
Who's excited to get their
holiday wishes?
Holiday wishes...
What's that, Stanley?
We know exactly what holiday
you're referring to.
It is important to be mindful
of all belief systems
at our holiday party.
I've been here 18 years
and I've suffered through some
weird, thematic christmases.
A Honolulu Christmas,
a Pulp Fiction Christmas,
a Muslim Christmas,
Moroccan Christmas,
Mo Rocca Christmas.
I don't want it.
Christmas is Christmas
is Christmas is Christmas.
I got Stanley tickets to see
Lewis Black for his birthday.
Might not have been
the best idea.
I don't want no kwanzaa wreath.
I don't need
a dreidel in my face--
That's its own thing.
And who's that black Santa for?
I don't care.
I know Santa ain't black.
I could care less.
I want Christmas.
Just give me plain
baby Jesus lying in a manger
Christmas.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
What is the status on my wish?
Fulfilled.
Brought my bicycle
so I can be
your designated driver later
in the event
that you drink too much,
which is by no means required.
What about my wish
that we don't have to attend
meetings that degrade
our sense of adulthood?
That, I cannot do.
But I did get you
an acre of property on the moon.
Where, dark side or light side?
Light side.
Is it by
the sea of tranquility?
As a matter of fact, yes.
Directly adjacent.
- Beachfront.
- Thank you, Andy.
So whose wish is next?
Oh, what about Santa's wish?
My biggest wish is that
you all get along well
with Jessica.
Come on, guys, Jessica.
Jim, tell them who Jessica is.
She's not your grandmother,
is she?
Ugh, gam gam's name
is Ruth, Jim.
You should know.
I introduced you on
speaker phone that time.
Jessica is
my super serious girlfriend
who is seriously awesome
and seriously sexy.
Only thing that's not serious,
by the way,
our repartee.
That's great.
When you know, you know.
Hey, what's Ruth's deal, man?
Totally out of your league.
So, in summation, ho ho ho,
please be nice to Jessica,
and mistletoe
is not an excuse
for sexual assault.
And don't go near gam gam.
I love Jessica,
and I haven't even met her yet.
It's like, we don't even
need to meet, you know?
I already love you.
Stay home.
I just want you to know that
I will be mean to Jessica,
if you want me to be.
Oh, no, no, it's fine, Kelly.
It's really no problem.
I was already planning
on being mean to her.
That's okay,
I don't want you to do that.
Hello.
Merry Christmas, Erin.
Kelly, happy Pancha Ganapati.
Ew, what is that?
The five day hindu celebration
in December,
honoring the God Ganesh,
patron of the arts.
Cool.
- Hey, man.
- Hey, oh!
How you holding up?
Because of
your wife leaving you.
Kevin.
I actually appreciate
the human intimacy.
I feel like a kitten
being cradled by a gorilla.
Yeah.
It's been ten days
since I had sexual intercourse.
Well, you came to
the right place.
Ah.
It-- This party will
cheer you right up.
I hope so.
The corporate party
was wretched.
I am so tired of
the Black-Eyed Peas.
It's rock and roll for people
who don't like rock and roll.
It's rap for people
who don't like rap.
It's pop for people
who don't like pop.
Ah, heartbreaking.
Oh, thank you.
Well, I hate to have to take
my Santa hat off
and put on my hard ass hat,
but...This is serious.
It's come to my attention that
somebody who shall
remain nameless
wants to switch desk clumps.
Fine with me.
Jim can leave
any time he wants.
- Good-bye.
- Wasn't me.
It wasn't either of you.
Kathy wants to leave our clump?
Don't look.
Who it was is not important.
But she did say that
your constant pranking
and one-upsmanship
is driving her crazy.
She or he.
I just want to say
this is not my fault.
Okay, the weak
always bully the strong,
contrary to what you see
in the media.
I am always acting
in self-defense.
Occasionally
preemptive self-defense.
- Ow, what are you doing?
- Hey! Hey!
Respect the hat.
Pam never seemed to have
a problem with us.
All right.
I'm gonna speak in a language
you both understand,
Monet.
- What?
- What is?
Money.
You both have sizable Christmas
bonuses coming your way.
If I catch either of you
messing with the other,
I will give both bonuses
to the other person.
- Can't do that.
- No, absolutely not.
You need consequences.
Okay, I want you both
walking on eggshells.
Hi, I'm Jessica.
I'm looking for Andy.
Jessica, yes.
We don't say hi.
We hug.
I'm Erin.
- I-- Oof.
- Sorry.
I hope you feel really welcome.
- We all want you here.
- Oh.
My ex is meeting my sex.
Which is always scary.
You know?
And not just because
you think they might talk
about your penis.
That's just part of it.
Hey! Jess, Erin.
I hope you're not talking
about my penis.
- Hi.
Hey, everyone,
I want you to meet Jessica.
She is an assistant cross
country coach at Bryn Mawr.
Wow.
Erin, by the way,
amazing receptionist.
Oh, that's great.
Backbone of the office.
Which is funny, actually,
because my spine is a mess.
- What?
- Oh.
Scoliosis.
Had to wear a back brace
for three years,
but I never did.
Oh, no.
Oh, no, it's kicking in.
- Spontaneous...Scoliosis.
- Spontaneous scoliosis.
Oh.
This thing could
take your arm off,
your head off.
You know,
just exercise caution.
- Thank you.
- All right.
All right.
Oh, yeah, and, um...
There's a Christmas party
upstairs tonight
I wanted to tell you about.
Isn't that just for popsicles?
Popsicles?
Yeah, like, upstairs people.
'Cause you got
a stick up your butt.
See, I thought it was because
they're all so rich
they could eat popsicles
all the time.
What?
I-- In my--
Well, you should
definitely come.
The foreman always comes.
Plus it's fun,
you know, cookies,
smoked fish,
alcohol, people acting stupid.
You had me at "clookies."
I can't wait to find out
what they are.
What should I wear?
Oh, it's nice.
It's real nice.
People get dressed up.
I will look so handsome
for you, Darryl.
Ah...
I'm gonna s--
Dwight really wants my bonus.
He's trying to entrap me.
Oh, God, now I can't drink
at this thing.
I get really pranky
when I drink.
Erin, what can I get for you?
Uh, do you have cola?
Kirkland, if you have it.
Why would you come to a bar
and ask for a cola
when you can get some
from the kitchen?
Did some small part of you
want something
a little stronger?
Ryan, Kevin, Phyllis, Oscar,
come and take these shots.
- Oh.
- Yes.
Will do.
The fifth one is for you, Erin.
You can take it or leave it.
To take it would be to accept
that you're at a party
and you're an adult woman
with an adventurous spirit.
To leave it would be fine, too.
- One, two, three.
- Yes.
- Mm.
- Whoa.
- Hey, hey, nice.
- Whoo!
Jiminy Christmas!
Jiminy Christmas, indeed.
- Hit 'er up.
- Oh, yes.
- Whoo!
- Yeah.
Yeah, I just got my
replacement credit card.
Do you want the number--
Oh, it's 4-7-9-3
0-0-3-2-3-3-1-3.
The security code is 927.
Okay, great,
thank you very much.
Bye.
So Dwight did take the bait.
He used my credit card numbers
to send a $200 bouquet
of flowers...
To my wife.
From me.
Boom!
Look, it's Christmas,
so you're allowed--
Whoa, hello.
♪ ♪
I meant dressed up
compared to normal.
You usually dress
like a ghostbuster.
Okay.
I thought you'd wear a sweater.
Since when does a sweater
mean "dressed up"?
Am I your grandson?
Come on, stay, all right?
It's good for people
to get to know you.
As a contestant on
dancing with the stars, maybe.
I want my sugar-free cookie,
and then I want a sugar cookie.
And then I want my nap.
That's right.
Thank you.
She is remarkable.
- Edgy impressions.
- Thank you.
How many drinks
have you had tonight?
I can't be driving
everybody home.
- A thousand.
- Whoa!
Maybe you should take a break.
Maybe you should
mind your own business.
Just kidding.
Ah, I've been attacked!
Oh, my God.
Oh, someone put a porcupine
in my drawer.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, I was just
sitting here at my desk,
and I reached into my drawer
to grab my toothbrush
and some tooth powder,
and-- and all of a sudden,
I was attacked by this
bloodthirsty rabid creature.
I wonder, in this office,
who has access to a porcupine?
Or who in this office
knows that I have access
and is trying to set me up?
Hm, you know, this sounds a lot
like the premise of
my latest Chad Flenderman novel,
a murder for framing.
Chad Flenderman.
Just an easy-going black guy
who knows the streets,
yet he also went to Oxford.
So just as comfortable
on a motorcycle
as he is on Air Force One.
Oh, and he's also the world's
leading egyptologist.
Toby, nobody cares about
your sex-crazed black detective.
No, no, no, no, no,
women chase him.
H-he misses his wife.
Hello,
lacerated hand here, folks.
Nice try.
This is ridiculous.
Oh, is it really?
Two separate times
you have set me up to believe
that I was being recruited
by the CIA.
- Three times, actually.
- You see?
Jim, this has
your fingerprints all over it.
Andy, you've got to be
kidding me.
Fingerprints can be planted.
You know,
with a severed hand--
Do you think that's
what happened?
Do you think he used
a severed hand?
Okay, you know what,
why don't we just
call Animal Control?
You might want to run that
by Angela.
'Cause it's so cute.
No. Porcupines
don't have souls.
They're like dogs.
Yes, I'm calling
from Dunder Mifflin.
We have a very rabid porcupine
in our office.
Someone should come pick it up.
Come down right away.
Uh, I don't know, let me ask.
Uh, were you quilled?
Yes, I was quilled.
- And what's its name?
- Henrietta.
- Oops.
- What?
All right.
Get her out of here, Dwight.
♪ ♪
Guys, I just wanted to say--
Come here.
I am so happy
you guys are together.
Okay?
And you both have
such beautiful hair.
Thank you.
I hope you guys get married.
And who knows?
Maybe at the wedding
I meet someone.
Okay.
And later on tonight,
I hope I see you guys kiss.
Yay.
Okay, well, I'm gonna go do
another reverse spit.
That's how the cool kids
say "get a drink."
That's, uh, that's the girl
you dated.
Um, yeah,
she's not really like that.
It's...
No, she-- she seems fun.
- Yeah, uh, excuse me.
- Okay.
- Hey.
Have you had anything to eat
besides candy canes?
- Every Martini has an olive.
- Okay.
Maybe I should make you some
oatmeal or something.
I don't want to put you out,
but if someone's
making oatmeal,
I'll take an apple cinnamon
and a maple brown sugar
in one bowl with whole milk.
Hey, I never told you
my Christmas wish.
- Okay.
- It's about you.
That's not what it should be.
It should just be like
a trinket or something.
I'd said I wish
Jessica was dead.
You-- you mean you wish
she wasn't here or something.
I wish she was in a graveyard
under the ground
with worms
coming out of her mouth.
Hey, you know,
you can't say that, okay?
That's my girlfriend
that you're talking about.
You and I
are not together anymore.
You need to get over it.
Take your wish back.
Too late.
It's already been wished.
And you promised
it would come true.
You wrote it in an email!
So which one are you,
a murderer or a liar?
♪ ♪
- Hey...
- Hey.
So there was talk of oatmeal.
You know? Don't listen to
what anyone is saying.
You look like a...
A princess.
- Yeah.
- Thanks.
I was too embarrassed.
Hey, guys, sorry to interrupt.
I, uh, just found this
on my desk
and need to talk
to somebody about it.
Can you believe that?
- Is that Cece?
- Yes, it is.
- Oh, man.
- That's awful.
- Cece is Jim's daughter.
- Oh, my God.
How could somebody do that?
I know.
I mean, the way I see it is,
you can deface
any picture of me.
Any one. Pick one.
Not my kid, though.
Who did this?
- Do you know who did this?
- I don't...
I know who did this.
Dwight.
- Dwight?
- Yeah, he did.
- What? No.
- He should pay.
He is gonna pay.
This is fire-able.
- Okay.
- It's-- I mean--
Let me just see it
one more time.
You know what?
I know who my friends are now.
But I shouldn't have
got you involved.
Because the truth is,
I don't even really care
about this picture.
It's a little out of focus.
It was probably an accident,
right? Like...
That's no accident.
Right.
You're right.
So maybe it was me who did it.
By accident.
- What?
- I'll figure it out.
Get to the bottom of it.
Merry merry.
Enough of this garbage.
This is Christmas.
♪ ♪
Hiya!
Christmas!
You all right, Santa?
You know those movies
where two friends
are sleeping together
and it's like,
hey, can they stay friends?
Yes.
Do you think two friends
who are not sleeping together
can stay friends?
Two friends who are not
sleeping together?
Can they remain friends?
Yes, yeah.
No. I-- Mm, I don't know.
- Okay.
- By the way,
I'm not gonna mess with
your and Dwight's bonuses.
I think it's causing
more problems.
So just be yourselves,
have fun,
and try not to let it
affect your work.
All right.
I will definitely do that.
I'll tell Dwight.
You know what?
You're sitting and thinking.
And it's probably better
if it comes from me anyway.
Christmas miracles do happen.
Yes, they totally do.
You can't click on
these Kardashian links.
That's why you have
so many viruses.
Well, help me, okay?
I'm trying, but--
- You need to--
- Kelly.
- Yo.
- Game on.
On it.
I don't know what
I was thinking, it was awful.
Jessica, did you just fart?
And that is how it's done.
I would like another alcohol.
Let's you and I take a walk.
Oscar, you're in charge
of the bar.
What?
I haven't bartended in forever.
Oh, never considered myself
a mixologist.
Oh, this is daunting.
Uh, I need a mortar,
pestle, muddler.
Does anyone have
any chocolate shavings?
Your heart is broken.
So's mine.
And?
And what?
And do you have any advice
or anything...
Oh, my God.
To help me feel better?
I've been married thrice,
and each has ended in
an acrimonious divorce.
I'm not sure I'm the best person
to give love advice.
Oh.
I was hoping you were going
to make me feel better.
- When you do your make-up...
- Uh-huh?
How long does it take usually?
'Cause...
Um, it-- it depends.
Chad Flenderman's kryptonite--
Whoa, we got a real
Clarence Thomas here.
- I'll see you at home.
- Okay, great.
- Perfect.
- Bye.
I still don't get why
you can't just call her a cab
and pay for it.
I would, it just--
That wasn't the holiday wish.
Either he drives or I drive,
and now I'm drunk and mad.
- Okay, bye.
All right, come on, Meredith.
Bye.
Thank you, Santa.
You bet.
Thank God Erin's getting
a ride home with Robert,
'cause she is trashed.
And who better to drive her
home than Robert?
I mean,
what a standup guy, you know?
I mean, he's going
through a lot--
Separating from his wife,
showing up at the Christmas
party in a track suit
and a blazer.
- Let's go, let's go.
- I'm coming, I'm coming.
- Hang on.
All right.
- Whoa! My stuff!
- What? What is all that?
- It's my valuables!
- It's junk.
This is my treasures--
No, they're my treasures!
You're a hoarder.
My God!
No, I'm not!
I'm gonna sell it on eBay!
No, no, no, you be careful.
- Be careful!
- Ah! My Santa suit's stuck.
What are we gonna do with
all that bonus money,
Henrietta, huh?
Where are we?
This ain't my street.
Shh, shh, shh, shh.
Mmm, this is the posh
part of town, huh?
Oh, my God.
Wonder what a studio condo
would cost in this neighborhood.
Meredith, shut your
drunk hole right now.
Erin, it was great fun tonight.
Take a few aspirin,
drink a whole lot of water,
sleep in in the morning.
Thank you.
Good night.
What are you smiling for?
You thinking what I'm thinking?
I'm sure I am not.
Let's get you home.
Ow!
Take it easy!
Whoo.
Oh, man!
Ah, fell asleep.
Took a nap.
Hey, guys.
I feel refreshed now.
- How's it going?
- Dwight.
Took a little nap
right next to Jim's desk.
I feel so good right now.
Mmm, cookies.
What's everyone staring at?
Oh, man! I was supposed
to tell Dwight something.
Come on, Jim...
I got nothing.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com