Oh, look who's back
reporting for duty.
Hey, guys.
Hey.
Hey, Pam, ah!
Look what I can do now that
she's no longer pregnant.
Bam, bam, bam, bam.
Are you glad to be back?
Yeah-- Yeah, I mean I could
have used another week or three.
You still had eight weeks
more than we did.
Well, it's not exactly
a vacation.
- Hello, everyone.
- Hey.
Remember?
Little old me, hi.
What are you doing here?
You just had our baby.
Our collective,
Dunder Mifflin family baby.
Four days ago.
I wanted to come back to work.
Not everybody needs
some long, luxurious,
- Parisian maternity leave.
- What?
Damn, girl, your body.
Angela, you look amazing.
Really? I feel like
this big rhinoceros.
Anyway, I wanted to thank
you guys for covering for me,
so I made some treats.
I've got brownies
and magic cookie bars.
Nice.
Oh, Angela, those brownies
have walnuts in them
and I think Kevin's
allergic to walnuts.
You're allergic to walnuts,
right, Kevin?
Extremely, but I'm going
to fight through it.
Aw, it's okay, Angela.
I have mommy-brain too.
I don't know what that is, Pam.
I made a batch with no nuts,
special for you, Kevin.
- It's right here.
- Ooh.
When did you find time
to do all this?
Babies sleep a lot, Pam.
If you feed them enough.
Brownie, Pam?
Thank you.
Oh, my gosh, it's really good.
I wouldn't know,
I'm watching my weight.
So, you guys, you know what's
an even more useful treat
- is cash, so--
- Nope, it's over.
- We wanted to say thank you--
- Nope. Okay.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Dwight, I have
exciting news for you.
What?
I think you're
going to like it.
You can't tantalize me.
Oh, maybe I can.
I got an e-mail
from corporate
- okay.
- That told me that you got a promotion.
Right? I mean,
that's not the kind of thing
you want to read
quietly at your desk.
If you make me head of sales
one more time, I swear.
No, this is legit.
You will be assembling
a team to go to Tallahassee
for three weeks to develop and
launch a chain of Sabre stores.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
The Schrutes have a word
for when everything
in a man's life
comes together perfectly.
Perfectenschlag.
Right now, I am in it.
I finally get a chance
to prove myself to corporate.
I am assembling
a competent team.
I am likely a father.
I am so deep inside
of perfectenschlag right now.
And, just to be clear,
there is a second definition,
"perfect pork anus,"
which I don't mean.
And here's the fax for you.
And here's some facts for you.
Did you know frogs
can hear with their lungs?
And that flamingos can have
orgasms that last 30 minutes.
Love to learn.
Yeah, it's weird
that I said that last one.
So...
Uh, yeah, look at that.
- We're pin twins.
- Pin twins.
This is a gift from Jessica,
kind of a gag gift, really.
Real gifts come later.
Yeah, that's cute.
When I saw it in CVS,
it made me gag too.
For awhile there, I thought
something would change,
but, nope,
Andy's still with Jessica.
They even carpool
together most days.
I don't know, I wouldn't mind
carpooling every day with Andy.
But I wouldn't want to spend
that much time with Jessica.
What do we have here?
Val knit me a beanie.
But I can't tell if it's a
"we're just friends" beanie
or a "I'm hot, you're hot,
let's get it popping" beanie.
So I'm going to up the ante,
give her
a clearly romantic gift.
And we'll get
to the meaning of the beanie.
Pam, pack up your
postnatal swimwear,
make it a one-piece,
or this offer is rescinded,
and join me for a fantastic
barbecue, one week from today,
in Tallahassee, Florida,
where I'm going to be living
for the next three weeks.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
I'll fly anywhere
for some good barbecue.
Ooh, me three.
No plus-ones.
This is for competent
workers only.
And don't worry about the cost,
Sabre is footing the bill.
Does this have anything
to do with
what you were talking
to Andy about?
God, you're such a spy.
Notice anything
different about me?
You're wearing the beanie.
You like it?
Super comfortable,
like sweatpants for my head.
I love it too, Val.
It's really itchy,
but to be fair,
my head is constantly itching.
So I can't really
peg it on the hat.
Wow, it's like
the nation of islam down here.
I like to knit.
Don't hate.
And who's that for?
Oh, this is a gift
for my man, Nate, here.
- What?
- Yeah.
Darryl, you shouldn't have.
- Can I open it?
- No, no, no, maybe just--
Ah, I can't wait,
I'm sorry, I'm too excited.
Darryl.
Wow, those are really nice.
- They're so elegant.
- Cashmere.
How'd you know?
Just a hunch.
Your gift is on the way.
Can't wait.
I'm glad you're in my life,
happy Valentine's day.
Oh, Darryl.
I am glad to be
in your life too.
Your card is more beautiful
than the gloves.
My first task as Special
Project Manager, Dwight Schrute?
Assembling a crack team.
I need people who are loyal.
People who will help me
get an inroad
with the gay-hispanic
community.
People who won't be missed.
- We don't need idiots.
- This hurts.
Good for nothings.
Meth-heads.
Or--
What's your name?
Kathy.
I just got a text
from Robert California
that says,
"bring your clubs to Florida."
Why?
Does he think
you're going to Florida?
I hope not,
because I am not going.
Two question marks.
No, just do one.
Two question marks
is kind of aggressive.
You know, it's like,
"wh-- what?"
Just do one.
You want to take
Darryl, Phyllis,
- Toby, Angela, and Oscar?
- Yes.
Can I interest you
in someone less essential?
Like a--
A Creed or a Meredith perhaps?
- Oh, my God.
- They're not expendable,
exactly, I just can't--
I can't think of the word
I'm trying to find.
Are you kidding me?
I'm supposed to get on an
airplane with those nincompoops?
We'd never
make it off the runway.
All right, look, I got to keep
this office functioning
somehow, so--
I have put together a list.
Here's your team.
Darryl and Phyllis,
you can have.
But you're also taking
Kathy, Kelly, and Kevin.
Oh, God.
You have your team.
Kevin? Kelly? Kathy?
Andy just gave me
a chain with three weak links.
Have you ever tried to use
a chain with three weak links?
I have, and now I no longer
own an arctic wolf.
Well, let's hear it.
"Robert, hey!"
Exclamation point.
I like it so far.
"Got your text, awesome idea.
Let's hit the links
the next time you're in PA."
Dash, JH.
It's perfect.
You emphasized the golf,
completely omit the Florida.
Yeah, it's a golf text.
Total golf text, send it.
Done--
Wait, I just feel weird.
I should just call him.
You want to call someone
that texted you?
Do you want to drive them away?
I mean--?
This is Darryl.
Oh, sorry, I asked
for the main shipping number.
I just need the address
for the warehouse.
I want to send my girlfriend
some flowers.
Your girlfriend?
Is your girlfriend Val?
Yeah, do you know her?
We're friends, we're friends.
Cool. Uh, so can I get
that address or--?
Yeah, yeah, sorry,
I'm just looking for a pen.
Why do you need a pen?
Back off.
I got my reasons.
May I have
your attention, please?
Could Kathy, Phyllis, Darryl,
Kevin, and Kelly please
join me in the conference room
immediately.
- Why?
- Oh, no big deal.
It's just that you five
have been deemed most deserving
of a three-week,
all expenses paid business trip
to Tallahassee, Florida.
Hell, yeah.
What?
Oh, I'm sorry, Stanley.
I can't share any more
details with you.
You see, Andy rejected you.
Wait, Kathy gets to go?
Why does she even
still work here?
Pam is back.
It just feels like
a slap in the face.
I can understand your pain
and your rage,
but you know what?
Andy is an honorable man,
let us not question
his choices.
I'm sure he had his reasons.
We're not questioning
his reasons.
I just want to know
what they are.
I know, you and me both,
brother.
It seemed kind of random to me,
but he was pretty clear
on who he thought
truly deserved
this boondoggle of a lifetime.
Well, he nailed it.
Because I do deserve
a vacation.
Sometimes Batman's
got to take off his cape.
Good point,
but we're going to be working
pretty hard until 5:00 P.M.
After that, it's gonna be
beach volleyball,
trips to Cape Canaveral,
and sea-kayaking
with Gloria Estefan.
What were the criteria
for going?
It might be innate goodness
versus innate badness.
But there's an easy way
to find out.
Oh, Andy,
got a few questions for you.
Moshi moshi.
Uh, the Florida picks got out,
and people were just
kind of curious
as to why they weren't picked,
and maybe you could
just clarify.
Uh, well, the deliberations
were confidential,
so I feel like
we should respect that.
Respect it?
You're trying to tell me
Kevin Malone
deserves more
than Stanley Hudson?
Hey.
Okay, it's obvious
that Andy picked the people
that are least important
to the office.
Important?
Oh, because you and your
enormous monster-baby
are so important to the branch.
My baby is not a monster.
Hey, be proud of your
enormous monster-baby.
I was once
an enormous monster-baby.
Guys, guys, guys,
come on, seriously?
We cannot let this trip
cause this kind of rift, guys.
Stop calling us "guys."
I use the word "guys"
a lot when I'm nervous.
Guys.
- Guys, guys, guys.
- Andy, please.
Stop it, Andy.
- Dudes--
- Andy.
The dudes
who are going to Florida
were picked by Dwight and me.
Okay, hey, I specifically
remember that there were
a lot of other people
I thought should be considered.
If anybody's going
to Florida, it should be me.
Every shirt that I have
that isn't a work shirt
is a Tommy Bahama.
I'm the only person in this
office who watches Burn Notice.
Okay, I did not realize
that so many of you
wanted to go so badly.
So if you feel like
you have a very good reason
to go to Florida,
I'm happy to hear you out.
Great idea.
So why doesn't everyone just
take the next five to six hours,
come up with a statement
on why you feel you deserve
to go to Florida, and Andy
and I will listen to it.
No, that is a ridiculous
waste of time.
For you, maybe.
- Five to six hours?
- Three to four hours.
- No, no, no, no.
- Just two to three hours--
come up with a statement
over the next hour.
30 minutes.
I'm out.
Okay, read it back to me.
"Robert, great offer."
Wish I could hit the links
with you in Florida,
but a father of a newborn
really should be helping out
"his wife
any chance he gets."
Good, doesn't sound pushy.
You're just stating a fact.
Absolutely.
Works for me.
- Okay, sending.
- Well done.
And we managed to kill
the entire morning.
We really did.
He responded "LOL."
I have a new swimsuit
I need to break in.
I already picked my team.
Darryl, Oscar, Angela,
Phyllis, and Toby.
And that is the team
that I am taking.
What's that?
It's not up to me?
I only have influence?
Well, that's all
Baltzer Glattfielder had,
and now no one
eats owls for Thanksgiving.
You have two young,
dynamic people in this office
who know trends,
who know youth.
That's myself and Kelly Kapoor.
You need one of us there.
Or both.
Not both.
Just one. Me.
Or if not me, Kelly.
Ideally, me.
Again, youth knowledge.
That's what you get
when you put Ryan Howard
on your Special Project Team.
Or Kelly Kapoor.
Again, not both. Thanks.
Very impressive.
He put a lot of work into that.
Powerpoints are the peacocks
of the business world.
All show, no meat.
Because I feel like
that I'm at a place
with my gambling rehab
that I can finally start
going to dog racing again.
You know, just sitting,
watching, enjoying the sport.
Maybe putting down a few
dollars, if there's, like,
a crazy mismatch or something.
Okay, thank you, Kevin.
We'll let you know.
- Thank you.
- When do we leave?
Thank you.
It has been a long,
lonely winter.
Wow, seasonal affective
disorder, aka, "SAD."
That sounds like
a very real thing, Toby.
It is real.
Thank you for saying that.
Yeah, wow, it's almost like
we're not all experiencing
the same winter.
"Florida Stanley" smiles.
"Florida Stanley"
is happy to go to work.
"Florida Stanley" is who
you want on your Florida team.
It's still, well--
Hey, guys, any spots left?
Erin, you want
to go to Tallahassee?
I do.
I really do.
I think it would be
a nice way to clear my head.
You know, I don't think
it's a good idea for you
to clear your head anymore
than it has been already.
I think you need a workplace
where the burdens
of everyday life keep you
tethered to reality.
Either or.
But if you can find someone
to fill in, I would love to go.
Well, it wouldn't be hard
to find someone to fill in.
Really?
Oh, great, good.
Now, is it too dark to say
that Cece's having an operation?
I think you
need to go to Florida.
I think you're right.
It's only for three weeks.
You know, with my mom and sister
at the house it'll be--
- A total nightmare.
- I was going to say,
"good, because I'll have
all the help I need."
Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
They're incredibly helpful.
You're lucky to have them.
I mean, with them there,
you probably
won't even know I'm gone.
Exactly.
Well--
No, no, absolutely not.
You are not going.
Over my dead body, no.
Tunes, I'm really sorry.
You're too essential
to the operation here.
I can't let you go.
I wouldn't say that.
That's a bit much.
You know, Dwight,
if you didn't want me to go,
the smart move would be
to tell Andy
that I actually am
essential to the operation.
That way I couldn't go.
Jim is essential to--
Hold on, just want
to get it on camera.
Andy,
Jim is just too ess--
Essential.
This is stupid.
Cut.
All right, I'm going
to pack my trunks.
He doesn't even want to go.
Well, I got a text from RC
inviting me to come down,
so I think that's going
to make us roommates.
Oh, my God.
Hey, quick question.
Do you shower at night
or do you shower in the morning?
Because I want to shower
when you're showering
to save some water.
Okay, listen up, everyone.
Here's who's going to Florida.
- Kathy.
- What?
- Stanley.
- No.
- Ryan.
- Erin.
- Fuck.
And Jim.
You got to be
fucking kidding me.
Okay, okay.
Florida group,
welcome to the team.
Aah!
Let's go.
Step it up, you runts.
Infants, let's move.
Why is it so hot in here?
Hot?
What are you talking about?
This is a nice,
temperate, Florida morning.
85 degrees, 73% humidity.
This is the exact environment
that you will be facing
for the next three weeks
of your life.
Welcome to Special Projects
Orientation.
The next three weeks
of your life
are going to be the most
miserable you've ever faced.
They're going to be hard,
they're going to be dirty.
You're going to wish
you were dead.
But.
But?
There's no buts.
That's it,
you'll wish you were dead.
You seem a little disturbed,
do you want to stay here?
No, no, I want to go.
Because if any of you
would prefer to stay here,
all you need to do
is ring this bell.
Is that the buzzer from Taboo?
- Shut up, maggot!
- It is.
You don't want to go,
ring the bell.
Ring it, ring it.
How many of you have seen
the documentary Deliverance?
How did a mosquito get in here?
I released 300 mosquitoes
into the conference room.
Just temporarily.
When I'm done, the frogs will
take care of the mosquitoes.
Yes, then he brushes your soft,
supple cheeks
with his worn,
leathery hands and says,
"I'm going to make you
the seventh Mrs. Rosenblatt."
Unless you ring the bell,
ring it.
- No.
- Ring the bell.
You want to spend
the rest of your life
changing your husband's
colostomy bags?
Huh, do you?
Ring it. Ah.
What was that?
Mosquito.
Orientation's over.
Oh, Darryl, hey.
Hey, what's up?
You called?
Yeah, you know,
I felt really terrible
that you got me
these lovely gloves
and I didn't get you anything.
It's cool, really.
No, it's anything but cool.
Now, I haven't
really had time to go out
and buy you anything,
but here goes.
- "This coupon entitles you to
one free tickle-monster attack."
Yeah, they're Nate coupons,
or "Na-pons,"
and they're all different.
Cash that one in and I will
bring you a stick of gum.
Any time, any place.
I'll find you.
Thanks.
Nice flowers.
Thanks, they're from my mom.
- Your mom?
- Yeah.
Oh, so I guess
that was your mom
who called me earlier
looking for the address?
Real deep-voiced woman.
Yeah, that's her.
She said her name
was Brandon, I think.
Your mom's name is Brandon?
Yeah, Darryl,
my mom's name is Brandon.
I guess I figured out
where I stand.
This is a love beanie.
Okay, Florida Team,
let's reconvene.
I'm going to Florida
and I'm not coming back.
So Sabre has setup
a conference room for our use
while we're at corporate.
So what is this
Special Project?
Basically, Sabre has
tasked us with helping them
branch into
the retail marketplace.
They want to setup their own
version of an Apple Store.
That sounds awesome.
It did, it did.
You know what might
be great is if instead
of a genius bar,
we have a lounge area
where people can ask questions
about the product
with other customers
who liked it.
Yeah, and they should
have a place where people
can check their computers
or printers before they see you
so you don't have
to carry it around like a dope.
Like a coat check.
Oh, don't write it down
unless you like it.
Oh, I like it.
It seems to me
that the Apple Store
is kind of like a party,
so I think our question is,
"how do we make this
a better party?"
No, we sell business tools,
and the stores
need to reflect that.
They need to be all business.
Let all the other stores
look like a toy store.
Right, think different
from Apple.
Dwight, is now
a good time to go over
what you expect of us?
Yes.
What are my expectations
for the group?
I had been given
the responsibility
to manage Stanley,
a solid player.
Ryan, who is capable
of surprises.
Erin, an excellent follower.
And Kathy, a probably not
totally useless enigma.
And, well, Jim.
Under the right manager,
that's not a bad team.
Perfectenschlag.
I don't know how I'm going
to live here without you.
Me neither.
Hey, will you put this coat
on my chair?
I just realized I'm not
going to need it down there.
Yes, I will take your coat
and I will keep it with me.
And I will sleep with it,
because it smells like you.
No, no, no, no,
just put it on my chair.
- All right.
- Bye.
Bye.
- Call me when you land.
- I will.
Safe travels.
Goodbye.
For a very, very long time.
Hmm?
Okay.
It's only three weeks.
All expenses paid.
Yeah, Jim's going to be there.
That marriage is not good.
Nobody knows better than me.
Definitely we will.
It's three weeks in Tallahassee.
What else is there to do?
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com