Hey, Angela.
Do you wanna see a picture of Philip
wearing those little booties you got us?
So cute.
Hey, you guys wanna see a picture of *?
He *
is all he wants to do.
Oscar thinks having a dog
is just like having a baby.
News flash,
if you didn't carry it around
in your belly for nine months,
it isn't your kid.
Exactly.
Unless you adopted, of course.
That is where we disagree.
Hey, are your little dudes
crawling yet?
No, three-month-old humans
don't do that.
My Philip is crawling.
- Angela is such a liar.
- It's maddening.
Exactly.
That's just like crate training.
All night long.
[Chuckles]
Well, count yourself lucky.
Wait until you have two.
That's two sleep schedules,
two naps that don't coincide.
I mean,
you'll never sleep again.
No one said,
"you must have two."
Like her genes
are so important.
The world just needs
more Pam-Jim DNA.
- Thank you, no.
- No, thank you.
[Giggles, cackles]
Check this out.
My brother just got
a new sailboat.
He has no idea
what he just got himself into.
There's nothing harder
than taking care of a boat.
Am I right?
Angela and Pam:
Unbelievable!
Un-be-lie-va-ble.
[Cheerful music]
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
It is the end of the day.
It is the end of the week.
We managed
to fill 40 hours somehow.
That's not bad, is it?
- [Laughs] Pretty good.
- That's great.
Well, thank you.
This is very helpful feedback.
Dwight, I am still
not ready to name a VP.
That's not
what I was gonna ask.
Gosh, jump to conclusions.
Come on, I know, you've got
so much on your plate.
Right now, you're like,
"oh, what's more important?
"Dwight's question,
figure out who's the VP?
Dwight, VP.
Dwight, VP."
Dwight, VP...
I can't be hypnotized, Dwight.
I tried it,
I ended up smoking more.
Can we at least eliminate those
that are not in the running?
Free them up to focus
more completely on the menial.
Like stacking
and sorting, or--
Catching butterflies.
That's a hobby
unless it's for food.
- Theater.
- Waste of time.
- Dragging.
- That's just a verb.
Dragging sticks.
Yes, nice, perfect.
Dragging sticks--
All right, I'm gonna eliminate
three people right now, okay?
Just--
You three, no.
Not good enough.
[Clicks tongue]
English peoples' main use today
is judging American talent.
[British accent]
You're crap. You're wonderful.
They're-- they're mean,
but they're incisive.
Everyone meet
in the hotel bar at 7:00.
I'm not allowed
to say it's mandatory,
so let's just call it
"compulsory."
I'll be there at 6:00.
Ugh, we're gonna have one of
those crazy nights, aren't we?
Maybe we'll see
the real "Talla-nasty"
we've been hearing
so much about.
- "Talla-nasty," very clever.
- Thank you.
Wait, wait, you think
she invented "Talla-nasty"?
[Chuckles] No, no, no, no...
Uh-uh.
Cathy? It's been great.
Fun, normal.
I thought I was gonna be hanging
out with Stanley on this trip,
but he's turned out to be
kind of a loose cannon.
My friend and I are new
here in Tallahassee.
Would you like
to get a cocktail?
Maybe go out
for a little dancing.
Beautiful day, no?
Okay, everybody.
5:00. Workday is over.
Put your pencils down.
And...
Bring 'em back up
because now
the late-night work jam begins.
Yes, the conference room
is set up.
I've got pens, I've got paper,
I've got a whiteboard.
- We are good to go!
- Say what?
We are good to go!
- We're good to go!
- Stop it. Stop it.
- Stop.
- Say--
- Andy.
Tonight we're staying late
to service the accounts
of the people who went
on the Florida trip.
Yes, of course,
we could've just been
doing this the whole time,
but someone dropped the ball.
Ball droppings
can be beautiful.
For example, when it
turns an awkward soprano
into a rich, full tenor.
Jason Bourne
would kick Bond's ass.
has no support staff.
His own government's
out to get him.
Genghis Khan
could take 'em both down
'cause he's not
afraid to kill children.
What?
It's true. He--
He would-- He would
eviscerate babies
and hang them from poles
outside of the villages.
Okay, drinking game.
Count of three, take three sips.
That's a stupid game.
I got a great drinking game.
Okay, everyone
empty your pockets.
Whoever has
the most seeds is the king,
whoever has the least buttons
is the hunchback.
What happens
if you're the hunchback?
- Oh, you get kicked.
- How many buttons do you have?
40. Always.
- Can I see?
- Sure.
So I get to kick you now.
No, they're not transferable
just 'cause I handed 'em to you.
Well, that's how
I played it in college.
- College rules. [Kicks]
- Aah!
And he lost
at his own lame game.
Ooh, double meaning.
The game was lame,
and now he's lame from the kick.
Quick wit.
Thank you.
I'll have a glass of
your oakiest chardonnay, please.
And I will have a waffle
with your mapliest syrup.
Sorry, no waffles.
Oh, okay.
Just forget it, then.
Forget it.
A waffle?
A hotel waffle.
I know what I want to eat.
- Is that crazy?
- No.
I'm moving down here, you know.
Oh.
No, I didn't know.
I'm young, and I can.
And if I can't,
I'm still pretty young.
I guess I'll always be young.
You come with me.
We're gonna get you that waffle.
Why would Erin confide in me
that she's staying
here in Florida
if she didn't want me
to make some sort of last-ditch,
nothing-to-lose,
Kelly ka-who run at her?
- Hey.
- Watson Carpet And Tile.
- One order.
Order reference
number 00983-126.
Eight cases,
bright white inkjet.
- Paid.
- I'm dying!
- Processed.
- And delivered.
Sometimes I get so bored
I just want to scream,
and then sometimes
I actually do scream.
I just sort of feel out
what the situation calls for.
- I will be right back.
- I will be here.
Hey, I see what you're doing.
It's futile.
The VP position is mine.
Oh, please.
You're through.
She's going to give it to me,
as I'm giving it to her tonight.
The cowgirl
has chosen her saddle.
[Clicks tongue, whinnies]
Well, saddles...
Sometimes fall off,
especially if you don't
properly cinch the girth.
What?
That's a joke, right?
You see the way
she's all over me.
If anyone's having sex
with g for personal gain,
it's me,
and I'm not joking at all.
If you don't tighten
your saddle, you may fall off.
Who is ready for dinner?
"Oh, I bet it's pizza or tacos
or something stupid."
No.
[Claps]
I went south of the border
for this.
And then I went south
of that border.
And we have ourselves...
[Jamaican accent]
A Jamaican feast, man.
- Ooh.
- Ugh.
If I wanted Jamaican food,
I'd just hire a bunch
of bodyguards and go there.
Additional trivia factoid,
this food comes
to us through Val.
And our server is none other
than Brandon, her "boyf."
- Hey.
- How you doing, Val?
- Hey, babe.
Jamaican, huh?
I just read about
the elections down there.
Crazy stuff.
Oh, no, I'm not
actually Jamaican.
- Terrific.
- What's up, man? I'm Darryl.
Darryl, I heard about you.
You doing good?
- Oh, yeah.
- Must be doing real good
since you're fucking
my girlfriend.
- Whoa.
Dude, you didn't tell me
you were fucking Val.
High five.
I'm not sleeping
with your girlfriend.
Brandon, what the hell
are you talking about?
Don't play dumb with me.
I know what's up.
Honey, I am not
sleeping with--
Hey!
Hey...
Let's get back to the food.
Brandon tell us about
these delicious-looking goops.
Hope you all like goat.
Goat.
- Blow in my ear.
- All right.
Like I'm on the beach.
- [Blows]
- Oh.
[Imitates seagull calls]
Seagull.
[Cawing]
And-- and a wave crashing.
A wave crashing.
[Both imitate waves]
Oh, that is lovely.
All right. That's gonna
do it for me tonight.
Have a lovely evening.
[Sports commentator
speaks indistinctly]
[Knock at door]
- Hey, how's it going?
- Hey, uh, good.
Uh, the heating system though
in my room is all messed up.
It's, like,
90 degrees in there.
Maintenance is working on it.
Can I hang out in here?
Uh...Yeah, I'm just
watching basketball.
- Okay, yeah.
- Okay.
Cool.
Is this March Madness?
I love March Madness.
Oh, no, that's not this
'cause that's in March.
Uh, this is just the NBA.
Professional.
Miami Heat, actually.
So--
- Lebron James.
- Yes, nice.
Good word association.
[Giggles]
[Crowd cheers on TV]
Impressive.
Oh, please,
anyone can tie a knot.
The real skill
is in untying it.
Mm...
- Thornwood Wholesalers.
- One order.
I read the text
you sent to Val, man.
That's messed up.
- Is this spicy?
- No, baby girl.
It would be messed up
if I didn't find anything,
but I did, so--
I'm pretty sure
if Darryl sent Val a text,
it was about some
paper emergency or something.
At midnight?
- Yeah.
- It happens.
Like a hospital needs
more napkins for surgery--
Guys, we're not gonna
settle anything this way.
I think we just
need to be grown-ups here.
Thank you.
I think we're gonna
need to hear those texts.
Kelly, remember how
you wanted to go home before?
No. There's no way
in hell I'm leaving.
Something interesting
is happening here
for once in my life.
I am staying here.
Darryl, read the texts.
[Knock at door]
Yup.
Coming.
All right.
My mini bar
is oddly out of rum.
- We have plenty.
- Oh, hello.
[Chuckles]
Do you want
to watch the game with us?
We're watching a game.
The Heat game. Just a game.
Got it.
Good night.
Careful, Jim.
It gets easier and easier.
- No, no, no, Stanley.
- Mm-hmm.
- Stanley.
- Uh-huh.
Stanley.
All right, hey.
You know what?
Just bring back those bottles!
Whoa.
The lights are still on.
Yeah, they keep them on
'cause it's less expensive
than turning them on and off.
I like how guys
just know stuff all the time.
Girls know
a lot of stuff too, okay?
And nobody knows more than you.
Especially me.
[Gasps] Hello, waffle iron.
Hello.
What do we have here?
Okay, so the recipe says
we need a mixing bowl...
- Right.
- A measuring cup...
Got that.
[Metallic thud]
[Whispers] Get down.
It's the fuzz.
Shh! Do you want us
to get scolded?
Shut your beautiful,
beautiful mouth, please.
[Sink running]
"I got too much ice cream.
You want some?"
- "Gettin' my fry on."
- Boring.
Uh,
"the moon is huge tonight."
Ooh, gosh,
the moon one's damning.
Yeah, sorry.
- That's regular text talk.
- You forgot one.
"You're such
a great friend."
With the dots.
"You're such a great friend,"
dot, dot, dot, dot, dot.
- Oh, ooh.
- Five dots, Darryl?
Are you kidding me?
Okay, 'cause three dots
means "to be continued,"
four dots is a typo,
but five dots means,
"whoa, do not make me say
what I want to say, baby,
but if I did,
it would blow your mind."
Dot, dot, dot, dot, dot.
All: - Oh...
- See? Yes.
Thank you, sister.
Brandon, Darryl and me?
That's ridiculous, right?
Yeah.
Totally crazy.
Puts me in an insane asylum
just thinking about it.
I'm stranded
on Shutter Island over here.
You look like Ed Harris.
If they stretched him
a little bit.
You want to see a picture
of me trapped under a tree?
[Cell phone rings]
Ah...
Excuse me.
What?
Not now. I'm busy.
I'm sorry.
I thought you'd want to know
that I saw a bedbug in my room.
But never mind.
Sorry to interrupt.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Bedbugs?
Oh, no.
Freak, I need a favor.
Well, then you have
to call me by my name.
Gabriel Susan Lewis.
I gotta be gone
for a few minutes.
You make sure that Packer
does not sleep with Nellie.
What's in it for GSL?
You really want
Packer as your boss?
Got it.
If Jim has bedbugs,
that means they're everywhere.
I can't risk them
coming back to Schrute Farms.
Our biggest attraction
is our 200-year-old mattresses.
- Where did you see it?
- In the bed.
I haven't seen anything.
We gotta find it
before it eggs.
- Argh!
- Jeez!
Describe it.
Brown, shiny, painful bite.
Could be a bat weevil.
Describe its mood.
Did it seem sleepy?
Stressed, but to be fair,
it was a tense situation.
Fair enough,
but after it bit you,
did it run away fearful,
or did it walk away
smug, self-assured?
So smug.
Like he thought
it was funny, like this.
- Pssh. That's a bedbug.
- Yeah.
- Everything's a joke.
- I know.
- Check your hair.
- Ow.
God, oh. So greasy.
You should just shave all this.
- Just check it.
- You are clean.
Okay...
One thing a bedbug thrives on
is heat and carbon dioxide.
I am gonna generate myself
into a human trap.
When I jump into the bed,
you are gonna cover me
with the sheet immediately.
And then we'll see
who's laughing.
- All right.
- [Dastardly laugh]
Yeah.
Cover me!
- Is this really necessary?
- He knows what he's doing.
Let the bedbugs bite!
Ugh, God, I feel so gross.
I have to go take a shower.
All right,
then I will catch you later.
- What do we do now?
- We wait.
[Shower starts]
Come to papa.
Oh.
- [Speaking softly]
- Mm-hmm.
[Spraying]
I don't know, Dwight, I think
maybe you should check again.
Nope, I wasn't bitten.
Okay, well, maybe it's
not warm enough in here.
Oh, it's plenty warm,
and I was farting continuously
under the sheet,
creating a kind
of greenhouse effect.
- Come on.
- If there were any in here,
they would've embedded
themselves in me.
You know what?
Maybe they just ate.
No, you're good.
Clean bill of health.
Besides, I got to get
back downstairs.
I left Packer alone
with Nellie for way too long.
Okay, well, they're fine.
They're adults.
No, that's the problem.
Packer is trying to bed Nellie
for the VP job
unless I do it first.
Is that really
how you want to get this job?
Such a chorus girl.
Okay, Dwight...
Dwight...
Dwight, Dwight, Dwight.
Uh...
Is crazy gone?
[Rock and roll music]
[Laughs]
[Vomits]
Oh.
They don't make these cords
in boot cut anymore.
Oh.
Pathetic, huh?
A real man swallows his vomit
when a lady is present.
Hey.
Yes, one with chocolate,
one with vanilla.
Okay, cool.
Thanks.
- I know, I'm a pig, right?
- Hmm? No.
[Giggles] Wait, this is why
I exercise like a fiend. Feel.
- Seriously.
- Okay, all right.
I'm really sorry, uh,
I just have to say it.
I'm-- I'm married.
I'm very happily married.
Oh, my God!
What are you thinking?
Um...
I mean--
I know that you're married.
I sat at your wife's desk.
How little do you think of me?
I'm sorry,
I feel like maybe I'm-- I'm--
I misread things.
Okay.
Let's just go back to watching.
Can you without running
to the other side
of the room all night?
- Yes, I can.
- [Laughs]
Uh, all right.
I'm really sorry.
I think we'll just--
We'll just watch.
You can watch, not watch,
whatever you want to do.
Take another shower.
I don't care.
Okay.
[Sighs]
I am so cold.
Hey, Darryl.
You okay?
She's got a boyfriend.
Play it cool, man.
She'll come around.
No, you should go for it.
I mean, nothing would've
happened with me and Jim
if he didn't
put himself out there.
Yeah, but...
My friend Jim would tell you
to play it cool.
My husband would tell you
to go for it.
- Hey.
- Hey, this is fun.
- A lot of fun.
- I know.
Can I give you a compliment?
I'm really impressed
by how much you've grown.
Since I met you,
it's like night and day.
You should
move down here with me.
- Yeah?
- We could be roommates.
- Really?
- We could get a dog.
We could go
to R-rated movies.
And who knows, I mean,
you're a guy, I'm a girl--
- Yeah.
- Maybe in six months--
Six months?
Um, okay,
I'm in love with Kelly.
Put your forehead near mine,
and see if you can read
my thoughts.
Okay.
Seven, one, one, nine...
No, no, no.
Not numbers, no.
- No, okay.
- No.
Try again.
Ugh, I'm still getting numbers.
Seven, one, one--
Is anyone around here thinking
the numbers seven, one, one?
'Cause please stop, okay?
Dwight, give me
a key card to your room.
Meet me in seven minutes
for some one-on-one time.
[Gasps] Wait, the numbers!
Mm-hmm.
- Oh.
- Mm-hmm.
There you go.
I will see you
in seven--
Seven minutes.
Nellie, wait.
Let me write my room number
on the card.
[Chuckles]
Win at all costs.
Don't respect women.
These are the tenets
I was brought up with,
and they have served me well.
But my ancestors never worked
in corporate America.
They were farmers.
And before that, hunters.
And before that,
time travelers.
And before that, me again.
At least,
that's how the legend goes.
The point is they never had to
worry about how they got ahead.
They just had to put food
on the table
and not alter the past.
1434-967, paid.
It has been processed.
It has been delivered.
That's it.
Last one.
[Applause] Whoo!
Andy, this has been
an amazing night. Epic.
Cool-down fiesta
begins right now.
- I got decaf coffee.
- No way.
I got Romy And Michele's
High School Reunion.
Hey.
I just wanted to apologize.
I mean, that was so weird.
Can we just, like,
never talk about it again?
- Sure.
- Okay, thanks.
Hey, just so you know,
me and you--
I don't think
that's ridiculous.
Dot, dot, dot...
Dot, dot.
All right. Now I think
it's time for you to go.
What?
Oh, Jim, I thought
we talked about this.
You're cool, right?
Cathy, go.
- Where's the bug?
- Awesome.
Stand back!
Aah! Stop it, oh, my God!
That burns! What is that?
It's a compound of chemicals
I pulled off of the maid's cart.
[Coughs] Oh, my God.
Dwight, there!
Oh, God, stop it!
Stop it!
[Coughs] Oh, big one!
Big one! Really big one!
- I can't breathe!
- I think I saw it!
Stop it!
[Coughs] Nice job.
I think you got 'em.
[Door closes]
You can't stay here.
This place is a biohazard.
If I were you,
I'd just bunk with Cathy.
[Scoffs]
[Tv noise]
Second best bananas foster
I've ever had.
Oh, yeah?
What's the first best?
Dwight?
[Knocks]
[Knocking]
Hello? Dwight...
- Is that Nellie?
- Don't let-- Shh.
Are you in there?
I can see the lights
under your door.
Hello?
Look, the light went off.
Just as I said the
light went on.
Dwight?
Oh, Dwight!