Andy's coming back today.
Ha!
David Wallace sent him
on an outward-bound
wilderness adventure
for a whole month
to make him more decisive
and confident.
He sent his own son too.
And the counselor said
they both grew up big time.
How was my summer?
It was pretty mixed.
I invented a new power drink
made of beet run-off.
Mmm. Mmm!
So that's really good.
But I got some disappointing
medical news.
Mr. Schrute,
the results are in.
- You're not the father.
- I told you.
Oh, God!
Oh, my God!
Oh, what a summer.
An emotional roller coaster.
I ran over a turtle
in the parking lot...
But then I saved him by gluing
his shell back together.
But I'm not that good
at puzzles...
Oh, that piece doesn't
go there.
Shh.
So I patched him with stuff
from around the office.
But I couldn't get
the pieces to fit right.
Then, one day, while I was
reaching for the glue,
I crushed his shell again.
But I rebuilt him even better
that time.
But it turned out
the turtle was already dead.
Probably when I ran over him
the first time.
For us, um...
Nothing new, really.
The kids are great.
You are really good at modesty.
She's a genius. She painted
this incredible mural
in the kids' room.
There's a hippo leading
a parade of 500 children--
Okay, well, you had
that interesting thing.
Oh... yeah.
Yes, Jim's friend
is starting a new company
based on this idea that Jim had
when they were back in college.
It's sports marketing,
basically,
but the athletes are partners.
And he wanted Jim
to be a partner too.
In Philly, so...
that doesn't really work
for the family.
But watch this guy make
a billion dollars off my idea.
He said if it takes off,
he's gonna buy us a new car.
An Altima or better.
Kelly Kapoor is gone.
Her fiance, Ravi, was hired
as a Pediatrics Professor
at Miami University.
I don't need 'em anymore.
I am going to Miami,
bee-yotches,
to hang with Lebron James
and Gloria Estefan.
Miami University, in Ohio.
On her last day, Kelly was still
a little confused about it.
- Enjoy the snow, losers.
- I'm so happy for you, Kelly.
Shortly after Kelly left,
Ryan quit
and also moved to Ohio,
for what he claimed were
unrelated reasons.
I've actually done a lot
of market research,
and it turns out that
Southwestern Ohio is going to be
the next Silicon Valley.
They call it
the Silicon Prairie.
It's a big university town,
and, uh...
It's not garbage,
it's my clothes.
And that was our summer.
- We good?
- Yeah. Thanks.
Don't you guys have everything?
I mean, it's just
a paper company.
Yeah, well, we're more
following you guys
to see how you turn out.
Oh, yeah, I guess we were
kind of dramatic
in the beginning.
Well, I don't think anything's
gonna change in our lives now.
With work and two kids,
there's just--
Nothing interesting's
gonna happen to us
for a long, long time.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Andy's coming back today.
Hey, uh, does anybody know
where we throw these out?
Oh, my God.
- It's called a garbage can.
- Helpless.
There's two new guys
back there with me now.
They're in their 20s,
and we really get along.
Looking good.
Just three single guys...
getting into trouble.
They're like the new
Jim and Dwight.
Oh, yes, yes.
I see that. Perfect.
Hey, new Jim,
come sit on my face.
No, thank you.
My name's Pete.
No, Pete is not the new Jim.
The only thing
we have in common is that
neither of us wants to sit
on Meredith's face.
And if that makes him
the new Jim,
then every human being
in the world is the new Jim.
Andy's here! Old Dwight,
new Dwight, Andy's here.
New Jim, Tuna, Andy's here.
Pam, he's here.
Hey! Ahh.
Wow, I thought about this place
a lot when I was on solo.
Three days on a mountain,
it'll change you.
The things we think we need.
Clocks.
Yeah, right.
It sounds amazing.
Tell us all about it.
What are you still doing here?
Wonderful, thanks.
You know, I had this
really funny dream
during outward bound
that you died.
Brilliant.
See me in my office later.
The new guys.
All right.
- Clark and, um...
- Pete.
Da da da da...
In Outward Bound,
it was all about nicknames.
They called me Iceman.
You will be called "Plop."
What-- Why?
'Cause you're always
taking dumps.
No, I'm not.
Come on, everybody defecates.
Relax, Plop.
You will be called "Fart"
- because you fart all the time.
- I love it.
Actually, Andy,
we call this one
"Dwight Jr."
No, I prefer "Fart."
No, Dwight Jr.
Infinitely better.
You guys look exactly alike.
Dwight, go stand next to him.
- This is insane.
- I don't see it.
I don't either.
Whoa.
Mind blown.
It's like father and son.
It's...
Dwight, you cool if we
call him Dwight Jr.?
Yes.
Yes, I am.
That's okay.
- Dwight Jr.
- Ha.
In a way, it's like
I have a son.
And who knows?
Maybe some day
they'll hire someone who looks
like a younger version of him.
And then I'll have a grandson.
Well, I need to give
my cat up for adoption.
- Mmm.
- The one who uses the doorbell,
or the one
with the Mexican hat,
with the rain galoshes,
or the one that you let
go around naked?
Angela's cats are cute.
So cute that you just want
to eat 'em.
But you can't eat cats.
You can't eat cats, Kevin.
- No, the one with the long hair
and the denim pants-- Comstock.
- Oh.
- Okay, look.
He's such a special kitty.
I just want to find him
a good home.
He loves those pants.
I'll take him.
Please.
After the turtle?
I am enormously proud
of what I did for that turtle!
Oscar. Oscar.
Will you take him?
No, I'm a dog person.
If you pray enough,
you can change yourself
into a cat person.
Those guys always
turn back, Angela.
David, outward bound
was incredible.
I was the best at slacklining.
I ate a worm.
Glad to hear it.
You sound really confident
and decisive.
Hey, you wanted to see me?
Yeah.
I gotta go, David.
Why is Nellie still here?
You can only fire Nellie
for cause.
Hmm. Then I will
make up a cause.
Except you just told me
you were gonna make it up.
Now, if she sues,
I have to testify against you.
Then forget
I just told you that.
I can't. I took a course
at the Weintraub Memory Academy.
Sat next to this woman
named Beverly Brook.
She had a Greek salad
for lunch.
See what I mean?
Now I know why Michael
hated you so much.
No, he didn't.
Good boy.
Getting big and strong.
Snack foods!
Yep.
Body by cheez-it.
Ah, humor.
I have it too.
Oh, boy,
I got a couple of tickets
to The Slayer concert
ten months from now.
You interested?
I think I'm busy that night.
Oh, or I would.
Mmm, okay, well,
we're both just kind of learning
as we go, aren't we?
Learning what?
Just... how this is gonna be.
You know.
You have a beautiful
round head.
Okay.
So what kind of farming
you into, huh?
More of a fruit man
or a root man?
Hey, is this-- is this code
for, like, gay stuff?
'Cause if so,
that's totally fine.
Like, I'm fine with it.
But you know, you should know
that I'm into the ladies.
Spoken like a true root man.
Hey, you know,
if you're ever swamped,
I can make
some sales calls for you.
- My calls?
- So could you give me
a list of all your clients,
or just the leads
that you haven't had time
to pursue yet?
You want a list of my clients?
You want my leads?
Yeah, I'll just
give it a glance.
- Okay.
- I'll give it a read.
Yeah, with my leads,
and stuff like that.
Yeah.
'Cause you're interested
in going into sales.
- I am.
- Wow, that's great.
- Yeah.
- That's great.
Okay, good.
Let's talk about that, okay?
- Okay.
- You're not getting my clients.
Nice try.
Paranoid?
I'm not familiar with the word.
And I really don't have time
to learn new words
right now, okay?
A pudgy 22-year-old
is trying to take my job.
Jim, get ready for the
battle of your life.
Done. Explain.
The new guys-- Dwight Jr.
is after my job.
Yeah, there is a shark
hiding inside
that adorable little cherub.
Oh, now I get
what Pete was talking about
at the sales meeting yesterday.
Wait, sales--
What sales meeting?
The new guys called one.
The new guys called
a sales meeting?
Clark ended the whole thing
with a karate demonstration.
Did you know there was
a belt above black?
There's no belt above black.
- Is there a belt above black?
- You should ask him.
It's a color
you would never expect.
Too easy.
Attention, everyone.
Comstock is still available.
Oscar has been flirting
with adopting him,
but still hasn't given me
a definite yes or no.
- Definitely no.
- Fine.
For any interested candidates,
I will be conducting
20-minute interviews.
My ideal situation would be
an independently wealthy
cute couple
with a strong commitment
to education.
Black or white--
I'm fine with either.
But not both.
Listen, you're in this,
but you need to wow me, okay?
I wanted to talk to you about
our working relationship
this year.
It's going to be terrible.
Not necessarily.
No, I'm going to make sure
that it is.
And if it isn't, I will take
immediate action
to rectify that.
Now, I don't like
to throw around the "B" word,
but I'm gonna be
a huge bitch to you.
Now, this is called
slacklining.
I set up the old slackline
to teach the office
the skills of focus
and discipline.
Or in the case
of certain individuals,
the skills of humiliation
and looking really dumb.
If you make it
all the way across,
your confidence will soar.
But if you Toby out--
Aah! Aah!
Then you'll feel like
a real Nellie.
How 'bout a hand?
Screw those guys.
Now, these are my actual
outward bound counselors,
Rafe and Feather.
- Iceman.
- That's me.
The powder is for
your protection.
Feather has permanent
athlete's foot.
Feather, show them
how you dance
upon the line of slack.
You, uh--
You a sports guy?
- Sure. Uh, boxing, tennis.
- Oh.
Any team sports?
Nascar.
The Amazing Race.
Phillies fan, though, right?
You mean horses?
No, like ba-- baseball.
The baseball team.
I like the Red Sox.
I'm from Vermont, so...
Okay. Good talk.
I have nothing in common
with Plop.
All right, who's next?
Nellie.
Oh, I would rather watch you
and your talented friends.
Nonsense.
Get up here.
- Go ahead.
- Come on.
Uh, you gonna wear your heels?
I'm very self-conscious
about my feet.
Okay. Sure.
There you go.
Atta girl.
Hey, all right.
Whoa! You suck.
All right, who's next?
Darryl.
This seems like
the kind of thing
white people
with dreadlocks do.
Dwight Jr., this looks
like your speed.
Uh, I guess I can
give it a shot.
Yeah, come on.
Get up here.
- Just hop on up.
- Okay.
Focus on the horizon.
Whoa!
Look at this guy.
I've always been good
at anything
that required balance.
My doctor says I have
gigantic inner ears.
Go, Dwight Jr.
- Yes!
- Boo! Unimpressed.
It's a tightrope for babies.
Boo.
All right, let's see you do it.
All right, let me show you
how a real man
walks across a flaccid cord.
Oh, ho ho ho!
Who ordered the hot apple fail?
Okay, I am just
getting started, okay?
You got this.
This is all you.
Oh!
- Oh...
- Got ourselves a yard sale.
- Oh.
- Whoa.
Balls and face.
- It's not a race, Dwight.
- Aah!
- Oh!
- Well, it's official--
Old Dwight is lame,
and new Dwight is cool.
That's not true.
Just give me another chance.
- But your mouth is--
- This is a bloodbath.
All right, I'm calling this.
- What?
- It's enough of this.
Everyone, let's go back
to work.
This is a stupid activity.
I would be embarrassed
to be good at it.
Get--
Idiots!
Slacklining.
Big deal.
Untie that rope,
give it to a couple
of pigtailed school girls,
let them start jumping with it
while chanting a rhyme
and giggling about boys.
Doesn't seem so macho now,
does it?
It's a jump rope!
Dwight!
Pam?
Hey, I'm up here.
Up the ladder.
Come on.
What are you doing?
Come here.
I'll show you.
Why do you want this cat?
Um, I don't want it, really.
How would you support the cat?
What are your ambitions?
I want to start
my own business.
I want to be a millionaire.
Lots of things-- Travel.
Make the world a better place.
Earn an MBA at night.
Have you taken any
concrete steps?
Well, I'm still just...
fitting in here.
You know, getting used
to the new job.
- Mm-hmm.
- But definitely on the agenda.
But that is a good idea, Angela.
I should make a list.
Oh, come on, Pete.
God, that's just sad.
If he doesn't watch himself,
he's gonna be here for years
doing nothing.
Wow, maybe Pete is the new Jim.
Do you see how the trapeze
completely surrounds the wire?
That means it is
literally impossible
for anyone to fall off.
So you will merely sit below
and be my counterweight
as I pedal across
the parking lot
to that telephone pole,
- I will?
- You will.
Yeah, we weigh about
the same, wouldn't you say?
- Sure, if you weigh 105 pounds.
- So you'll do it?
- No.
- Come on!
This will be the only thrill
of your boring life.
Dwight, you may find this
hard to believe,
but I love my boring life...
- Come on.
- Exactly the way it is.
- No, Pam.
- Yes.
And there's nothing you can say
that would get me to run
the slightest risk of losing it.
- Please? Please, Pam?
- Find someone else.
I don't know, ask Phyllis.
I can't use Phyllis.
Are you kidding me?
The moment she steps
off this bar
I'll be launched into space.
God, you're so insensitive!
Why are you getting rid of it?
Allergies.
- Your husband?
- No, the baby.
Please, it's my husband's
favorite cat.
He's broken up about it.
It's the only time
I've seen him cry
other than our wedding night.
You know what?
I will take Comstock.
Really?
Oh, Oscar, thank you!
I'll come by after work
and pick him up.
Yay!
Oh, poor Robert.
He won't get to say good-bye.
He has this business dinner
tonight.
Oh, c'est la vie.
Please don't teach
the cat French.
Yeah, good news.
Tonight, when you come over
for dinner,
you can play
with your old buddy Comstock.
You ready?
Yeah.
You know what?
I'll meet you down there.
I've just gotta make
a quick call.
Okay.
All right...
Oh, God.
Attention, employees
of Dunder Mifflin.
Everyone thinks the new guys
are so cool
'cause they can slackline.
Ooh!
Hey, Clark, this is what
a real salesman looks like.
They say that you only
live once,
and I'm about to prove it.
- Dwight Schrute!
- Dwight!
Hey, man, it's Halpert.
Did you go
to the other guy yet?
Great. Don't.
I'm in.
Yeah, yep, I'm all in.
Okay, talk to you soon.
Bye.
Yeah!
Whoo-hoo!
- Call somebody.
- Hang on!
Hang on!
Hold on, Dwight!
In the parking lot today,
there was a circus.
The copier did tricks
on the high wire.
A lady tried to give away
a baby that looked like a cat.
There was a Dwight impersonator
and a Jim impersonator.
A strongman crushed a turtle.
I laughed and I cried.
Not bad for a day in the life
of a dog food company.
Crap, sorry, Nellie.
Once again, I understand
that old habits die hard,
but if everyone would kindly
walk their refuse
to the trash bins,
instead of tossing them,
then we would--
Oh...
Swish.
Oh, it's nothing to do with me.
I just happen to be sitting
near to where the bins are.
There are two things
that I am passionate about--
Recycling and revenge.
Flook.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com