All right, everybody.
Great season of softball,
I'm super proud of you, guys.
And I think you're
gonna like this
little highlight reel
that I've put together.
Dunder Mifflin!
Andy Bernard presents...
Summer Softball, epic fails!
Fail.
- That's me.
- Fail.
Is this like a blooper reel?
A blooper reel?
What is this, 2005?
Do I look like Bob Saget?
Fail!
Who's this guy?
♪ Meow, meow, meow, meow
meow, meow, meow, meow ♪
Look at him dance.
Fail!
Fail.
I deserve that.
♪ Doont-de-doont-de-doont,
doont-de-doont-de-doont ♪
That was a triple.
Can't take the fail?
Get out of the fail video!
My pleasure.
Hi, I'm Pete.
Puberty is such a drag, man.
And I'm Clark.
I like to eat toilet paper.
We fail.
I'd like to take a solemn moment
to remember Jerry,
in the warehouse,
who passed away this year.
Well, that's all, folks.
Ski you later, everybody.
Thanks for a great season.
What was that?
That was just normal video
with you making vulgar noises.
Well, I worked
with what I had, Oscar.
Next time,
do more fail-ier stuff, okay?
What happened
to that video I sent you?
Oh, that wasn't--
that didn't work.
That was...
not the right thing.
- Wait, let's see it.
- Play it.
- I think I got it right here.
- No--
Oh!
Forgot about this.
That was not a fail.
That was actually
a serious accident
that could've resulted
in severe bodily harm.
- Fail, fail, fail.
- You're all failing right now.
Congratulations
on your epic fail
of the use of the word fail.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Oh, God.
What's going on?
Nothing, nothing is going on.
Keep moving, please.
What's he measuring?
Okay, excuse me,
I'm the landlord.
This is between me
and the management,
no one else, please.
It's an EMF hotspot.
Oh, my God!
It stands for electromagnetic
fields generally caused
by a concentration of wiring
in one area,
especially if poorly insulated.
Dwight?
Um, okay,
I'm just walking into this.
Am I to understand
there's a beehive in the wall?
You think I have a machine
for measuring beehives?
I was just asking
a question, Toby.
How are you not murdered
every hour?
Well, I'm not getting paid
to work in a microwave oven.
Okay, listen,
everything here is up to code.
Oh, the wires need insulation.
It's a wire, people.
I'm not buying it a fur coat.
- Thank you.
- You got it.
Last week, I finally told Pam
about the other job
- I took in Philly, the side job.
- Thank you.
And she was
so incredibly cool about it.
And now, I just want to do
something huge for her.
Like if we were
in some biker bar,
and she mouthed off
to some bikers,
and they came lumbering over,
and I was like, "wham!
Gotta go through me first."
Andy, could I have a word,
please?
Um, it won't take a moment.
It's extremely important,
and it really has
to happen now.
Fine, I will give you
one minute--
Oh, please, don't use
the hourglass.
You have one minute,
and your minute has begun,
and no time will be added
at the end,
even to accommodate
this sentence
with all of its
baroque-dependent clauses
and cascading turns of phrase.
I'm trying to adopt a baby.
A baby what?
A human?
And the agency require
character reference
from my employer.
Oh.
You won't have to do anything.
I would write
the letter myself.
You'd just need
to sign it, so--
Okay, and fall right into your
plagiarism-entrapment scheme?
- I don't think so.
- It's not--
And I happen to notice you're
down to about 30 seconds here.
Well, then, if I could just
convince you that you--
And those sand grains
are tumbling with fury down--
It's not entrapment
if I'm writing--
Time's up!
Fine.
Sure, I'll read her letter,
and if she tells the truth
about how evil and unfit
to be a mother she is,
then, yeah, I'll sign that.
"Statistical correlations
exist between EMF radiation
and various health hazards,
but mainstream studies
are inconclusive."
That means
you can't make me do squat.
You better fix this.
I already ditched my uterus,
and I ain't losing
any more good parts.
You people don't realize
what you're asking.
I'd have to rip open the walls.
I'd have to shut this place down
for a week.
Week off.
That'd be great.
Hey, if you don't want
to teach me PowerPoint,
just say so.
I don't want
to teach you PowerPoint.
Come on.
Just show me PowerPoint.
- Just do the tutorial.
- You're the tutorial.
No, dude, I'm not.
I'm not the tutorial.
- You could be.
- Mm-mm.
What are you doing?
Getting my wife a week off
from work.
You popped one kernel.
Awesome, right?
So creed
is that dude's stepdad?
Correct.
Well, I don't know
about the rest of you,
but I'm just going to say it;
I'm nervous.
I have no idea
what health problems
this is all going to cause.
- He's right.
- What? Come on.
I'm getting older.
I'm losing my hair.
- I'm sorry.
- I'm gonna grow a third arm.
I know what Jim
is trying to do.
He's trying to get
big, bad Dwight
to shell out
for a huge repair job,
while Lucky Jimbo gets
a paid vacation.
Well, sorry, Lucky Jimbo,
I can live very happily
in a magnetic field.
Most of my childhood heroes
got their powers that way.
Side effects of EMF
include headaches--
Had them all my life.
Breast pain--
No nobbies, no probbies.
Nice try, Jim.
Oof.
Infertility.
Yeah, right.
Ah, there's my popcorn.
Can you just grab that for me?
Keep your snacks
on your side, Jim, idiot.
- What the--?
- What?
Some of these kernels
have crowned.
That's impossible
'cause that's a brand-new bag.
Oh, my God.
Andy!
I'm going to drive you
up to the lake,
give you a whole week
on the water,
just you, me, and the kids.
Oh, can we stop
by that pie stand on the way?
You mean, "Laverne's Pies,
Tires Fixed Also"? Yes.
We will be doing that,
and we'll be getting a dozen.
A dozen different pies?
'Cause that means rhubarb.
Why would you say that?
I meant four apple,
four blueberry,
two cherry, one peach,
one chocolate.
I thought that was implied.
Yeah, okay, then.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I have heard your complaints,
and we reached a settlement.
So...
We will be leaving the office
for one whole week.
Nice job.
In my contract,
it is stipulated
that I provide
a temporary work space.
It will arrive in one hour.
What?
- What's this?
- Oh!
- What?
- Bring it in.
Roll into the future
with work bus.
Say good-bye
to wasteful buildings.
These days, a mobile office
isn't just
for hotshot politicians.
Now anyone can rent a work bus.
If you've got a parking lot,
a work space is just
a phone call away.
In this age
of belt-tightening
and less-empowered workers,
a work bus
is how tomorrow
gets things done.
- Shh!
Shh!
$23.99 a page, yes.
- Six. Yes.
- Yeah.
Oh, sorry about that.
Oh, my God!
Oops. Sorry.
Lose weight.
I'm trying.
Sorry.
Ah.
The Pennsylvania Department
of Public Welfare
pre-adoption standard?
Oh, of course,
you were adopted.
I wish.
No, I made some short lists,
I had a couple of sleepovers,
but I never managed to get
in the end-zone.
I don't know what it was.
Not lovable, maybe?
Oh, well.
Listen, I'm really struggling
with this form.
But as you know the system,
do you think maybe you could--
Absolutely, I know exactly
what they want to hear.
I would--
I would love to help.
Oh, thank you so much.
Just don't tell Andy because--
- He hates me.
- And--
- Thinks I'm a monster.
- That--
- Should go back to Loch Ness.
Stretch.
All right.
How many times do you need
to take a stroll?
I-- my legs cramp up, okay?
It's a circulation issue.
Boy, I will hammer-spank
your rear.
All right, all right, gang.
Let's just settle down.
You're yelling in her face.
It's a medical thing.
Just-- You good?
I'm good. I--
I'm so sorry for all of this.
It's okay.
You know what they say,
a change is as good as a rest.
I-- I need to get
to the paper, please.
Sorry.
Oh, God!
- Oh, oh, my God!
- Okay--
- Oh!
- I'll get you a napkin.
Can someone get napkins,
please?
You know what, it's fine.
It's fine, let me just--
It's fine.
Pam, I'm really sorry.
I just--
I'm-- I'm really sorry
about all that.
Really?
Smirking?
What can I say?
I love justice.
You forced me to spend money
on needless repairs,
and now you're locked
in a prison bus,
and your woman drips
with beverage.
Hey, Dwight, I was trying
to do something nice for Pam.
Can you just help me out?
Can we maybe take
this thing somewhere,
or do something to not make this
the worst day ever?
It's not my responsibility
to solve your marriage problems
by spending my money on gas.
Andy!
Yo!
Toonces.
You're the boss.
Don't you think we'd all be
a lot more productive
if while we were doing work,
we looked up and saw
the best rural pie stand
in Pennsylvania?
Ooh, I know
I'd be more productive.
- As would I.
- No question.
No! No!
This is a work bus.
The wheels are for transporting
the work space
to and from the work site.
What are you talking about?
You're not the boss, Andy is.
Andy?
Pies, pies, pies,
pies, pies, pies.
All right!
The fat people have spoken.
Dwight, get this bus moving.
Next stop, Laverne's Pies,
Tires Fixed Also.
Oh, yes!
Yeah, Jim!
So it looks like this work bus
was a pretty good idea
after all, huh?
Get your foot
behind the yellow line.
You got it.
Yeah, Jim!
- Stop.
- Come back.
- Too late.
- Mm.
♪ Shabooya roll call,
shabooya-ya-ya ♪
♪ shabooya roll call ♪
- ♪ My name is Pam ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I like to paint ♪
- ♪ You think you're better? ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
- ♪ Oh, no, you ain't ♪
♪ Roll call ♪
♪ Shabooya-ya-ya ♪
♪ shabooya roll call,
shabooya-ya-ya ♪
♪ shabooya roll call ♪
- ♪ My name is Kevin ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
- ♪ That is my name ♪
- ♪ They call me Kevin ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
- ♪ 'Cause that's my name ♪
- ♪ Roll call ♪
♪ shabooya-ya-ya
shabooya roll call ♪
Thanks.
Playing a little hooky
from work today.
Oh, my God.
Dunder Mifflin road trip 2012!
Okay, now a serious one.
Hey, where's Dwight?
He should be a part of this.
Has he been acting
kind of weird to you lately?
If by "lately," you mean
for the last 12 years, yeah.
No, I mean, he's sulking.
That's not like him.
He's just mad
that we're all having fun.
Then why isn't he scheming
or preparing to avenge?
He's fine.
He's indestructible.
Always say that a child
is placed for adoption,
never surrendered.
We're not hostages.
Although I have
considered kidnapping one.
Oh, and never say that.
I am so excited
thinking about this child
you're going to adopt.
I wish I could just wave
a magic wand
and make you a parentless
five-year-old again.
I would snap you up.
Oh.
Next stop, pies.
Next stop, pies!
Next stop, pies,
next stop, pies!
Let's go, driver!
Laverne packs up the pie wagon
at 5:00, so--
At 5:00?
That's only 20 minutes from now.
The pie shop is 13 miles away.
So at 55 miles an hour,
that just gives us
5 minutes to spare.
So, wait,
when pies are involved,
you can suddenly do math
in your head?
Hold on, Kevin,
how much is 19,154 pies
divided by 61 pies?
314 pies.
What if it were salads?
Well, it's the--
carry the four and the--
it doesn't work.
I'm sorry to spoil Jim's
fantastic voyage, everyone,
but we're almost out of gas.
Okay, well, I saw a station
about a mile back,
so chop, chop.
That name brand place?
No, forget about it, sorry.
The tanks are so big on
this thing, 5¢ a gallon extra?
It really adds up.
Are you kidding me?
- Dwight, come on.
- Hey.
Honey, I don't think
we should push him.
Oh, no, I'm going to push him.
You know why?
Because you are getting a pie.
Why?
'Cause you deserve it.
And what is he doing?
He's trying to drive us all
around the countryside,
looking for gas because he
knows we won't get there.
Is that what we want?
No!
Stop ordering me around, Jim!
- What do we want?
- Pies!
When do we want it?
- Pies.
- Okay, fine.
You win, Jim.
You win.
We have been battling
for a long time,
but, you know what, you win.
'Cause you are the winner,
you are the alpha male.
There you go.
Alpha male,
go buy your wife a pie.
Go buy the whole world a pie.
That's impossible.
- Oh, no!
- Dwight!
- What are you doing?
- What the hell?
- Whoa, Dwight.
- Dwight.
- What?
Well, now I don't even
feel like pie.
Wait.
No, it's back.
Just drive away.
Phyllis, that's not safe.
Guys, we only have
18 minutes left.
At 61 miles an hour, we're just
going to barely make it.
Go up and check on him,
he's upset.
You know
he's doing all this on purpose.
Please, just make sure
he's okay.
Hurry it up, for God's sake.
They're going to be
out of banana cream.
Banana cream's the first to go.
We'd be lucky to get pumpkin
at this point.
What?
Dwight?
Why are you such a jerk?
I'm trying to do something
for my wife, and you keep--
- I'm barren, Jim.
What?
My trouser hives
are void of honey.
I had congress with Angela,
and the child that she bore
did not issue from my loins.
Thought I would be a father,
and instead I am a eunuch,
neutered by my own building.
Is this about the popcorn,
or the X on the ceiling?
Dwight, that was a prank.
You mean
you flooded my building
with dangerous electromagnetic
radiation as a prank?
- No.
- That's genius.
That's the best prank
you've ever done.
I'll take it.
Andy?
Who is it?
- Um, is this a good time?
- Yeah.
Perfect time, right in
the middle of a rooftop crisis.
Fine, yeah, let me read it.
What do we have here?
Okay--
You've made this very easy
for me.
It's unsignable.
Oh.
What, is there something--?
It's inaccurate, dishonest,
and, in a word, dong-water.
Oh, well, perhaps
I could reword some of it--
Here's the thing.
You asked me to do you a favor,
I did it, I read it.
Thank you very much to me
for my time.
Good luck
with your impossible dream.
All right, then.
Dwight, sometimes
it takes couples
years to get pregnant.
Really? How long did it take
you and Pam to conceive?
That doesn't matter.
What position
did you use to conceive,
regular
or lady-on-her-back?
You used lady-on-her-back,
didn't you, freak?
Yuck, gross.
Never mind, Jim.
British women,
famously over-emotional,
am I right?
I don't think that's Nellie.
- What?
- Oh.
Oh, no, no, no.
It's all right.
Really, it isn't your fault.
No, no. It's--
You were so kind,
and it isn't anything
to do with you.
Did you ever think that
because you own the building,
everyone in it,
we're all kind of like
your children.
You know, there's a phrase
about that in German,
bilden-kinder,
used almost exclusively
by childless landlords
to console themselves, but now,
I really understand it.
Well, now you have a bus full
of real building-kinder.
- Bilden-kinder.
-  Okay.
And they're all dangerously
close to not getting pie.
And there's only one guy
who can save them.
It's not me.
- I agree.
- Oh!
Oh.
Hey, how did it go?
- It was pretty good, actually.
- Yeah?
We bonded,
we got to t--
- Oh!
- Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- Dwight, Dwight!
- Dwight!
That's what happens when
you don't get out of the way.
Out of the way!
You feel okay now?
Oh, better than okay.
And you know what, honey?
I'm going to get you
that rhubarb pie.
Well, actually, rhubarb
- is the one pie that I don't--
- Don't, don't.
Everybody, hang on!
Pie, pie, pie, pie, pie, pie!
Oh.
I changed my mind.
- Oh, you signed it?
- Yeah.
Not as is, obviously.
Made a couple of changes,
added some sentences
at the end.
Trust me, it needed it.
But, yeah, whatever.
"She's tough in business,
but tender
with the people
she cares about.
She'll make a wonderful mother
to any child
who can overlook
weird accents."
- I insult you, Oscar.
- What?
I insult you to your face.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Then why don't you
do something about it?
Kevin, are you trying
to get me to hit you
in the face with my pie?
You don't have the guts.
You stupid, dumb,
doo-doo face.
Yes!
Oh, my God.
I'm getting so stuffed.
We did it.
You did it.
- ♪ My name is Andy ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
- ♪ I don't do drugs ♪
- ♪ Now, check the style ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
- ♪ Of flatt and scruggs ♪
Roll call.
What?
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com