This year I decided to really get
into the spirit of Halloween.
It may have been the costliest
decision I've ever made.
My greased up head went into
the pumpkin no problem...
- It won't budge.
- ...but I can't get it out.
Try again.
I mean, I could try
destroying the pumpkin...
No! No! No! No!
Please!
But as Jim and I discovered...
No!
...any blow to the pumpkin itself
could prove fatal to me.
At first, I drove myself crazy
thinking about the things
I should've done differently.
Yes, Dwight.
I never should've
played that joke on Erin.
I never should've hollowed out
this damn pumpkin
in the first place.
But then I realized
I was being silly.
I mean, the pumpkin
should rot off of my head
in a month or two...
right?
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
- Hey, guys.
- Hey.
- Pam, what are you?
- I'm Doctor Cinderella.
Cece's really
into princesses now,
so we decided to turn them into
positive female role models.
I'm an oncologist.
And you are a dog.
No, I'm a puppy.
Dang it!
I was worried that would happen.
- It's okay.
- Um, Jim,
you're not dressed up at all.
Sure I am.
I am...
one of the Men In Black guys.
Can I have your sunglasses?
Jim, come on.
I thought we were past this.
So the sports marketing
business
that Jim told everyone about
except for me?
There's
a big investment lunch today,
so I decided
to skip the costume.
Unless he has a secret costume
that he told everyone about
except for me.
Getting a lot of
mileage out of this, aren't you?
Yeah, well,
get used to it, bud.
♪ A jitterbug ♪
You guys look great!
The party is right after lunch,
so make sure you get
all your work done before that
or throw it out.
Any questions?
The senator
will be joining us later.
Not a question.
- No, it wasn't.
- Excellent.
That reminds me,
has anyone seen Treble?
Anyone?
I could have sworn
I saw some Treble somewhere.
Oh, ladies and gentlemen,
Here Comes Treble!
- ♪ I'm a man ♪
- ♪ A man ♪
♪ without conviction ♪
♪ you come and go,
you come and go ♪
♪ Karma, karma, karma, karma,
karma chameleon ♪
♪ you come and go,
you come and go ♪
♪ loving would be easy if your
colors were like my dreams ♪
♪ red, gold, and green,
red, gold, and green ♪
♪ karma come on ♪
Ah! So good!
What lab did these
little clones escape from?
My Cornell a cappella group.
You were in
an a cappella group?
You went to Cornell?
Yeah.
Uh, okay, ha, ha, ha, ha.
But you have no idea
how lucky you are,
because HCT is doing a set
at our Halloween party.
Ugh, I don't want
to sit through
a whole concert of that.
I do.
I love the boss's interests.
Atta boy, Clark.
Where you boys staying?
How does it work in the rooms?
You get a privacy partition?
No. No, nope, not--
No, stay away.
You know what I just realized?
They might actually
call me up to solo
on George Michael's Faith.
That was one of
my signature songs.
Oh, man.
That would be insane.
I'm so not prepared.
Are you sure you're okay with
me putting in this much money?
Yeah.
I mean, listen,
if we're gonna do this thing,
then we should do it right.
You're the best.
I kind of am.
- It's crazy.
- Okay.
- I'll see you in a little bit.
Jim, look, I'm eating you.
- Shut up.
- Ha, ha!
Hey, Erin,
look, these are nerds.
I'm eating Jims.
Must eat more Jims.
Stop it! Stop it!
- I'm spilling Jims...
- Stop it! Stop it! Stop it!
- All over the carpet, Erin!
Mm. Mm.
Hello, little pill.
What do you do?
Dumatril is licensed
to treat anxiety symptoms,
such as panic attacks,
excessive worrying, and fear.
Translation,
there's a madman in our midst.
Okay, I give up.
What are you?
I'm Sexy Toby.
Gross.
I love it.
Dumatril!
Something wrong, Dwight?
- Dumatril.
- Yes?
This is a pill
I found here in the office,
but it's not for worms
or eczema,
like any normal pill.
It's not for any disorder
of the body.
It's for a disorder of the mind.
The mind is part of the body.
Okay, this is a pill
that combats insanity, okay?
Whoever is taking it
is not only insane...
they are now off their meds.
Dwight, our
co-workers' health issues
are really
none of our business, so--
Why are you trying so hard
to bury this thing, huh?
What's going on, Nellie?
- Talk to me.
- Mm?
It's my pill.
I have an anxiety issue
and I'm not ashamed of that,
but I'm not loving the idea of
Dwight having that information.
I once saw him yell at Phyllis
for sneezing wrong.
Yeah, you're right.
This man needs
to be apprehended.
I'll get my apprehension kit.
♪ Dudes... ♪
What's up?
I know it's pathetic
to re-live your college years,
but cut me some slack, okay?
Because I was
a freaking rock star in college.
When I joined
Here Comes Treble,
that's when I became somebody.
When I got the nickname
Boner Champ,
that is when I became me.
You didn't come here
to sit in a room, right?
You came here for some
intergenerational "bro" time.
Well, now's your chance!
I'm here.
You got Qs, I got As.
Did you say you've got AIDS?
No, I don't have AIDS.
That's not what I said.
Next question.
You don't have any--
any questions
about the old days?
You at least want to know why
they call me Boner Champ?
I thought Broccoli Rob
was the Boner Champ.
I'm sorry, what?
I just thought Broccoli Rob
was the Boner Champ.
Broccoli Rob was Broccoli Rob.
Andy Bernard
is the Boner Champ.
- I hadn't realized that everybody here
dresses up every year. - Me neither.
It's Halloween.
That is really,
really good timing.
I was just talking
to some of the actives,
and they think
that you're Boner Champ.
I'm so sorry.
I don't know how
that could've happened.
Did you maybe
tell them that or--
I just-- I just started yappin'
about the old days,
and I guess the wine coolers
were flowing,
and, you know,
somehow things just got hinky.
Could you call them
and just tell them the truth?
'Cause I know
it's really stupid,
but it's also really, really,
really important.
Will do.
I love you, Andy.
Love you too.
So the workspace looks awesome.
- Wow.
- And the graphic designer
is gonna be sending us in
some of the logo treatments.
Can't wait to see them.
- You guys rock.
- I killed it.
- Boom.
- Rockin'.
Oh.
- You get some?
- There we go.
I also have been
running the numbers,
and between our backers
and our own investment,
we're looking great
for a full year on this.
Oh, uh,
is it too late to get in?
Oh, no, no.
Jim, I explained everything,
so you're all set.
Oh, no, I actually
talked to my wife,
and we'd really like to,
you know, invest,
get in on the ground floor.
Wow, well,
what level of investment
are you thinking about?
We were thinking somewhere
between $5,000, $10,000.
I can do the full $10,000.
We should just...
all in.
All right, welcome aboard.
All right.
Awesome, cool.
Hey, Darryl.
I'm just here to...
Smear some peanut butter
on my forehead.
You know, to protect
his brain from the nanobots
that the government
put in the air conditioning.
That makes sense to you, right?
Or does it sound...
crazy?
I can't really picture it.
Can you get it on there?
Yeah.
And maybe get the cheeks.
So this makes sense, then.
Or is it crazy?
Get under your chin first,
yeah.
Is that where the nanobots
like to come in?
Take it all the way
up to your lip, yeah.
Okay, is that
how they like to get in?
Yeah, that's crazy.
I don't know.
I just don't know.
Yo, bad boys of a cappella.
Hey.
Heard any good stories lately?
Or new twists on old stories?
Yeah, I got a call
from Broccoli Rob.
I guess you really are
the Boner Champ.
Did he tell you
how I got the name?
No.
Spring sing '95,
got completely ripped
on bud dries.
I had sex with a snowman.
I just went at that thing.
Cold would've stopped
most people,
but I stayed locked in.
You know,
took the face off.
Just seemed easier that way.
And I told Phyllis
not to put it out,
but she insisted, so anyway...
- Hi. Oh, Oscar.
- Oh.
Remember my husband,
the senator?
Senator Lipton,
nice to see you.
Nice to see you, Oscar.
Wait a second,
who designed this spread?
The sweets and savories
are all mixed together.
This is mayhem.
So, Oscar, you're a dinosaur?
Actually,
I'm the electoral college.
Ouch!
Right on target.
You know what?
This is outrageous.
I have to find Phyllis.
You two talk, okay?
Sorry, babe.
Phyllis!
God, it's just
so good to see you.
I-- uh-huh, just...
All having this
wonderful Halloween gathering.
Excuse me, is that punch?
They didn't know
about the snowman story,
and when I told 'em,
they were not impressed.
- What is with these turkeys?
- Right?
Hey! You better do Faith,
you get me?
We don't know it.
So learn it.
You all go to Cornell,
you're like eight Rain Men.
Just learn the frickin' song.
Look, I know it was big
with the old guys, but--
Buts...
are for pooping.
Okay?
Make it work.
You have to
or Andy will flip out...
and make it a surprise please.
This isn't stupid.
What?
- Hey.
Hey, Toby.
Are-- are you me?
Yeah.
Oh, my goodness, look at--
- Look at this.
- Yeah.
I thought I'd,
you know, be you.
- Look at-- look at me.
- Oh, look at you!
It's funny, right?
Mm.
All right, all right,
just stay focused on the pill.
Okay, look, Dwight,
let's just call this thing off.
I mean, it's just
an anxiety pill.
Lots of people have anxiety.
You think I don't have anxiety?
I have anxiety all the time.
Every waking moment of my life
is sheer torture.
I have land disputes to settle
and idiot cousins to protect
and ne'er-do-well siblings
to take care of,
but I don't need
some stupid pill
to get me through all this.
Cool, free upper.
Ah, ha, ha!
The jig is up, psychopath!
- What? Hey, what--
- Yeah! Yeah, gotcha!
- Don't dog-catch me!
- Gotcha!
- Yeah!
- Oh!
Let's see you
get out of this web, huh?
- The pill is mine.
- Wh--
Get her out.
- Oh.
- Stop baggin' my head!
Oh, Dwight, look,
it's just a pill, all right?
It's for anxiety--
I take it every day,
and it makes me feel better.
And maybe it could
help you too.
- Oh, hey! How'd it go?
- Hey.
Oh, man, it was great.
They were great.
Did you end up investing?
- I did, yeah.
- How much?
Uh, man, by the end,
I guess it was... about ten.
"About" ten?
Ten.
It was the full $10,000.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
- Yeah. Yeah.
It's a good thing
we talked about it, though,
- 'cause we had to--
- Yeah, yeah, no.
Yeah.
- So did everybody--
- What is it? Hold on.
Did everybody
end up investing $10,000?
Um, oh, man,
I don't actually know.
What?
They weren't really
talking that much about money.
They just said,
"we're good with investing,"
and-- and I--
Ladies and gentlemen,
Here Comes Treble.
They said they were
done with the investing,
and then
you volunteered $10,000?
- ♪ Ooh, ooh ♪
- No, no, I had to.
Look, I needed to look like
a team player, Pam.
So you invested $10,000
to look like a team player?
- You weren't there.
- ♪ And I'll be... ♪
It was very clear
that $10,000 was what we had--
- We'll talk about it later.
- No, I want to
- talk about it now.
- Pam.
Jim, that was
most of our savings.
♪ And I'll be better
when I'm older ♪
♪ I'll be the greatest fan
of your life ♪
Wait. Wait, hold on.
Where's the band?
'Cause there's no way
you guys are making this magic
with just your mouths.
That's what she said.
What, am I overdoing it?
No. No.
♪ That color them wonderful
stop me ♪
- We said "some."
- We'll talk about it.
- We'll talk about it later.
♪ Steal my breath ♪
We said "part,"
not "all."
♪ And I'll be ♪
♪ your crying shoulder ♪
♪ Fill up
and you don't have to pay ♪
♪ bah dah bah ♪
♪ come on and give us a play ♪
♪ get a wash right away ♪
- ♪ car wash, yeah ♪
- Yes!
- Oh, man.
- That's how you do that!
- Whoo!
- Thank you.
Show some pride.
This is crap.
I agree, yes. Crap.
Continue.
Now, folks, by special request,
we're going to take it
a little old school.
There is a former Trebler
in this room.
Who?
It's Mr. Andy Bernard!
No, do not sing that.
Do not-- oh, man.
He reminded us today
of how much he means to us,
and we certainly
seem to mean a lot to him,
so without any further ado,
here's an old Treble classic.
♪ Ah, ah, ah ♪
♪ dank, dank, dank,
dank, dank ♪
♪ dig-a, dank, dank, dank ♪
♪ a-well,
I guess it would be nice ♪
♪ if I could touch your body ♪
♪ I know not everybody
has got a body like you ♪
- ♪ but I gotta think twice ♪
- Whoa! Whoa!
♪ Before I give my heart away ♪
What the hell
is Broccoli Rob doing here?
She said
you wanted to hear Faith.
That's Broccoli Rob's
signature song.
♪ Oh, but I need some time off
from that emotion ♪
That's my signature song.
I really didn't know that, man.
I just thought
you wanted to hear it.
Russell, I'm dressed
like George Michael.
I thought
you were Adam Lambert.
Wha--
The more I hear about
all this a cappella drama,
the more I think
it's kind of pathetic,
but when you're with someone,
you put up with the stuff
that makes you
lose respect for them,
and that is love.
Are you okay?
- He's still mad.
- Okay.
Shut up, Broccoli.
Champ, I feel awful
about this whole thing.
Russell called me up,
and they said they needed
20 ccs of George Michael, stat,
so just... wham!
I sprang into action.
You know me.
I assumed you wanted to hear me
do your signature number.
You thought I wanted
to sit in the audience
like some slutty Treb rat?
A man's signature solo
is his for life.
Okay? That's group policy
and you know it.
Look, it's not my fault
I still live near campus,
and it's my duty as an alum
to be friendly
to the young guys,
and stop in two,
three times a week.
Just don't do the song anymore.
I'll tell you what...
We'll have a sing-off for it.
You pick 12 alums from any year
to back you up
and I'll do the same,
and I'm so confident
that I'll win,
I won't even warm up.
Fine, go ahead,
thrash your pipes.
My pipes are primo, Champ!
Why don't you ask
Trey Anastasio about my pipes?
I knew you would go there,
you son of a bitch!
He said, and I quote,
"hey, Rob, nice pipes."
- That happened!
- Okay, fine, yeah,
- that's one guy's opinion.
- That's real!
- That'll never change!
- Okay!
Okay, doesn't mean
you're the best singer ever!
Dick.
I thought that concert
was pretty great.
Oh, yeah. I decided
acapelca music is awesome.
They lost me
when they sang Monster Mash.
That song obviously
glorifies the occult.
Angela, it's Halloween.
You have to sing Monster Mash.
Oh, you have to, Jim?
You literally have to?
Uh...
No, I'm just--
I'm saying,
what would happen
if they didn't sing it?
Would they go to jail?
Would they be shot?
Okay.
We'll just forget it.
- No, no, I'm interested.
- Mm-hmm.
I mean, I think
everybody's interested
in why they have to sing it.
- 'Cause it is Halloween.
- Mm-hmm.
So if you're gonna
sing a concert,
it's a good idea
to throw that one in.
Yeah, yeah, no, no,
it's a good idea
to brush your teeth,
but you have to,
um, feed your children,
send them to school.
You know,
all things you can't do
if you just keep
singing Monster Mash.
It turns out Pam really,
really hates Monster Mash.
I mean, like, never bring
that song up in front of her.
Even though
Jim was making great points,
like, in favor of the song,
Pam was like,
"no. Hate it. Stupid."
This is all so silly, right?
What am I gonna do,
move back to Cornell?
Yeah.
I mean, what if we did that?
Like, we got jobs
and we were happy all the time?
Oh, well, Andy,
we're not moving to Cornell.
Duh, I know.
- That would be insane.
- Yeah.
It could totally work, though.
I don't know why we wouldn't.
Oh, my God, are we doing this?
Oy. Andy,
what is going on?
If I am not Boner Champ...
I don't know who I am.
Well, you know,
maybe you're the wise, old guy
that the new, um,
B-O-N-E-R Champ looks up to.
You know,
you could just--
Make a donation.
Well, I was gonna say
be a mentor.
Yes.
I'm gonna make a donation.
And it just so happens
I know someone
who works at
the Bernard family foundation.
- Her name is "mom."
- Oh.
I want some of those pills.
Oh.
Well, good for you.
I mean, you'll need
a prescription.
Oh, no. No, no, no,
they're not for me.
They're for my cousin Mose.
He's just having a tough time,
being wifeless
and a high-pressure job
and his crazy cousin Mose.
- Other cousin Mose.
- Mm.
Got it.
Well, you tell Mose
that he's a good man
and I hope he feels better.
Which one?
Mose or the real Mose?
The real Mose.
He says thank you.
Mom, I had
this really charitable idea
to set up a scholarship
for a cappella kids at Cornell,
and just need to wire
some money over there.
What?
♪ Far above the busy humming ♪
♪ of the bustling town ♪
♪ reared against the arch of
heaven looks she proudly down ♪
What's wrong?
My parents are broke.
♪ Lift the chorus,
speed it onward ♪
♪ loud her praises tell ♪
♪ hail to thee,
our alma mater ♪
♪ hail, all hail, Cornell ♪
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com