[Sighs]
I'm having second thoughts
about one
of the shirts I packed.
The blue one with the stripes.
I'm sure it's fine.
It's a blue shirt.
Well, yeah, but I'm wondering
if it's too blue.
Like, am I making
a statement with the blueness?
I am leaving early today
for Philly,
because tomorrow is
the first day of my new job.
So I figure
I'd get in at 5:00,
check into a hotel
at about 6:00
so I can get a real good night
of restless sleep
and nervous puking.
Uh, excuse me.
Trying to get work done.
Some people don't care
about Jim's new sports job
in Phila-whatever.
So you know my job
has something to do with sports,
but you don't know the end
of the word "Philadelphia"?
Philadelphia.
From the Greek philia,
meaning "love,"
and adelph,
meaning "Adolf."
"The city
that loves Adolf."
Good luck
with your new enterprise.
And don't wear
the blue striped shirt.
It makes your neck
look like an old mop handle.
Oh...
Hey, guys,
the Christmas party is today.
Merry Christmas, everyone!
- No.
- Is it?
- I mean,
it says "X-mas party,"
but I think we all know
what that's code for.
So we're not gonna have
a Christmas party this year?
Angela, how could you
do this to us?
Oh, right, like I'm responsible
'cause I'm in charge
of the party planning committee.
Well, you are
the one in charge of it.
Don't blame me
for something we all forgot.
Yeah, let's not blame her
I didn't realize how many of
Angela's opinions I agreed with,
until she tried
to have my kneecap shattered
for sleeping with her husband.
She makes a lot
of very sound points.
I knew the party was today,
but nobody asked me to plan it,
so I didn't.
Hmm, funny how that works.
[Scoffs] We're out there
sweating our balls off
every day,
bustin' our balls.
We deserve a Christmas party!
Well, then, why don't we
just get some liquor
- and those mini-cupcakes?
- Mini-cupcakes?
As in the mini version
of regular cupcakes,
which is already
a mini version of cake?
Honestly, where does it end
with you people?
What about an authentic
Pennsylvania Dutch Christmas?
Drink some gluhwein,
enjoy some hasenpfeffer.
Enjoy Christmas
with Saint Nicolas'
rural German companion,
Belsnickel.
Yes!
That, that, that!
We're definitely doing that.
Are we all in agreement?
- No.
- No!
- Done, right?
- No.
I want tropical Christmas.
- Topless Christmas.
- Tapas Swiss miss!
Spanish tapas
and Swiss miss hot cocoa--
what's so hard to understand?
Or, who was it that suggested
the authentic
Pennsylvania Dutch Christmas?
I think
it was someone really popular.
- We already said no.
- No, no, no.
Too weird.
This is me and my family
celebrating
Pennsylvania Dutch Christmas
in 1982 on the farm.
There's me and my brother jeb
breaking
the ceremonial pig rib.
He doesn't come back
for Christmas anymore.
The sepia tint
is from an app on my phone.
This is the same photo,
Matrix style.
I'm not understanding
the confusion.
Am I the only one
who wants to try
hufflepuffs and schnauzerhosen,
and meet this glenpickle guy?
[Shrill whistle blows]
Party planning committee,
emergency meeting.
Now.
- I'm on it.
- Right.
I'm just hoping
German terrorists
don't take over
this Christmas party.
Make me go
all John McClane on their asses.
Wait, German terrorists?
That's oddly specific.
And I think--
I think you mean John McCain.
Die Hard reference.
- I haven't seen it.
- You haven't seen Die Hard?
- Mm-mmm.
- Why haven't you seen Die Hard?
I don't know, I just haven't.
Come on, you had to have
at least seen some of it.
No.
"Now, I have a machine gun.
Ho, ho, ho."
[As Bruce Willis]
"Come out to the coast,
we'll get together,
have a few laughs."
None of this
makes any sense to me!
Oh, yeah, and when he takes
the gun off his back,
and he's like,
"yippie-ki-yay, mother--"
Actually,
he doesn't say that there.
He says it earlier when
he's on the radio with Hans.
Yes, you are right.
Forgive me.
- Oh, that's okay, bud.
- Nope.
- Common mistake.
- No, it's not.
Nerd!
Do you know
every line of the movie?
My brother dared me
to memorize it,
and I did it,
and I loved doing it.
Okay, let's hear it.
- Hear what?
- Die Hard.
Every line.
Go.
You don't like flying, do you?
Don't change the subject.
No, that's the--
Movie is starting.
We're thinking of collaborating
with Mike Schmidt
on some of his charity work.
I love Philly.
Dirty town.
Ah-ha-ha!
Philly!
- Exciting stuff, man.
- Whoo!
So you sure you remembered
everything for your trip?
- Yeah, I think so.
- Think that through for a sec.
Yeah, Jim's going
to Philly tomorrow.
He said he was gonna
take me with him,
but that was two months ago.
And I haven't heard
anything since.
I mean, he said that, right?
What else could you possibly
be forgetting?
- Uh--
- Things? People?
[Chuckles nervously]
You know who's not
gonna get to work
on some exciting
new startup this year?
George Howard Skub,
AKA the alleged
Scranton strangler,
because he's in prison
for something
he may not have done.
I'm sorry, the--
uh, the Scranton who?
The Scranton strangler.
George Howard Skub.
Haven't I told you
about the jury
I was on a couple years ago?
[Gasps] Oh, what happened?
I mean, if you can
talk about it, obviously.
Because if you can't,
I mean, I understand.
I-- I could--
I could talk about it.
See you next Christmas.
I could, sure.
Have a seat.
I would start at the beginning,
but I think I need
to go farther back.
We're the party
planning committee,
and we did not get where we are
by playing it safe.
We got here
by being risk takers.
And, yeah,
Dwight's party
is gonna be terrible.
Maybe.
Maybe it's not.
Maybe it's going to be great.
And, if it's great...
I think we all know
what that would mean to us.
Let's do it.
Yes.
Phyllis!
No.
I don't want my name
attached to this party.
What does that even mean?
Where would your name appear?
Please just take my name
off of everything.
Just take her name
[Clears throat]
The party planning committee,
minus Angela,
has decided that we're all going
to do Dwight's Christmas.
Yes!
Yeah!
Okay!
Yes!
It's a Christmas miracle!
Yeah!
- Whoo-hoo!
- Dwight, there is one rule
that you need
to take very seriously.
- Uh-huh.
- And that is...
Uh-oh.
That there are no rules.
You have never been cooler.
Best Christmas ever.
- You're welcome.
- Thank you.
And Pennsylvania Dutch Christmas
has officially begun.
Ugh.
What is this stuff, lava?
That is gluhwein,
otherwise known as glow-wine,
also used to sterilize
medical instruments.
And, interesting factoid,
this is the very spoon
that guided my soft skull
through the birth canal
when I was born.
- Enjoy.
- What is it?
Don't touch it.
- Somebody's found the hog maw.
- Oh!
What?
It's a Pennsylvania
Dutch specialty.
Hog maw.
That's a beauty, isn't it?
I don't even want
to tell you what it's made of
until after you try it.
Ugh.
I'm not eating mystery meat.
It is stuffed pig stomach.
And, after we finish it,
we get to break the pig rib.
- Can't wait.
- Weird.
Where are the sugar cookies?
Where's the karaoke machine?
This is austere, Meredith.
This is celebrating Christmas
for all of the right reasons.
The cookies and toys and sweets
are mere distractions.
I mean, most people
don't even know
that a candy cane
represents a shepherd's crook,
which I assure you
does not taste like peppermint.
It tastes like sheep feces.
How would anyone even know--
Have you ever tasted
a shepherd's crook?
I don't know.
Is it what you expected?
I feel like--
Dwight is holding a candle
and reading a poem.
So happy right now.
[Speaking German]
Wait, what is that I hear?
Is someone on the roof?
How strange.
Excuse me.
I have to run to my car
to take a dump.
I wish my car had a bathroom.
"Let Heinrich
plant the detonators
and Theo prepare the vault.
- After that--"
- Eh. That wasn't the line.
I'm sorry, Pete.
That is transcribed
by some fan.
They make mistakes.
I don't know.
This looks pretty legit.
[Cell phone chimes]
Oh, my gosh.
I just got an email from Andy.
That means they hit land.
"What up, shorty?
We got in last night,
sold the boat,
went out, got drunk,
saw Life of Pi,
got super depressed
and introspective.
Gonna hang out here a while.
Maybe a couple of weeks.
Figure
this whole life thing out.
Maybe see Hobbit.
Lates."
Hey.
Everything okay?
So what comes next?
Right, um, okay.
So he says,
"after we call the police,
they'll waste hours
trying to negotiate--"
We should just watch the movie.
That makes much more sense.
Or we can just sit
and talk, though.
No.
No more talking.
It's movie time.
I mean, are you sure...
Yeah, I probably have
a copy or two in my car.
Oh, great.
Great!
So we're
watching Die Hard, now.
Good! This is a good plan.
Okay.
Here's the thing
about moonlight.
It's not sunlight.
[Mouth full]
I love this hog mama.
Dwight said it's "hog maw."
[Chokes]
What is maw?
It's the lining
of the stomach of--
[Cackling] Ohh...
[German accent]
Judgment is nigh,
for the Belsnickel ist I!
Yes, he is finally nigh.
I am nigh!
Every year, my grandfather
would dress up as Belsnickel
at Christmas.
He was... okay at it.
I am great.
You know how they say some
people were born to be bad?
Well, I was born
to be Belsnickel.
Ohh, Belsnickel
has traveled from distant lands
to discover how
all the boys and the girls
have been behaving
this last year.
Whoo hoo hoo hoo hoo!
Ohh... too much strudel.
So he's kind of like Santa,
except dirty and worse.
No, much better--
no one fears Santa
the way they fear Belsnickel.
Wow. It's my favorite
part of Christmas.
The authority.
- And the fear.
- Yes, exactly!
Come on, Dwight,
you're making this up.
- No...
- This is a real thing.
"Belsnickel is a crotchety,
fur-clad gift giver
related to other companions
of St. Nicholas
in the folklore
of Southwestern Germany."
- Ah.
- Wow.
Okay, great.
Seriously, you guys?
Now you believe
in Dwight's traditions,
when some Democrat looks it up
on Wikipedia?
"His partner, Zwarte Piet,
or Black Peter, a slave boy,
often portrayed in colorful
pantaloons and blackface."
Uh-uh.
No, Dwight. No.
Oh, come on.
We don't blindly stick
to every outmoded aspect
of our traditions.
Come on, get with the spirit
of it, you guys.
[Phone blips]
[Cell phone buzzes]
[Suspenseful music]
Okay, Karl was actually
a ballet dancer in real life.
- Isn't that crazy?
- Mm. [Chuckles]
Jim, that guy.
[Scoffs]
You gotta stick to your word!
Like when you say something
to a buddy,
a real buddy...
what are you gonna do, lie?
To your buddy?
[Sighs] It's awful.
Take a bowl and pass it down.
Thank you, Dwight.
These are nice.
No, these are gift bowls.
When you receive a gift,
it will go in the bowl,
but the bowls must be
returned at the end.
They're a set.
Now, hold your bowls forward.
The Belsnickel will decide
if you are impish
or admirable.
Oh, it's like naughty or nice.
No, impish or admirable.
Quick question--
do you just decide
who gets what in the moment,
or did you make a list?
- I decided earlier.
- Oh. Nice.
- Did you check that list?
- Of course I checked it.
But more than once? 'Cause you
could have made a mistake.
- I checked it more than once.
- Okay, so you made a list,
you checked it twice, and now
you're gonna find out who's--
Impish or admirable.
Damn.
Phyllis Vance!
Cheer or fear?
Belsnickel is here.
I judge your year as...
admirable.
There you are.
Oh. What are these?
It's a set of rubber gaskets
for canning jars.
- I'd rather have the bowl.
- You can't have the bowl!
Oscar Martinez,
cheer or fear?
Belsnickel is here.
I judge your year...
as impish!
Ow! You hit people
with that thing?
No, I'm carrying
around the stick
in order to look cool.
For the kinder.
Ooh.
Mouse trap.
In a head-to-head contest,
people prefer Belsnickel
over Santa every time.
There aren't as many songs
about him,
but I attribute that more
to rhyming difficulties.
My brother and I
wrote one once.
It was about
a fickle pickle salesman
who would tickle you
for a nickel.
[Giggling] Oh, you know what?
- I gotta go.
- Stop giggling.
Oh, really?
Already?
- Yeah, it's all right.
- It's a punishment.
Hey, where are you going?
I have to go to Philly.
But this was amazing.
- Okay?
- But you work tomorrow.
Yeah, I know,
I'd just like to settle in
and get a good night's sleep.
But we were gonna
break the pig rib.
- Ohh.
- Remember?
That's right.
No matter!
Belsnickel cares not
about this--
off with you!
Perfect.
Merry Christmas, everybody.
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Don't you want to know
your present?
You know what?
Yeah. Have at it.
Jim Halpert, cheer or fear?
Belsnickel is here.
I judge your year as impish.
Ohh! Are you nuts?
- I judge you impish!
- Ow! Ow!
Okay, that is three,
and you didn't
hit anybody that hard.
They're not
abandoning the party.
Just-- just-- hey!
[Shouts indistinctly]
That's enough, I'm done!
- Okay? Agh!
- Impish!
Aah! Ow!
Belsnickel,
I gotta run out early too.
[All groan]
Oh...
what was that?
Now I'm gonna be all whipped
for my first day at work.
God.
One second.
- Oh...
- Well...
this is it.
I'm probably never gonna
see you again.
Shut up.
I'm trying to be serious.
Okay, sorry, sorry.
I can't believe
this is actually happening.
Listen, thank you so much
for putting that all together.
That was the perfect
last Christmas party.
All right, wish me luck?
Okay.
Good luck.
You're gonna be great.
I'll call you when I get in.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Love you.
[Laughter, indistinct chatter]
[Elevator bell dings]
- What's going on?
- Party's over.
You quit on Christmas,
Christmas quits on you.
And guess what, kids.
Belsnickel isn't real.
It's me, Dwight!
We found some old decorations
on the warehouse.
Oscar ran to the store
for some food and drink,
and I dipped into
my stash of eggnog.
I guess they needed me
after all.
It's like in
It's a Wonderful Life
when Jimmy Stewart realizes
that all those people
at the building and loan
were just jerks,
and he was the real hero.
Kevin. Kevin! Aaah.
Stop it!
Oh, it sounds like the party's
- starting up out there.
- Yeah.
So anyway, the entire jury
wants me to vote guilty.
But then I did a little
research of my own,
and forget everything
you thought you knew
about fingerprinting.
Meredith's a little cute.
I'm just realizing.
She got, like,
a Emma Stone thing.
[We Wish You a Merry Christmas
playing]
♪
Boo!
For what it's worth,
I liked your party better.
Everyone thought
the food was gross,
and that Belsnickel was some
darkly erotic freak.
I don't think anyone
thought that.
Jim couldn't even stay
till the end of the party.
Well, that didn't have
anything to do with you.
I don't care.
Guess how much I care
- on a scale of one to ten.
- Zero.
Damn it!
I'm gonna tell Jim
to go fuck himself.
[Groaning]
Do you think Andy would ever
jump off an exploding building
tied to a hose for me?
Yeah.
Definitely.
[Explosions, screams on TV]
[Sobs]
Hey, what's--
oh, no, come here.
Hey, hey.
Come on, huh?
I'm still Andy's girlfriend.
Oh, yeah, of course.
I know.
But you can leave your arm.
[Overlapping chatter]
Dwight, want me
to get you some eggnog?
No, thanks. I'll just have
another Dumatril.
Jim taught me
this really cool way to take it.
You crush it into a powder,
and you snort it up your butt.
Yep, I did say that.
- Jim!
- What's going on?
Where's the Belsnickel?
Oh--
oh, my God!
What are you doing?
Last time I saw you, you were
whipping me out of the building.
Shh.
Let's not speak of that.
The pig rib.
We could totally break
the pig rib!
I'm gonna dig it out
of the trash.
What happened?
Did you miss your bus?
No. I just missed
my wife.
I found it!
And I found out
that there's a bus
at 5:00 AM.
[All cheering and chanting]
Oh!
[All groan]
Damn it!
Jim got the bigger half.
Back for more, huh?
Ooh, nog it.
Let me get some nog.
[Indistinct chatter]
Thanks, Phyllis.
Where's Andy?
- You!
- Oh, hey, man.
Oh, you know what?
Before I forget again,
I talked to the guys
about hiring you.
They're gonna bring you in
for an interview.
That's great.
Right?
- Thanks, man.
- Hey, of course.
I shall come by
at your convenience.
Thank you, sir.
- Whoo!
- Go get 'em.
Oh! Whoa!
[Alarmed shouts]
Very impish.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Two dimes, seven nickels--
well, okay,
no, that doesn't add up.
- It was one quarter and--
- Shh.
What?
I was just explaining--
Shh.
- Why wouldn't it--
- Shh.
- But why?
- No... more... talking.
Are you gonna kiss me?
Yes.